Chapter 602: Parting Ways

Han Li took a glance at his surroundings, then turned to Daoist Xie as he said, "We've already wasted enough time, so let's keep going, Brother Xie."

Daoist Xie nodded in response, then flew onto the green flying carriage before releasing an incantation seal, and the carriage immediately sped away as a streak of green light.

At the center of the carriage, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, assessing his own internal condition.

Even though his baleful decay had already been delayed by time law powers imbued within the thread of time, the baleful qi in his body still hadn't receded at all, and three of his originally uncontaminated immortal acupoints had also been infiltrated by baleful qi.

Han Li's heart sank slightly upon seeing this, but a thought then suddenly occurred to him, and he opened his eyes before flicking a finger through the air, conjuring up a mirror of water in front of himself.

Through his reflection in the mirror, Han Li could see bursts of gray light occasionally flashing through his eyes, turning his pupils a murky gray color, and it seemed that the frequency at which his pupils were turning gray had increased from before.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li swept away the mirror as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Given what he currently knew, it appeared that the Northern Glacial Immortal Region was only a small and rather secluded immortal region in the True Immortal Realm, one that had barely any High Zenith cultivators. Hence, even though he had been trying to gather information on the five decays, his efforts had largely proven to be futile.

On top of that, his current situation was rather different from the normal fifth decay that one could expect to experience, and his only option at this point was to try and find a solution after he reached the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

All of a sudden, another thought occurred to Han Li, and he flipped a hand over to produce his Dragon 5 Reincarnation Palace mask before putting it on.

Sure enough, there had already been quite a few responses to the requests that he had made for Origin Void Pill refinement ingredients.

Close to an hour later, as Han Li stowed away the mask again, a small pile of these ingredients had already appeared beside him.

He instructed Daoist Xie and the others to keep a close eye on Jin Tong, then quickly scoured the surrounding area to ensure that nothing was amiss before sweeping a sleeve through the air to summon his silver pill cauldron.

With another sweep of his sleeve, his Flame of Essence was released, and it landed beneath the cauldron in its miniature humanoid form.

A burst of terrifying heat instantly erupted out of the fiery figure's body, and it seemed to have become even more powerful than before.

The fiery figure yelled something unintelligible up at Han Li in an excited voice, then sat down before making a hand seal, and the scorching white flames all over its body instantly surged forth as 12 uniform bursts that evenly coated the underside of the cauldron.

Before long, the interior of the cauldron had become extremely hot.

Thanks to the pill refinement experience that he had accrued back in the Soul Stirring Winds, Han Li was extremely familiar with the process of refining Origin Void Pills. The only problem was that he would have to make some adjustments for balancing purposes as the Black Marrow Crystals that he was using were of a far superior quality to before.

However, this was not a major problem for him, given that he had the power of time laws on his side.

After taking a deep breath to compose himself, Han Li picked up one of the ingredients before tossing it into the cauldron to commence the pill refinement process.

Seven or eight years flew by in a flash.

The green flying carriage continued to race over the boundless primordial land, speeding over all types of different terrains.

The route that had been marked out on the map provided by the patriarch of the Heavenly Fox Race required them to go on a far longer journey than if they were to cross the primordial land in a straight line, but it did prove to be a very safe route.

Occasionally, some primordial beasts would get in their way, but none of them stood a chance against Mo Guang, Daoist Xie, and Xiao Bai.

All the while, Han Li remained seated within a light barrier, casting a string of incantation seals into the silver cauldron in front of him.

Right at this moment, a burst of silver light flashed over the cauldron, and the lid flew off on its own to reveal a glistening black Origin Void Pill inside.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he carefully stowed the pill away, then stowed the silver cauldron and the Flame of Essence away as well.

Up to this point, he had exhausted all of the ingredients that he had purchased, and with those ingredients, he had managed to refine around two dozen Origin Void Pills.

He picked up one of the pills, then scrutinized it for a moment before swallowing it.

He had to take one of the pills to ensure that it was indeed what he needed.

As soon as the Origin Void Pill entered his stomach, it immediately began to melt, turning into a burst of cold power that flowed through his body.

Nothing of particular interest took place. The power of the pill merely resonated somewhat with the baleful qi in his body, but it did nothing aside from that.

However, Han Li knew that the pill took some time to truly take effect, so he wasn't overly concerned, and he closed his eyes to meditate while waiting for the pill to do its work.

Close to a year passed by.

All of a sudden, the burst of cold power formed by the Origin Void Pill drew to a halt near Han Li's lower abdomen, where it transformed into a strange vortex that was constantly revolving while forming a special connection with the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints.

The baleful qi in his body gradually began to fall dormant, and even the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints had become a lot more sluggish.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he flicked a finger through the air to conjure up a mirror of water, and through his reflection, he could see that the gray light in his eyes had already completely faded, restoring his pupils to close to their original color.

This was naturally quite a relief.

If his pupils were to occasionally turn gray once he entered the Black Mountain Immortal Region, then it most likely wouldn't be long before he became a target of the Heavenly Court.

Even though he could take certain measures to disguise the abnormal coloration of his eyes, there was no guarantee that he wouldn't be exposed. Now that his baleful qi had entered a dormant state and his pupils had largely returned to normal, his chances of being exposed were significantly decreased.

This supply of Origin Void Pills should be enough to last him and Mo Guang quite some time in the Black Mountain Immortal Region, but as a safety precaution, Han Li released a few more missions for the acquisition of Origin Void Pill ingredients in the Transient Guild.

Right at this moment, a dull thud suddenly rang out.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to remove the surrounding restrictions, and a hint of elation immediately appeared on his face as he identified the source of the sound.

At this moment, the golden ball within the cloud at the end of the flying carriage was glowing radiantly, while the cloud had been stirred up into a frenzy.

An enormous aura was surging out of the golden ball in all directions, and Xiao Bai was roused from its slumber as it hurriedly rose to its haunches.

Mo Guang was seated with his legs crossed on the other side of the flying carriage, and he only opened his mouth to take a glance in the golden ball's direction before closing his eyes again.

"Brother Xie, find a place to stop the carriage," Han Li instructed.

Daoist Xie did as it was told, casting an incantation seal into the flying carriage, upon which it immediately swooped down before drawing to a halt in a misty valley.

All the while, the golden light radiating from the golden ball was becoming brighter and brighter, and at this point, it was glowing as radiantly as the sun.

Han Li cast an incantation seal to withdraw the white flag, and almost immediately thereafter, a series of cracks appeared on the surface of the golden ball, then quickly spread before a massive hole was blasted into its surface, following which a slender figure emerged from within.

It was a young girl who appeared to be in her teens, and she had shoulder-length golden hair and a set of gorgeous facial features.

With her emergence, the golden ball exploded into a vast expanse of golden powder that rained down into the valley below.

The young girl began to make her way toward Han Li and the others, and even though golden powder was falling all around her, none of it was able to land on her at all.

"You're... Jin Tong, right?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

Both this young girl's appearance and aura were completely different from Jin Tong's, and the only similarity that they shared was the color of their hair.

This made Han Li feel as if he were looking at someone completely alien to him, and Xiao Bai was also staring at the girl with a dumbstruck expression at a loss for what to do.

The girl gave Han Li a nod, then stretched lazily as she said, "Even now, when I look back on what happened over these past years, it still feels like a dream."

Her voice had also changed drastically, and it was extremely pleasing to the ears, but was completely devoid of emotion.

Han Li's brows remained furrowed as he scrutinized Jin Tong with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and some skepticism still remained on his face.

"Why are you looking at me like that, Uncle? If I'm not Jin Tong, then who am I? The Gold Devouring Immortal that was chasing after us? I've gained a lot of new memories after devouring that thing, but I'm still the same Jin Tong from before," Jin Tong said as a mischievous smile appeared on her face, only to fade immediately thereafter.

"Have you recalled something?" Han Li asked as his brows finally unfurrowed.

Through their spiritual connection, he could tell beyond a reasonable doubt that this was indeed Jin Tong.

Jin Tong was silent for a moment, then suddenly extended a curtsey toward Han Li as she said, "Thank you for looking after me for so long, Uncle. Without you, I would've never been able to make it to this point."

"Why are you suddenly saying this?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"I want to go out on my own and search for other Gold Devouring Immortals," Jin Tong replied.

"Have you already found some other Gold Devouring Immortals?" Han Li asked.

"No, but I have a vague sense of where they are," Jin Tong replied.

"While it's true that you've become significantly more powerful than before, I still don't think its safe for you to go off on your own," Han Li said.

"Master's right, the True Immortal Realm is a really dangerous place! Why don't you stay with Master? You'll always have stuff to eat, and with your combined powers, even if you encounter another late-High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal, you'll be able to take it down together!" Xiao Bai said.

Jin Tong was completely unmoved, and she shook her head as she said, "Searching for other Gold Devouring Immortals is my destiny. You also have things that you need to do as well, don't you, Uncle?"

Han Li fell silent upon hearing this.

Xiao Bai opened its mouth to say something, but decided against it after seeing the determined look on Jin Tong's face.

After a brief silence, Han Li asked, "Have you made up your mind?"

Jin Tong nodded in response.

Chapter 603: A Game of Go

"In that case, I won't try to stop you. As the saying goes, all unions must conclude with separation someday," Han Li sighed.

Jin Tong extended another curtsey toward Han Li, then turned to depart, but Han Li called out to stop her before tossing an intricate green jade bracelet at her.

Jin Tong reflexively caught the bracelet, and Han Li explained, "There's a map of the primordial land inside, as well as some spirit treasures and Immortal Origin Stones, which should be enough to last you a while. Aside from that, there are also a few Transient Guild masks in there. If you need anything, feel free to reach out to me."

When it came to Jin Tong, his feelings were very mixed. To him, she was like an intimate comrade, but also like a daughter that he had raised from birth.

A complex look flashed through Jin Tong's eyes at the sight of the bracelet, but she didn't refuse it, and she silently put it on her left wrist.

"I'll go with you, Jin Tong," Xiao Bai suddenly said before springing over to her side, much to Jin Tong's surprise.

"You said that you were making me your lackey, so you can't just leave me behind!" Xiao Bai said as it rubbed its head against the back of Jin Tong's hand.

"Take Xiao Bai with you. If you run into any other Gold Devouring Immortals more powerful than yourself, you'll at least be able to hide in Xiao Bai's stomach for some time," Han Li said.

"Alright, I'll take you with me, but you better hurry up and get stronger! If you dare to get in my way, then I'll leave you behind without a second thought!" Jin Tong threatened as she patted Xiao Bai on the head.

Xiao Bai immediately nodded in response with an ecstatic expression.

"By the way, I once read in a scripture that a Gold Devouring Immortal of unknown power seemed to have appeared some time ago in the Golden Origin Immortal Region. I don't know if it's still there, but you can go to try your luck there if you can't find any other leads," Han Li said.

"I see. Thank you, Uncle. Take care," Jin Tong replied with a nod, then took one final glance at Han Li before speeding away with Xiao Bai as a streak of golden light, instantly vanishing into the distance.

Han Li looked on in the direction that Jin Tong had departed in for some time before withdrawing his gaze, following which he instructed in a calm manner, "Let's continue."

Shortly thereafter, a streak of green light rose up from the ground before speeding away into the distance.

Moments later, a burst of spatial fluctuations emerged nearby, and Jin Tong and Xiao Bai re-emerged onto the scene.

"Uncle, I would love to stay with you for longer, but what I'm going to be facing from here onward is far more perilous than what you can imagine... We only just barely survived this ordeal by the skin of our teeth, I really don't want to be a burden to you anymore," Jin Tong murmured to herself in a forlorn voice.

"Surely there was no need to do this," Xiao Bai said in a timid voice. "Even though I've only been with Master for a short time, my instincts as a primordial true spirit tell me that he's a good person, and he definitely doesn't mind having you around as a burden."

"So you're saying I really am a burden to him?" Jin Tong asked as she turned to Xiao Bai with a hostile expression.

"N-no, what I meant to say is that you're so wise and powerful, you could easily explore this world on your own!" Xiao Bai hurriedly amended.

"Even though I've managed to recover some of my memories, some things are still quite unclear to me. However, I get a vague sense that I don't just seem to be an ordinary spirit insect. Xiao Bai, you've decided to follow me, so I'll be sure to treat you well. As long as you help me find what's rightfully mine, you can eat anything you want from here onward," Jin Tong said.

"Rest assured, I'll follow your every command and eat anything that you tell me to!" Xiao Bai declared with a serious expression.

"You've become just as much of an ass-kisser as Mo Guang!" Jin Tong scoffed in a disdainful voice, then flew away into the distance. "Let's go. According to this map, the Golden Origin Immortal Region is very far away."

"Wait for me!" Xiao Bai hurriedly called out as it set off in pursuit.

......

In the northern region of the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

There was a peaceful valley that was filled with lush, green bamboo trees, and a clear stream was flowing through the center of the valley. The bamboo forest on either bank of the creek was filled with mist, and the clear and pleasant call of an oriole could occasionally be heard.

Deep in the forest, wild deer with white pelts that carried cherry blossom patterns could be seen traversing through the undergrowth.

The midsection of the stream was situated in the steepest and most precarious part of the valley, with jagged rocks on either bank. From there, the stream flowed down a long and winding curve, then pooled into a deep, green pond.

To the left of the pond was a huge stone platform, atop which sat an azure-robed middle-aged man with his legs crossed, strumming a dark purple guqin.

The man had a set of handsome facial features and a head of long hair that spilled down his back. His slim and fair fingers were gently strumming over the strings of the guqin, producing wonderful music to complement the sound of the flowing stream.

Seated across from the azure-robed man was an elderly man with a head of black hair and another elderly man with a head of white hair, playing a game of go.

The black-haired elderly man's clothes were pristine and completely devoid of creases, while his black hair was also immaculately groomed, giving him a very clean and sharp appearance, much like a drawn sword.

In contrast, the white-haired elderly man seated across from him was far less meticulous in maintaining her appearance. He was wearing a white robe with some embroidered flame designs littered haphazardly over it, and his hair was completely wild and disheveled as he sat in a bleary-eyed fashion.

The black-haired elderly man had the white stones, and he played each move swiftly and forcefully, ensuring that there was an audible clack with each stone that he placed down. In contrast, the white-haired elderly man was far slower to make his moves, and he also placed his stones down much more softly and quietly.

The black-haired elderly man seemed to be accustomed to this, and he didn't urge his opponent to play faster, merely closing his eyes after making each move to calculate how the position could unfold.

A brown-robed elderly man was watching the game, and he chugged down a mouthful of wine, then complained, "As usual, you're unbearably slow, you old fart! If I didn't know any better, I'd suspect you to be an old turtle that attained a human form through cultivation!"

"If you don't have anything nice to say, then keep your mouth shut! Fellow Daoist Duan hasn't even said anything, why are you chirping, you old drunkard? Go drink your horse piss!" the white-haired elderly man scoffed, but it was clear that he wasn't actually enraged.

"How long did that game between you and Lu Guanzi from the Sunny Valley drag on for? 30 years! In the end, you stalled for so long that he couldn't bear it anymore and resigned..."

Before he had a chance to finish, the white-haired elderly man loudly interjected, "That's because Lu Guanzi heard that an extremely beautiful female True Immortal had come from the Rainbow Phoenix Valley, and he couldn't resist the urge to go and take a look. Otherwise, that game would've gone on for at least 20 more years!"

"Extremely beautiful my arse! I went to go see her as well, and at the very most, she's only above average. Only someone with terrible taste like Lu Guanzi would be into someone like that," the brown-robed elderly man scoffed with a shake of his head.

The white-haired elderly man massaged his own chin as he stared intently at the go board. It seemed that he had found himself in a difficult position, and he was ignoring the brown-robed elderly man to focus on the game.

"Talking to the three of you is no fun at all. I wonder what Fellow Daoist Li is up to. He hasn't been around for a while," the brown-robed elderly man mused as he turned to take a glance at the entrance of the valley.

The azure-robed man stopped strumming his guqin upon hearing this, then turned to the brown-robed elderly man as he said, "I heard that Fellow Daoist Li has been refining a batch of Five Stone Pills of late. I sent a message to him some days ago, but I've received no response, so I presume he's still in seclusion."

As soon as his voice trailed off, an azure-robed young man emerged from deep within the bamboo forest, then began to approach the stone platform where the four men were gathered.

The man was none other than Han Li, who was wearing a disguise adopted using his Reincarnation Palace mask, and it had already been over 400 years since he parted ways with Jin Tong and Xiao Bai in the primordial land.

At this point, Han Li had been living in this Floating Cloud Valley for close to 200 years.

The brown-robed man immediately rose to his feet at the sight of Han Li and yelled, "You're finally here, Fellow Daoist Li! Come and have a drink with me!"

The two elderly men seated at the go table also returned their stone to their respective holders, then rose to their feet as well. As for the guqin-strumming young man, he remained seated, but he had also turned to Han Li with a friendly smile.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he rose up into the air, then descended onto the giant stone platform.

"Fellow Daoist Hot Flame, Fellow Daoist Jingyang, Fellow Daoist Duan, Fellow Daoist Ziqi, my apologies for my tardiness," Han Li said with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute toward the four men present.

"Don't worry about it. You're a pill refinement master, so your priority should be pill refinement. Only useless old men like us who have nothing to do can waste our time pursuing such trivial hobbies," the white-robed elderly man chuckled.

His name was Immortal Lord Hot Flame, and he was the grand elder of a medium-sized sect in the Black Mountain Immortal Region. He was a very lazy man who didn't want to have to attend to any official sect duties, so he had dumped all of his responsibilities onto a junior martial brother of his and came to the Floating Cloud Valley to live a life of leisure.

Despite his disheveled appearance, he actually possessed the highest cultivation base of the four men at the late-Golden Immortal Stage.

Chapter 604: Relaxation and Leisure

The black-haired elderly man who had been playing go with Immortal Lord Hot Flame was named Duan Yuzai, and he was also from the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

As for the guqin-strumming man and the brown-robed man, they were Yu Ziqi and Daoist Master Jingyang, respectively. Both of them had traveled to the Black Mountain Immortal Region from other immortal regions, and one of them was at the late-True Immortal Stage, while the other was at the late-Golden Immortal Stage.

Despite the vast cultivation base disparity between them, they shared the closest bond out of the four men present.

Aside from Han Li and these four men, there were many more cultivators residing in the 72 valleys and 36 ravines of the Floating Cloud Mountain Range.

Most of them were itinerant cultivators or traveling immortals who had no chance of making any further progress in their cultivation, so they settled down here to live out peaceful and leisurely lives instead of continuing to toil away in the world of cultivation.

Over time, the Floating Cloud Mountain Range gained a new name, which was "Relaxation Mountain".

The valley that Han Li and these four men resided in was originally called the Cloud Deer Valley, but it had since been renamed to the Leisure Valley.

There was a set of rules that had to be followed in the mountain range, which prohibited residents from prying into the past of other residents, forbade conflicts and battles from taking place in the mountain range, and also forbade any external powers from disrupting the order in the area.

According to Immortal Lord Hot Flame, these rules had been established by an itinerant cultivator who had once resided in the mountain range. Initially, no one paid any heed to these rules, but the cultivator was extremely brutal in enforcing those rules, and he had the power to match, killing everyone who dared to break his rules. As a result, everyone was forced to follow those rules.

Apparently, that cultivator held an important post in the Heavenly Court, and following their departure, those rules gradually became set in stone on Relaxation Mountain, even in their absence.

"Relaxing and pursuing trivial hobbies is the norm here on Relaxation Mountain, so I'm the odd one out here. My constant seclusion and pill refinement really brings shame to the good name of this place," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"Thank heavens you're a pill refinement master. If it wasn't for that Golden Soul Pill that you provided in such a timely and generous fashion, I would've surely perished while attempting my Golden Immortal Stage breakthrough," Duan Yuzai said with a serious expression.

"Please don't mention this every time you see me, Fellow Daoist Duan. I just so happened to have a spare Golden Soul Pill on hand, and after that, you were the one who introduced me to this place, so you've repaid me for the favor," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"You saved my life! How could I possibly ever repay you?" Duan Yuzai protested as a hint of guilt flashed through his eyes.

Han Li was already accustomed to Duan Yuzai's serious personality, so he knew that there was no point in dwelling on this subject any further.

Hence, he looked around momentarily, then changed the subject as he asked, "Where's Celestial Maiden Mo? Is she late as well?"

"You know what Mo Wuxue's like, she's gone to meditate on the Light Breeze Cliff," Yu Ziqi scoffed.

"Meditate my arse, all she does is stare off into space for decades, even centuries at a time! There are a lot of strange people gathered in this mountain range, but she surely ranks near the top," Daoist Master Jingyang scoffed with a hint of disdain in his voice.

"Even if pursuing the Great Dao is bound to be a futile endeavor, she still shouldn' just waste her life like this. Instead, why not enjoy some mortal pleasures in the time that we have left?" Yu Ziqi sighed in a slightly wistful manner.

Han Li knew that Yu Ziqi had been harboring romantic feelings for Mo Wuxue for quite some time, and he jibed, "Some mortal pleasures are impossible to enjoy alone, so you have to give her a hand."

Yu Ziqi's smile remained unchanged, but he could only heave an internal sigh.

Mo Wuxue was an early-Golden Immortal cultivator, while he was only at the late-True Immortal Stage. On top of that, with his limited aptitude, there was no hope for him to ever reach the Golden Immortal Stage, and with the five decays constantly looming, he simply couldn't bring himself to ask her to be his dao partner.

Right at this moment, Daoist Master Jingyang approached Han Li with a fawning smile as he asked, "By the way, I hear that you've recently been refining a batch of Five Stone Pills, Fellow Daoist Li. can you sell one to me?"

"Sell? I can't accept any money from you, Fellow Daoist Jingyang," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

Daoist Master Jingyang's smile instantly widened even further upon hearing this, but his smile then immediately stiffened once he heard what Han Li had to say next.

"There's no need for you to buy a Five Stone Pill from me, just give me a flagon of your Green Fermented Wine in exchange."

Green Fermented Wine was a very special type of wine that Daoist Master Jingyang had learned to brew from an ancient scripture. It incorporated the essence of over 100 different precious spirit plants, and it was no less precious than a Five Stone Pill.

Everyone was very amused by the sight of the pained look on Daoist Master Jingyang's face at the thought of having to part with a flagon of his precious wine.

Ultimately, Daoist Master Jingyang was unwilling to give up a flagon of his wine, and he grumbled to himself, "I don't need any pills, wine tastes much better anyway..."

An amused smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he suddenly swept a sleeve through the air to release four streaks of light, each of which flew toward one of the four men on the stone platform.

The four men hurriedly caught the streaks of light to discover that each of them contained a white jade vial.

"What's this, Fellow Daoist Li?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

"There's one Five Stone Pill for each of you in those vials, but I'm not giving out any more than that!" Han Li said.

The four men were very surprised to hear this. Five Stone Pills were Golden Immortal Stage pills that were very effective both for cultivation base consolidation and cultivation advancement, so it was definitely not something to be given out casually like this.

"To tell you the truth, I'm giving all of you these pills because I have something to request of you," Han Li said. "I'm sure all of you have already noticed the abnormal abundance of baleful qi in my body. Right now, I'm enduring the baleful decay."

A hint of enlightenment appeared on the faces of the four men upon hearing this.

They all knew that the five decays were unavoidable, and that this was perhaps going to be a hurdle that would stump them as well, so they were very sympathetic to Han LI's situation.

"A while ago, I obtained a recipe for a pill that can temporarily ward off baleful qi backlash, but I've been struggling to find an ingredient for the pill known as the Profound Zoysia Crystal, and I'm hoping that all of you can help me search for it," Han Li continued.

The recipe that he was speaking of was for a pill by the name of the Baleful Quelling Pill, and it was an obscure pill recipe that he had obtained from the Transient Guild. As opposed to temporarily warding off the baleful qi backlash, the pill was actually capable of cleansing baleful qi to help Golden Immortals overcome the baleful decay.

However, this was only the purported effect of the pill. The reality was that the pill was so rare that its effects hadn't been verified on a widespread basis.

In order to refine this pill, the two main ingredients were of the utmost importance, and one of them turned out to be none other than those dozen or so strange spirit plants that Han Li had harvested from the bottom of the ravine.

Through the Transient Guild, he learned that the spirit plant was known as the Bitter Ornament Herb, and it only grew in places with high densities of baleful qi. At the very least, tens of thousands of years were required for this spirit plant to arise, and they were extraordinarily expensive.

As for the other main ingredient, that was the Profound Zoysia Crystal.

Out of the four men, three of them had clearly never even heard of this material before, while Immortal Lord Hot Flame was silent for a moment before asking, "Fellow Daoist Li, are you referring to the legendary Floral Heart Stone?"

"That's right, have you seen this material before, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li hurriedly asked.

"This is a spirit material of an exceptionally high caliber that I've never had the pleasure of witnessing for myself, but I've heard that it once appeared in the Jade Kun Pagoda of Jade Gathering City several centuries ago," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied.

"What exactly is this Profound Zoysia Crystal? It sounds so mysterious," Daoist Master Jingyang asked with a curious expression.

"The Profound Zoysia Crystal is a type of premium spirit stone that serves as a primary ingredient required to refine many High Zenith Stage pills. It starts off as a plant, which only produces a flower after tens of thousands of years, and once that flower blooms, a tiny crystal will appear in the heart of the flower. That is the Profound Zoysia Crystal," Immortal Lord Hot Flame explained.

"Unless external forces act upon it, the flower will never wilt, and the crystal will continue to grow. The older the crystal, the more potent the spiritual power and medicinal power that it contains.

“However, if even the slightest of external forces act upon it, the crystal will fall off, and the entire plant will instantly wilt away. As a result, they often grow in extremely secluded places, thereby making them extremely rare and expensive," Han Li added.

"It sounds like these Five Stone Pills of yours are going to be wasted," Daoist Master Jingyang mused with a shake of his head.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, I may not be the most outgoing person, but I do have a few friends in the spirit materials business, and I'll be sure to ask them to keep an eye out," Duan Yuzai said in a serious manner.

"You have my thanks," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"I don't think I'll be of much help here. Old Man Hot Flame can enter Jade Gathering City as he pleases, so he should be able to gather some information for you. Perhaps what you're looking for will reappear in the Jade Kun Pagoda someday," Daoist Master Jingyang said.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, I'll pay Jade Gathering City a visit as soon as I finish this game," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said, then returned his attention to the game at hand.

"I resign," Duan Yuzai declared without any hesitation.

"You... Fine, fine, I'll make a trip to Jade Gathering City right away," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed in a resigned manner, then bade farewell to everyone before flying away toward the south.

Chapter 605: Keeping a Low Profile

Tens of thousands of kilometers to the south of the Floating Cloud Mountain Range stood the largest and most prosperous city in the northern region of the Black Mountain Immortal Region, Jade Gathering City.

In contrast with the cities of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, which were mostly inhabited by mortals, there were hundreds of immortal powers in Jade Gathering City, including both cultivating clans and sects, and the vast majority of the city's residents were also cultivators.

Perhaps this was why the Immortal Palace was particularly stringent in its regulation of the city, which was split up into two sections, the outer city and the inner city. All cultivators could access the outer city as they pleased, but there were many restrictions on those wishing to enter the inner city.

Cultivators below the True Immortal Stage and weren't registered with any of the Black Mountain Immortal Region's local sects were barred from entering the inner city, and that included even local itinerant cultivators.

Only those who were at least at the High Zenith Stage were free to enter the inner city without having to satisfy any other conditions.

It was said that an immortal envoy from the Heavenly Court was constantly stationed in the inner city of Jade Gathering City, and that they possessed unfathomable power.

Back when Han Li first arrived in the Black Mountain Immortal Region, he had actually gone straight to Jade Gathering City as opposed to the Leisure Valley.

As soon as he entered the city, he spotted a plaza, upon which was a hovering platform named the Immortal Slaying List.

The platform hovered over 10,000 feet above the ground, and there were figures from all types of different races depicted upon it, beneath which were lines of text that stated their crimes and the rewards on offer for their capture or demise.

Han Li spotted quite a few familiar figures on the list, including Baili Yan, Daoist Hu Yan, and Wyrm 3.

Wyrm 3 was ranked even higher on the list than Baili Yan, but the name attached to her visage was Gan Jiuzhen, and instead of revealing her true appearance, the image of her only depicted her wearing a crimson mask.

As Han Li's gaze neared the bottom of the list, he spotted himself.

In the image, he was dressed in an azure robe while holding a sword in one hand. His appearance was slightly inaccurate, but it was certainly very vibrant and lifelike.

Beneath his image was a small passage of text that read: "Li Feiyu, cultivated forbidden arts and participated in the killing of an important Heavenly Court official. 5,000 Immortal Origin Stones, dead or alive."

Han Li's brows instantly furrowed tightly upon seeing this, not because he was on the list, but because he was feeling indignant at the measly reward being offered for his capture, which was only 5,000 Immortal Origin Stones compared with 100,000 for Wyrm 3.

Setting aside his killing of Tao Yu, surely the reward on offer for him should've been higher, given the role that he had played in killing Gongshu Jiu, a High Zenith Stage immortal envoy.

With that in mind, Han Li turned his gaze back to the image of Gan Jiuzhen on the list, upon which he discovered that she was being accused of a far more extensive list of crimes, including cultivating forbidden arts, killing immortal officials, and colluding with Gray Immortals.

An enlightened look instantly appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. It seemed that Gan Jiuzhen and Mo Yu were being regarded as the main culprits behind Gongshu Jiu's death, while he was only considered to be an accomplice.

After that, Han Li was planning to leave the city right away, but he quickly discovered that even though there were countless cultivators in Jade Gathering City, barely anyone ever stopped to check the Immortal Slaying List.

Upon closer inspection, he discovered that most of the people on the list were wanted by the Black Mountain Immortal Palace and the Heavenly Court, so they were already very familiar to the majority of the people in Jade Gathering City. Hence, they naturally weren't going to waste any time checking the list unless they had gathered some leads.

Of course, another important factor was that most of the people on the list were formidable figures that were not to be messed with.

Hence, Han Li decided to temporarily stay in Jade Gathering City to find a way to resolve the issue for the baleful qi in his body. However, his efforts proved to be futile, and given the special circumstances surrounding himself and Mo Guang, they encountered many inconveniences in the city, so after encountering Duan Yuzai by chance, he decided to move to the Leisure Valley.

Everyone was quite amused to see Immortal Lord Hot Flame storming away.

"There really was no need to do that, Fellow Daoist Duan. This is not a matter that I expect to have resolved anytime soon, so you could've easily finished your game with Fellow Daoist Hot Flame before sending him on his way," Han Li said with a smile.

"It's fine. The heart is the most important thing in the game of go. I had already lost interest in the game, and I'm sure that was apparent to Fellow Daoist Hot Flame as well. Besides, I have the position memorized, so we could easily continue the game another time," Duan Yuzai replied, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of black light that swept up the go board and the stone holders.

Right at this moment, Daoist Master Jingyang approached Han Li with a smile as he said, "Fellow Daoist Li, you mentioned last time that you were going to brew a few jars of Fire Drop Wine. How has that been going?"

"Fire Drop Wine isn't as difficult to brew as your Green Fermented Wine, so my batch is already done," Han Li replied with a smile.

"My batch of Green Fermented Wine is still a few thousands years away from being ready, so if I were to bring it out now, it would be a terrible waste," Daoist Master Jingyang explained with a slightly embarrassed expression.

"There's no need to explain yourself, I know you're not a stingy person, Fellow Daoist Jingyang," Han Li assured, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a yellow wine jar in front of Daoist Master Jingyang.

Daoist Master Jingyang hurriedly grabbed onto the jar with an ecstatic expression, then opened the clay seal before taking a whiff, upon which a blissful look instantly appeared on his face.

"Exceptional!"

A perplexed look then appeared on his face as he asked, "Why does this wine look like it's been sitting for at least several centuries? It doesn't look like something that only just finished brewing recently."

"We're all friends here, so I naturally have to bring out my best wine. This is a prized jar from my collection, so you're all in luck," Han Li explained with a smile.

Duan Yuzai and Yu Ziqi weren't avid drinkers, but they were more than happy to have a drink as a small circle of friends.

As night fell, Han Li took his leave and returned to his cave abode, which had been dug into a mountain face deep within the bamboo forest, quite far away from the cave abodes of the other four men.

At this moment, the stone gate of the cave abode was tightly shut, and there were two Dao Warriors standing on guard duty on either side of it.

The two Dao Warriors were looking far different from before, with both of them displaying increased statures and drastically elevated auras, and some peculiar corkscrew patterns had also appeared on their bodies.

On top of that, there was a hint of intelligence flashing in their eyes, and both of them extended a collective bow toward Han Li upon his return.

Han Li paid no heed to the pair of Dao Warriors as he made his way into the cave abode, upon which the stone gate swung shut behind him on its own.

The cave abode wasn't very large, consisting of only a main hall and several secret chambers.

He took a glance at two of the secret chambers to the left, which were where Mo Guang and Daoist Xie were cultivating in seclusion.

Even though Mo Guang's baleful qi was being concealed through consumption of Origin Void Pills, that was still not a foolproof solution, and in particular, he had almost been exposed on multiple occasions back in Jade Gathering City.

Hence, upon arriving in the Leisure Valley, Mo Guang had remained in the cave abode the entire time.

As for Daoist Xie, he had also suddenly gone into seclusion for some reason after arriving in the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

Han Li withdrew his gaze as he made his way into the secret chamber where he normally cultivated, then sat down with his legs crossed in silence.

Following his separation with Jin Tong, he had followed the route on the map given to him by the white-robed man, which had allowed him to avoid most of the dangerous areas in the primordial land. Even so, he still encountered several crises that left him on the verge of death.

If it weren't for his current cultivation base and his time law powers, as well as the accompaniment of Mo Guang, he would've most likely already fallen to his demise.

On one occasion, they were pursued by several High Zenith Stage Lightning Beasts for three whole years. Those Lightning Beasts were extraordinarily fast, and they were able to use a teleportation secret technique similar to Han Li's lightning teleportation array.

For some reason, they were intent on hunting Han Li down, and in the end, Han Li was unable to shake them off his trail, so he had no choice but to fight them.

He and Mo Guang joined forces to slay two of the Lightning Beasts, intimidating the remaining Lightning Beasts into retreat, but he had also suffered severe injuries during the battle, injuries that took him several years to fully recover from.

On another occasion, he inadvertently stumbled into a naturally arising secret area that was filled with fire, and in the end, he was only able to escape after over 10 years of toil with the help of the Essence Fire Raven.

While it was true that this had been an extremely perilous journey, he had also reaped many rewards.

Setting aside all of the precious primordial materials that he had gathered, he had also snuck into the settlements of some primordial tribes along the way and learned many of their secret techniques and cultivation arts.

The two Dao Warriors at the entrance of his cave abode had been refined using one of those secret techniques.

Under normal circumstances, he would've been ecstatic to have reaped so many rewards, but at the moment, the threat of the baleful decay was constantly looming over his head, so he was constantly under a great deal of pressure.

After sitting in silence for a moment, he suddenly made a hand seal, and a series of bright golden halos emerged in front of him, then converged toward a single spot to conjure up his Clear Time Vial.

The vial was significantly larger than before, and it appeared almost substantial in form. There were hundreds of Time Dao Runes flashing on its surface, and a series of long streaks of golden light were wrapped around the vial, giving off formidable time law power fluctuations.

Over the past years, he had attempted to incorporate the experience that he had accrued while cultivating the Mantra Treasured Axis, using the time crystals produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial to increase the number of Time Dao Runes on the Clear Time Vial, and it had worked without a hitch.

Han Li inspected the Clear Time Vial momentarily, then set it down beside him before making another hand seal, upon which bursts of golden light surged out of his body.

He began to chant an incantation while continuing to make hand seals, and the streaks of golden light transformed into grains of golden sand that hovered in the surrounding air while giving off faint golden light and time law power fluctuations.

More and more of these grains of golden sand were emerging, and in the span of just a few seconds, they had formed a golden sand pit that was over 100 feet in size, filling up virtually the entire secret chamber.

Chapter 606: Fusing Time Law Powers

A special type of law power was flowing through the golden sand pit, while the golden light in the air was flashing incessantly while fluctuating in brightness, presenting a rather disorientating sight to behold.

What was most remarkable was that in the space encompassed within the sand pit, the flow of air and the world's origin qi was clearly far faster than it was in the area outside.

Due to the presence of baleful qi in his immortal acupoints, Han Li was unable to make any progress in his cultivation beyond the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage. Hence, he had spent the majority of time cultivating the Water Divination Time Arts and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture.

Perhaps he really did possess exceptional aptitude in the cultivation of the laws of time, but he was able to make rapid progress in both cultivation arts, having already reached the sixth chapter of the Water Divination Time Arts, and he had also reached a very high level in the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture, allowing him to unleash the Illusory Dawn Sand Sea ability.

As he flicked a finger through the air, the golden light emanating from the Clear Time Vial abruptly brightened, and the streaks of golden light around it began to circulate far faster than before, resonating with the Illusory Dawn Sand Sea down below.

Han Li made another hand seal to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis, and at this point, the number of Time Dao Runes on its surface had increased significantly.

By consistently producing more time crystals with the Heavenly Controlling Vial, Han Li had been able to reach the current upper limit of 720 Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis.

A vast expanse of golden radiance erupted out of the Mantra Treasured Axis to fill the entire secret chamber.

The three bursts of golden light from the Mantra Treasured Axis, the Clear Time Vial, and the Illusory Dawn Sand Sea all seemed to be resonating with one another, causing the surrounding space to tremble and buzz faintly.

Han Li wasn't all that surprised to see this.

Back when he first obtained the Water Divination Time Arts and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture, he had already noticed that they seemed to be somehow connected to the Mantra Axis Scripture, and his suspicions had only been confirmed through his pursuit of the three cultivation arts.

The three cultivation arts were so closely intertwined with each other that it almost felt as if they had come from a single cultivation art, but Han Li was unable to conclude whether this was truly the case as he still hadn't reached full mastery of all three cultivation arts.

Right at this moment, Han Li closed his eyes and began to chant an incantation, upon which the three bursts of golden light began to flash in unison before gradually coming together as one at his behest.

The three bursts of different time law powers were also intertwining with one another, seemingly attempting to fuse with each other, but there was some resistance that existed between them, preventing their fusion.

Through his cultivation, Han Li had gained a deeper understanding of the three cultivation arts and the power of time laws.

As one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time was one of the most central and fundamental laws of heaven and earth. On a small scale, it directly impacted the life cycle of a living being or the decay of an object, while on a grand scale, it could be said that time was the driving force that was pushing the entire True Immortal Realm along.

It was as if there were a pair of invisible hands that raised up the laws of time so that it transcended above all other laws, and the reason why it was renowned as one of the paramount laws was because it was unaffected by the vast majority of other laws, but could also affect or alter some laws.

For example, the most commonly seen laws of water and fire had their powers significantly diminished under the influence of the laws of time.

Through the use of the Mantra Treasured Axis, the Mantra Axis Scripture allowed one to control the speed of the passage of time in a certain area, which was already an extraordinary ability, but that was only one of the uses of the power of time laws.

In other words, the laws of time were extremely vast and profound, and the Mantra Axis Scripture alone certainly wasn't enough to encompass it in its entirety.

As for the Water Divination Time Arts and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture, they were merely also alternative interpretations and uses of the power of time laws.

It was a very rare feat for anyone to be able to expertly control and use any particular law power. For the average True Immortal, even if they could sense the power of laws, there was no way for them to control these powers due to their limited immortal spiritual power, whereas Golden Immortals satisfied the minimum immortal spiritual power requirement to begin delving into the realm of law powers.

The best way to improve one's mastery over a type of law power was to develop a better understanding of said law power.

This was why Han Li had decided to use all three of these cultivation arts at once in order to come into contact with different types of time law powers, thereby furthering his understanding.

As he continued to cycle through a string of hand seals, the three bursts of golden light in the secret chamber gradually came together to form a swirling golden vortex.

All three bursts of time law powers had been incorporated into the vortex, but they were still separate entities that showed no signs of fusion.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he began to cycle through his hands seals even faster.

As a result, the golden vortex began to revolve faster while gradually shrinking in size.

The three bursts of time law powers were clashing together forcefully, and countless golden runes surged out of the center of the vortex, giving off violent time law power fluctuations.

However, the three bursts of time law powers still showed no signs of fusing together. Instead, it felt as if they were on the brink of exploding.

Han Li hurriedly stopped what he was doing upon seeing this, and the golden vortex instantly stopped shrinking, while the violent time law power fluctuations also subsided.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he shook his head with a resigned expression.

Over the years, he had tried many different methods to fuse the three different time law powers, but all of his attempts had concluded in futility.

Was there simply no way to fuse these three time law powers, or was there something that he was missing?

All of a sudden, a fierce look appeared in Han Li's eyes, and he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a flurry of over 1,000 azure array flags, all of which vanished into different parts of the secret chamber.

Azure light flashed erratically within the secret chamber to form a thick light barrier, upon which countless profound runes were flashing incessantly, giving the light barrier an indestructible appearance.

At the same time, he drew upon his Xuanwu bloodline, and pieces of massive azure turtle shells appeared over his body, coming together to form a suit of dark green armor that encapsulated his entire body.

After that, Han Li still wasn't content, and he opened his mouth to release several defensive immortal treasures, which transformed into protective barriers of different colors around him.

With all of the preparations complete, he resumed what he had been doing before, and the golden vortex began to shrink once again as the three time law powers clashed fiercely to produce an explosive aura.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and instead of stopping, he pressed on even more aggressively.

The golden vortex was revolving rapidly, and the golden light at its center had become unbearably bright, while countless golden runes were surging violently within it.

In the next instant, a terrifying aura erupted out of the center of the vortex, and it felt as if it could explode at any moment.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he redoubled his efforts, and the golden vortex shuddered violently before shrinking even further.

As a result, the ball of golden runes at the center of the vortex was compressed even more aggressively, and it was truly on the verge of explosion now.

However, right at this moment, the three time law powers seemed to have been compressed beyond a certain threshold, and they suddenly became mellow and docile, succumbing to Han Li's will and fusing together.

The violently churning golden runes collapsed inward, then rapidly shrank down to form a shimmering ring of golden light, which sucked in the surrounding golden vortex.

All of the golden light within the entire secret chamber quickly faded, and all that remained was a tiny golden ring that was glowing radiantly while hovering in mid-air.

This was a completely unexpected turn of events for Han Li, and was looking on with a combination of elation and astonishment in his eyes.

However, the golden ring wasn't very stable, and it quickly began to tremble violently while a series of cracks appeared over its surface, looking as if it could shatter any moment.

An incredibly tremendous burst of time law power fluctuations swept out of the golden ring, rapidly whittling down the azure light barrier within the secret chamber on contact.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

While he did have other restrictions set up in the cave abode, they most likely wouldn't be able to contain this burst of time law power fluctuations, either.

Right as he was to do something, a ball of green light suddenly flew out of his robes, and it was none other than his Heaven Controlling Vial.

The vial hovered in mid-air with its opening facing the golden ring, and it was glowing as radiantly as a green sun.

A burst of immense suction force surged out of the vial, sucking in the golden ring in a flash.

With the golden ring gone, the burst of terrifying time law power fluctuations also faded, and the azure light barrier in the secret chamber was able to remain intact.

Meanwhile, the Heaven Controlling Vial rapidly expanded as countless green runes emerged within it, then came together to form a churning green cloud.

A burst of formidable law power fluctuations surged out of the green cloud, causing the nearby space to ripple incessantly.

Right at this moment, a vertical golden eye abruptly sprang open at the center of the Mantra Treasured Axis, and a translucent golden thread shot out from within before vanishing into the Heaven Controlling Vial in a flash.

The green cloud within the vial instantly brightened before erupting forth as a thick pillar of green light.

The space in the path of the pillar of green light parted as countless rays of translucent light surged out of the resulting spatial rift, forming a translucent wall of light with a series of images rapidly flashing over its surface.

A hint of disappointment appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. He had thought that something different would be triggered out of the Heaven Controlling Vial, but that didn't seem to be the case.

Right at this moment, two beady little black eyes suddenly appeared on the surface of the Heaven Controlling Vial before turning to Han Li.

At the same time, a faint voice rang out in his mind.

"It's about time..."

Chapter 607: Mysterious River

Han Li's expression instantly changed slightly upon hearing this voice, but before he had a chance to do anything, an enormous vortex suddenly appeared on the translucent wall of light.

A burst of tremendous suction force erupted out of the vortex to envelop Han Li's entire body, and this burst of suction force was several times more formidable than on the previous occasions where Han Li had been sucked into the wall of light.

However, in the next instant, the burst of suction force suddenly faded, and Han Li felt a sharp pain in his mind, following which he completely lost consciousness.

Some time later, Han Li returned to his senses in a rather disoriented fashion, and he looked around to discover that he was situated in a murky gray space, while down below was a barren dark red plain that stretched as far as the eyes could see.

The plain was completely devoid of vegetation, and above it was a glittering silver river that was flowing through the sky amid a burst of dull rumbling.

Upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered that as opposed to water, what was flowing through the river were actually water-droplet-like balls of light.

Han Li was very surprised to see this, but he didn't immediately move.

This instance of spiritual transmigration seemed to be different from the previous few occasions.

There was a mysterious aura permeating throughout the entire surrounding environment, and he couldn't help but think of the eyes that had appeared on the Heaven Controlling Vial and the faint voice that he had heard in his mind.

Those eyes weren't unfamiliar to him as they belonged to the vial spirit of the Heaven Controlling Vial.

As for the voice that he had heard, that had most likely come from the vial spirit.

Han Li couldn't see the vial spirit anywhere nearby, nor could he make sense of what it had said, so he set the thought aside for now and began to examine his surroundings.

All of a sudden, he noticed that unlike his previous spiritual transmigrations, he didn't seem to have possessed anyone. Instead, his bare soul was hovering mid-air.

It appeared that all of this had been triggered by the golden ring formed by the three bursts of integrated time law powers, and it seemed to have reacted somehow with the Heaven Controlling Vial.

With that in mind, Han Li swept his gaze over his surroundings once again, but didn't find anything of note over the boundless barren plain around him.

After withdrawing his gaze, he began to approach the river in the sky, and from up close, he was able to see that the river was flowing from somewhere too far away for Han Li's eyes to reach, and there was no end to it in sight, either.

There were countless balls of light of different sizes flowing through the river, with some as large as millstones, while others were as tiny as grains of rice.

Each of the balls of light contained a shimmering image, but they were flowing by too quickly for Han Li to be able to catch a clear glimpse of any of the images.

The entire river was giving off an indescribable aura of mystique, and after staring at it in a transfixed fashion for some time, Han Li began carefully approaching the river again before peering into one of the larger water droplets that was passing by.

This water droplet depicted an image of a yellow desert that was rapidly changing.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li released his spiritual sense onto the water droplet in an attempt to catch a clear glimpse of the image on it, but right as he did this, the water droplet immediately began to glow brightly before releasing a burst of tremendous suction force.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li's soul was sucked into the water droplet without being able to put up any resistance.

His vision instantly faded, and only after an indeterminate period of time did he slowly return to his senses, upon which a slightly ragged voice tinged with a hint of lingering fear rang out from nearby.

"What a terrifying opponent that was... Even with the five of us joining forces, three of us were still killed."

Another high-pitched voice rang out in response, and it was also sounding a little out of breath.

"That man had already reached the pinnacle of the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, so he was bound to be an extremely formidable opponent. Those three were far too eager to claim the reward on his head, and they rushed in without any preparation like idiots! Having said that, it's a good thing that those three did rush in and weaken him. Otherwise, we wouldn't have been able to take him down."

"In any case, we suffered extremely heavy losses here. Will we be in trouble with our higher-ups?" the first voice asked in a concerned manner.

"It'll be fine. Us immortal envoys are always tasked with perilous missions, so some casualties here and there are inevitable. All we have to do is bring this man's head back to our higher-ups, and we'll surely be handsomely rewarded," the high-pitched voice replied in a gleeful fashion.

Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this conversation, and he hurriedly restrained his own spiritual fluctuations, then began to inspect his surroundings in secret.

Just like during the previous few spiritual transmigrations, he had possessed a corpse.

The body belonged to a black-robed middle-aged man with a head of disheveled long hair and a long and thin face. Even though he was already dead, there was still a fierce look about his sharp facial features.

At this moment, he was laying on a yellow desert, and countless huge craters had been blasted into the ground all around him.

Plumes of dense smoke were billowing out of some of these craters, releasing an acrid sulfurous odor.

It was clear that an intense battle had just taken place here not long ago.

There were two men clad in suits of golden armor nearby, and the symbols on those suits of golden armor were precisely the insignia of the Heavenly Court.

One of the armor-clad figures was a tall elderly man with a tall nose and a pair of thin eyebrows, while the other one was a bald young man with a round face and a rotund frame.

At this moment, both of them were looking rather pale, and the bald young man was looking particularly worse for wear, with blood trickling down from the corner of his lips and signs of damage on his suit of golden armor.

Strewn over the ground further away were there more bodies clad in suits of golden armor.

Han Li only briefly inspected his surroundings before immediately withdrawing his spiritual sense and directing it deeper into the mind of the body that he had possessed.

Through that brief inspection of his surroundings, Han Li had determined that the two armor-clad men were both at the High Zenith Stage, and their cultivation bases were far superior to that of Gongshu Jiu, indicating that they were at least at the mid-High Zenith Stage, perhaps even the late-High Zenith Stage.

Through their conversation, Han Li had learned that they were both immortal envoys of the Heavenly Court, and if they were to discover that another soul had appeared in this body, then they would be sure to kill it right away.

His soul had been transmigrated to this place by the Heaven Controlling Vial, so he wasn't sure what the consequences of being killed here would be, but he wasn't keen on finding out.

Right as Han Li's soul began to burrow deeper into the black-robed man's mind, a tremendous burst of heat suddenly surged forth before fusing into Han Li's soul.

The burst of heat was a burst of enormous and extremely pure spiritual sense, and it quickly began to inflate Han Li's soul like a balloon.

The burst of immense spiritual sense carried with it a series of memory fragments belonging to the black-robed man, and they also flooded into Han Li's mind.

Perhaps Han Li's soul had already grown accustomed to all of this from the previous few instances of transmigration, but he was able to easily receive the black-robed man's memories without much pain or other adverse effects.

Han Li's soul was able to easily harness these fragmented memories, but the burst of spiritual sense was too immense, and only a small portion of it had surged into Han Li's soul before full saturation was reached.

The remaining spiritual sense swirled around Han Li's soul, forming a glittering and translucent white cloud that was rapidly revolving along an extremely profound trajectory.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this. This burst of spiritual sense was far more powerful than his own, and this method of channeling spiritual sense was the exact method stipulated in the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Han Li had been arduously cultivating the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique over the years, but it had been far more difficult to grasp than he had anticipated, and even after toiling away for several centuries, not much progress had been made.

As he felt this burst of spiritual sense swirling around him, he found solutions to many of the problems that had previously stumped him in his cultivation, and he was struck by a sense of enlightenment.

However, given the current situation, he couldn't afford to immerse himself in all of this.

His eyes abruptly sprang open as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a black flying sword shot out of the palm of his hand.

As soon as the flying sword was released, it instantly vanished into thin air, immediately following which countless black sword projections emerged, forming a massive sword mountain that swept toward the pair of armor-clad men.

There was no way that the two men would've failed to notice the eruption of spiritual sense from the black-robed man's mind, and sure enough, both of them turned to the body on the ground with astonished expressions before hurriedly darting back in retreat.

However, in their panic, both of them had failed to notice that a streak of translucent light had shot out of Han Li's glabella before vanishing into thin air.

"How are you still not dead?!" the tall elderly man exclaimed in an incredulous voice as he made a grabbing motion with one hand, and countless blue ripples instantly surged out of the pal of his hand, forming a massive blue wyrm projection that swooped down toward the black sword mountain.

The giant blue wyrm wrapped its body around the black sword mountain, then released a burst of formidable glacial power that instantly froze the entire surrounding space.

The black sword mountain was also frozen solid and drew to an abrupt halt as a thick layer of blue ice crystals appeared over its surface.

As for the portly young man, there was a fearful look in his eyes, but he also sprang into action, sweeping a sleeve through the air to release a pair of crimson curved daggers, each of which was around three feet in length.

Bursts of crimson flames were burning over the curved daggers, forming a series of fiery crimson flowers that were giving off a terrifying scorching aura.

The two curved daggers circled around in the air before hurtling directly toward Han Li as two streaks of crimson light.

Right at this moment, Han Li thrust his hands into the ground, launching himself upward like a weightless sheet of paper, allowing him to just barely evade the two streaks of crimson light.

At the same time, a faint smile appeared on his face as he abruptly made a hand seal, and several translucent chains shot out of thin air behind the tall elderly man before vanishing into his head in a flash.

A horrified look appeared on the elderly man's face, yet before he had a chance to do anything, his eyes completely glazed over, while his body also became suspended in mid-air in a completely still manner.

The sneak attack from Han Li had come far too abruptly and unexpectedly, and the elderly man was barely able to display any of his power before his soul was trapped within a Spiritual Sense Cage.

Chapter 608: Fragments

"Senior Martial Brother Gao!" the portly young man called out in an alarmed voice, and the fear in his eyes became even more pronounced.

A cold smile appeared on Han Li's face as he flew directly toward the young man with translucent light flashing from his glabella.

The portly young man immediately flew away as a streak of crimson light in a blind panic, and he was in such a hurry to escape that he had even abandoned his pair of curved dagger immortal treasures.

The streak of crimson light vanished into the distance in the blink of an eye, and Han Li immediately stopped in his tracks upon seeing this, choosing not to give chase.

All of a sudden, his complexion became extremely pale, and he was panting heavily as he drifted back down onto the ground.

There wasn't much immortal spiritual power left in this body to begin with, and it had been virtually completely exhausted while Han Li was unleashing his Spirit Sense Cage on the elderly man, so if the portly young man had fought back, then he would've been completely powerless to resist.

Thankfully, the young man had a very cowardly personality, and he immediately fled the scene at the slightest show of intimidation.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce an Immortal Origin Stone that he held in his hand to recover his immortal spiritual power, and at the same time, he pointed a finger forward, mustering up what little remained of his immortal spiritual power to shoot a beam of black light out of his fingertip, which pierced through the tall elderly man's head.

The elderly man's head instantly exploded, and his headless body toppled to the ground.

After doing all of that, Han Li also slumped to the ground, feeling completely spent.

Now that the immediate threat had been dealt with, he was finally able to take a look at his surroundings, and he discovered that this yellow desert was rather similar to the setting that he had seen in that water droplet.

After sitting in silence for a short while, Han Li looked up to discover a Mantra Treasured Axis projection hovering above his head, and at this point, only a small portion of its 720 Time Dao Runes had faded.

He closed his eyes as he carefully sensed the circulation of the enormous spiritual sense in his mind, experiencing the feeling of the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique while also examining the memories of the body that he had possessed.

As it turned out, the black-robed man's name was Lu Renjia, and he was a Reincarnation Disciple of the Reincarnation Palace.

In contrast with Han Li, he was a true Reincarnation Disciple, granting him access to a vast array of the Reincarnation Palace's cultivation resources. However, in return, he had to periodically complete missions released by the Reincarnation Palace.

It was during one such mission that Lu Renjia had come to this place, which was called the Open Origin Immortal Region, and he was ambushed by five immortal envoys of the Heavenly Court, thereby leading to his demise.

Han Li really wanted to know more about the Reincarnation Palace, so he closely examined Lu Renjia's memory fragments, and a long while later, he raised his head with slightly furrowed brows.

Most of Lu Renjia's memory fragments contained cultivation information that was useless to him, and Han Li was only able to find very little information about the Reincarnation Palace.

Lu Renjia had already been a Reincarnation Disciple for over two million years, but he was a cultivation fanatic who was constantly cultivating in seclusion in his cave abode, very rarely coming out to go anywhere.

Even though he was a Reincarnation Disciple, he had no intention of becoming excessively involved with the Reincarnation Palace. He had carried out many Reincarnation Palace missions, but never had he met any of the Reincarnation Palace's leading figures. The person that he came into contact with the most was a reincarnation envoy, who served as the contact between him and the Reincarnation Palace.

Aside from that, there was no other information pertaining to the Reincarnation Palace.

Han Li shook his head before raising his head to look up at the Mantra Treasured Axis projection once again, and at this point, over a quarter of the Time Dao Runes on its surface had already faded.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li rose to his feet, then made his way over to the body of the tall elderly man before tracking down his storage tool.

He then strode over to the other three bodies and collected their storage tools as well.

After that, he sat down and placed the four storage tools on the ground in front of himself along with Lu Renjia's storage ring, then began to examine their contents one by one.

All five of these deceased cultivators had been at the High Zenith Stage, so they were extremely wealthy, and their storage tools contained enormous numbers of Immortal Origin Stones, as well as many immortal treasures, materials, and pills of an extremely high caliber.

Unfortunately, there was no way that Han Li could take these things with him, so he began focusing on things that could be of use to him.

Moments later, a small pile of items appeared on the ground in front of him, consisting mostly of some scriptures and jade slips, as well as a golden disk, a golden badge, and a white plate.

Han Li picked up the golden disk and the white plate for a brief examination, then set them down before picking up the golden badge.

He had seen both of these items in Gongshu Jiu's storage tool before. The golden disk was the item that was used for communication between immortal envoys, while the white plate was what they used to detect the aura of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

As for the golden badge, that appeared to be an identity badge, and each one of the four armor-clad figures had one in their possession.

There was a beautiful dragon engraved onto the edge of the badge, and on one side was engraved the character for "Prison", while the other side carried a number.

Han Li briefly inspected the badge for a moment, then quickly set it aside before turning his attention to the scriptures and jade slips, most of which contained cultivation arts and secret techniques.

These were naturally all very remarkable cultivation arts, given that they were part of collections of High Zenith cultivators, and they were certainly very eye-opening for Han Li.

Even though he still had time, he didn't want to spend too much of it here, so he quickly flipped through the scriptures one after another, making no attempt to memorize their contents.

All of a sudden, he spotted a gray jade slip, which contained a pill recipe as opposed to any cultivation art or secret technique.

The recipe was for a pill by the name of the Vajra Iron Bone Pill, and it contained the laws of metal, able to enhance the consumer's physical constitution while also aiding in the mastery of the laws of metal.

Han Li took a glance at the Mantra Treasured Axis projection above his head to find that only less than half of its Time Dao Runes remained lit.

He then withdrew his gaze before taking some time to memorize the pill recipe, following which he tossed the jade slip aside before continuing to check through the other items.

It didn't take long before he had examined all of the scriptures and jade slips, and he swept a sleeve through the air to stow them away, then picked up the five storage tools before flying away into the distance.

Shortly thereafter, he descended onto an oasis in the desert, at the center of which was a small lake.

He swept a sleeve through the air once again to release a burst of black light that enveloped the storage tools, carrying them to the lakebed before burying them.

After that, he sat down beside the oasis with his legs crossed and continued the experience the intricacies of the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

He hadn't closely examined the contents of the storage tools as he wanted to dedicate as much time to experiencing the Spirit Refinement Technique as possible.

As time slowly passed by, the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis projection faded one after another, and as the final Time Dao Rune turned dark, the axis projection suddenly turned a black color, then transformed into a vortex.

A burst of tremendous suction force surged out of the vortex, and Han Li's soul was sucked into it without being able to pose any resistance.

Once again, his consciousness faded, and some time later, he slowly opened his eyes, upon which he discovered that he had returned to his cave abode.

The Heaven Controlling Vial was still hovering in mid-air, but the green light that it was giving off was rapidly fading, and in the end, it returned to its original size before falling down from above.

Han Li reached out to catch the vial, then briefly examined it before injecting his spiritual sense into it, trying to contact the vial spirit that he had caught a brief glimpse of.

However, despite his best efforts, he was unable to garner any response from the vial spirit, and it was as if it had fallen into a slumber once again.

Han Li could only heave a resigned sigh before stowing the Heaven Controlling Vial away.

After that, he flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip, then transferred the Vajra Iron Bone Pill recipe that he had memorized onto it so that he wouldn't forget it.

After stowing the jade slip away, Han Li took a deep breath before closing his eyes once again.

During this instance of spiritual transmigration, he had been transported into that mysterious space and witnessed that mysterious river, which had left him with many questions.

It seemed that the scenes flowing through the river depicted the history of certain people.

It appeared that all of these people had already died or were on the brink of death, and by possessing their bodies, Han Li was able to examine some of their memories and learn some things.

As for whether he could choose which target he could possess, that was something that he would have to examine next time.

The problem was that with each spiritual transmigration, all of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis would be snuffed out, and even though they were currently able to recover far faster than before, it would still take quite a bit of time for a full recovery.

The main reward that he had reaped from this instance of spiritual transmigration were the cultivation insights pertaining to the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique that he had gleaned from Lu Renjia.

With these newly gained insights, he was confident that he would be able to make far faster progress in his cultivation of the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Right as he was about to begin cultivating, he suddenly opened his eyes before casting his gaze outside.

A ball of white light light had flown in from outside the cave abode, and it circled around in Han Li's secret chamber momentarily before suddenly shattering.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he rose to his feet before deactivating the surrounding restrictions, then made his way out of his secret chamber.

The gate of the cave abode was opened to reveal a gray-robed elderly man standing outside. The man had a goatee on his chin, and he had a rather snide and sneaky appearance.

Han Li faltered slightly at the sight of the elderly man, then smiled as he said, "Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Lu."

The elderly man was Lu Guanzi, who lived in the nearby Sunny Valley, and he got along very well with Daoist Master Jingyang and Immortal Lord Hot Flame, regularly paying them visits, so over time, Han Li had also become well acquainted with him.

"Please pardon my intrusion, Fellow Daoist Li," Lu Guanzi said with a smile.

"Come in! What brings you here today?" Han Li asked as he made an inviting hand gesture.

"It's alright, let's just talk here," Lu Guanzi refused with a faint smile.

Chapter 609: Return to Jade Gathering City

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then smiled as he prompted, "Please go ahead, Fellow Daoist Lu."

"Recently, several fellow daoists and I discovered a set of ruins deep in the Heavenly Peak Mountain Range in the north. However, there are quite a few powerful restrictions and some other hazards present in the ruins, so we all decided to come back and recruit some more people to explore the ruins together.

“You're one of the most powerful cultivators in the few nearby valleys, so I thought I'd come and ask if you were interested in coming with us to try your luck," Lu Guanzi said with a smile.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he didn't immediately offer a response.

The smile on Lu Guanzi's face faded slightly at the sight of Han Li's reaction, but he didn't try to hurry Han Li into making a decision.

"Thank you for the invitation, Fellow Daoist Lu, but I'm busy with some other things at the moment, so I'm afraid I won't be able to explore the ruins with you," Han Li replied after a brief silence.

Lu Guanzi could see that Han Li had already made up his mind, and a slightly disappointed look appeared on his face as he cupped his fist in a parting salute. "In that case, I'll leave you to do what you need to do."

After escorting Lu Guanzi out of the cave abode, Han Li closed the gate and returned to his secret chamber before sitting down with his legs crossed.

He hadn't turned down Lu Guanzi solely because he was busy cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique. Instead, there were some other factors at play as well.

With that in mind, he made a hand seal, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light, with all 720 of its Time Dao Runes completely dull and devoid of luster.

With his Mantra Treasured Axis in its current state, Han Li's powers were significantly hampered, making it very unwise to venture into a set of potentially dangerous ruins.

After withdrawing the Mantra Treasured Axis back into his body, Han Li closed his eyes, and a layer of faintly rippling translucent light surfaced over his glabella.

The stone gate of his cave abode remained shut, and none of the residents of the Leisure Valley came to disturb him.

Over 30 years flew by in the blink of an eye, and on this day, a streak of light arrived from afar before descending in front of Han Li's cave abode.

A disheveled elderly man emerged from the streak of light, and it was none other than Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

Before he even had a chance to announce his arrival, the gate of the cave abode swung open, and Han Li emerged from within with a smile on his face.

"My apologies for not coming out to greet you sooner, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame."

"There's no need to be so formal with me. Besides, I only just returned, so how could you have known to come out sooner than you did?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a smile of his own.

"Please come in," Han Li said as he made an inviting hand gesture.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame waved a hand in response. "It's alright, I won't come in. I came here today to deliver something to you. You've constantly been in seclusion of late, so I could only wait until today."

An elated look immediately appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he exclaimed, "Could it be that you've found a Profound Zoysia Crystal?"

"I'm afraid not, Fellow Daoist Li. A material of such exceptional rarity is not that easy to find," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a wry smile.

"Oh? What else could it be then?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

A burst of white light flashed over the palm of Immortal Lord Hot Flame's hand, and he tossed an object at Han Li.

Upon catching the object, Han Li discovered that it was a palm-sized white jade badge, upon which was engraved a red leaf design, to the left of which was inscribed the words "outer sect elder badge" in ancient text.

This was an outer sect elder badge from the Fire Leaf Sect, which was the sect that Immortal Lord Hot Flame belonged to.

Han Li flipped the badge over to find that the words "Li Han" were engraved onto the other side.

"What is the meaning of this, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li asked.

"With this badge, you'll officially be a registered cultivator at our Fire Leaf Sect, so you'll be able to visit the inner city of Jade Gathering City as you please. Having said that, this badge is only a symbolic token, and you won't be receiving any elder benefits from our sect. Ours is only a small sect, and we can't afford any Golden Immortal Stage outer sect elders," Immortal Lord Hot Flame chuckled.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame. Rest assured, if I'm going to serve as an outer sect elder of the Fire Leaf Sect, then I'll be sure to do my part. From now, I can guarantee the provision of a batch of True Immortal Stage pills every 300 years. Of course, your sect will have to provide the ingredients," Han Li said.

"There's no need for that, Fellow Daoist Li. All of us have come to this place to unburden ourselves from responsibilities. I'm not giving this badge to you because I want something in return, so there's really no need for you to promise me anything," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a serious expression.

"Rest assured, refining a batch of True Immortal Stage pills every 300 years is not much of a hassle for me at all. I presume it wasn't easy for you to secure this elder badge for me, so it's the least that I can do," Han Li said.

Even though Immortal Lord Hot Flame wasn't explicitly asking for anything in return, Han Li naturally couldn't just take the badge free of charge. Furthermore, it was clear from the barely concealed delight in Immortal Lord Hot Flame's eyes that this was the exact outcome that he had been hoping for.

In the short term, a batch of True Immortal Stage pills every 300 years wasn't going to have much of an impact, but how would it look after tens of thousands of years? It wouldn't exactly be enough to elevate the Fire Leaf Sect to a whole new level, but it would certainly allow the sect to put some distance between itself and its closest competitors.

Even though Immortal Lord Hot Flame had come to reside in the Leisure Valley to escape from his worldly responsibilities, it was clear that the Fire Leaf Sect still held an important place in his heart.

All official personnel changes in large and medium-sized sects within the territory of Jade Gathering City had to undergo a screening and registration process with the Black Mountain Immortal Palace.

Outer sect disciples weren't considered to be official sect members, but all inner sect disciples, outer sect elders, core disciples, and inner sect elders fell into that category, and the higher one's rank in the sect, the more rigorous the screening process would be.

"I have some acquaintances in the Black Mountain Immortal Palace, so the registration process shouldn't be a problem," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame," Han Li said as he extended another grateful salute.

"If you insist on being so formal with me, then I'm going to take back the badge," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said in a stern manner.

Han Li chuckled in response as he stowed the badge away, and the two of them chatted for a while longer before Immortal Lord Hot Flame departed, while Han Li returned to his cave abode.

......

Two months later.

Jade Gathering City was riddled with countless streets and alleys, and there were shops and merchant carriages stretching as far as the eyes could see, interspersed throughout which were throngs of people, presenting an extremely lively and bustling sight to behold.

Numerous enormous merchant ships could also be seen in the sky, flying along set trajectories before descending onto the docks in the city in an orderly fashion, transporting all types of different wares.

The outer and inner cities were separated by a giant city wall that was over a thousand feet tall, which was patrolled by cultivators, and there was a huge city gate in each direction, north, south, east, and west, all of which were overseen by True Immortals.

The people streaming through the northern gate of the inner city was relatively sparse compared with the other three gates, and there were only fewer than two hundred people gathered there in a line, waiting to be examined before being granted permissions to enter the inner city.

Near the back of the line was none other than the azure-robed Han Li, who was currently inspecting the city gate up ahead.

Numerous array patterns had been engraved into the city wall around the gate, and they would glow with azure light whenever someone made their way through the gate.

It seemed that this was a measure in place to examine the cultivation bases of those wishing to enter the city. Whenever the array patterns lit up, that meant that the person being examined was at least at the early-True Immortal Stage, and as long as they were verified to be registered with a local sect, then they were granted free passage into the inner city.

Han Li was slowly advancing forward in the line when someone suddenly flew directly past him, flying directly toward the city gate without any regard for the line or displaying any items of identification.

Right as everyone was wondering what this person was doing, the array patterns engraved into the city wall suddenly began to glow with dazzling golden light, indicating that the new arrival was a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal.

Even though Jade Gathering City was the number one city in the northern part of the Black Mountain Immortal Region, High Zenith cultivators were still a very rare sight here, so everyone was looking on in awe and wonder.

Before anyone had a chance to catch a clear glimpse of the Jade Immortal, they had already drifted into the inner city and vanished out of sight.

After a brief disturbance, the line settled down again before continuing to advance toward the city gate.

A few minutes later, Han Li arrived at the city gate, and the array patterns around the gate began to glow white, reflecting his Golden Immortal Stage cultivation base.

At the request of the cultivators stationed at the city gate, Han Li offered up his Fire Leaf Sect elder badge, and one of them accepted the badge before placing it onto a nearby stone platform.

The miniature array on the stone platform immediately lit up to examine the badge, and moments later, the badge was returned to Han Li by a middle-aged cultivator, who said in a respectful manner, "You're free to enter the inner city, Senior."

Han Li recovered his badge before making his way through the city gate, and as soon as he set foot into the inner city, he instantly felt as if his surroundings had become a little brighter, while the spiritual qi in the surrounding air had also become more abundant.

Han Li examined his surroundings briefly to discover that there were countless strange runes engraved onto the ground and the walls of the nearby buildings, and he couldn't help but remark to himself, "This entire inner city has been constructed like an immortal sect! No wonder the people on Relaxation Mountain always speak of the inner city of Jade Gathering City with such reverence."

As he made his way deeper into the inner city, he discovered that it was far more peaceful here than in the outer city.

There weren't many pedestrians on the streets, and most of them were traversing from one shop to another.

Han Li picked out a shop that was situated in a large three-story pavilion before making his way inside, but it didn't take long before he was escorted back out of the shop by an apologetic-looking shopkeeper.

According to the shopkeeper, only three shops in Jade Gathering City had any chance of having a Profound Zoysia Crystal in their catalog, and even if they did, they were very unlikely to be willing to sell such a precious material.

Han Li had already anticipated this, so he wasn't overly disappointed, but he still decided to try his luck in the city.

Chapter 610: Golden Jade Silk Square

Over the course of the day, Han Li visited dozens of shops, but the outcome was the same every single time. In fact, many of the shopkeepers had told him that while a Profound Zoysia Crystal had indeed once appeared in Jade Gathering City, the chances of it reappearing in the city were slim to none.

However, Han Li remained unfazed as he continued to go from one shop to the next.

At this point, it was getting quite close to night time, and Han Li had arrived at the Jade Kun Pagoda that Immortal Lord Hot Flame had spoken of.

In contrast with Han Li's expectations, the Jade Kun Pagoda wasn't some particularly grand and majestic building. Instead, it was an octagonal pagoda with red walls and green roof tiles, looking much like a building one would find in the mortal world.

At this moment, the pagoda's southern entrance was closed, and there was a sealing talisman that bore the insignia of the Black Mountain Immortal Palace plastered to it.

After asking around, Han Li learned that the Jade Kun Pagoda was not just some ordinary shop. Instead, it was an auction venue that only opened during the city founding celebration, which took place once every three thousand years, and there were still two hundred to three hundred years until the next celebration.

Hence, Han Li made his way to a rather secluded immortal inn in Jade Gathering City, then rented a cave abode for himself there, going out to continue his search during the day while cultivating at night.

Five or six years flew by in a flash.

During this time, Han Li didn't have any luck in his search for the Profound Zoysia Crystal, but he learned many things about Jade Gathering City.

This place was truly a central hub for countless immortals and businesses, and the number and variety of things like spirit materials, spirit medicines, treasures, and cultivation arts being sold here far surpassed that of any city in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

Furthermore, the wares being sold here held significant advantages in terms of quality and price as well.

Compared with the free market system adopted in the Transient Guild, the prices of the wares being sold in Jade Gathering City were clearly determined in a much more organized and systematic fashion. Hence, during his search for a Profound Zoysia Crystal, Han Li had sold many of his redundant immortal treasures, spirit materials, and other items, and he had also purchased many supplementary ingredients for refining Baleful Quelling Pills.

However, he didn't dare to splurge excessively on those items, only buying one or two of each supplementary ingredient. After all, he was going to need all of the Immortal Origin Stones that he could save up if he really did encounter a Profound Zoysia Crystal.

He had made a killing back in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, but in the wake of his journey through the primordial land and the expenditures that he had made in Jade Gathering City, he currently only had fewer than five hundred thousand Immortal Origin Stones left.

This sounded like quite a significant sum, and it was, but it was only a fraction of the wealth that he had possessed prior to entering the primordial land. This rate of spending was quite alarming to Han Li, and he decided that he had to be more frugal from now on.

At this point, he had already visited most of the large shops in the city, but he still hadn't received any news on the Profound Zoysia Crystal. During his search, he had significantly neglected his cultivation, so he left Jade Gathering City and returned to the Leisure Valley once again.

The days spent in the valley were just as peaceful and leisurely as usual, and less than half a year following Han Li's return, he suddenly received a message from Daoist Master Jingyang, inviting him to a gathering at the Wave Ripple Pavilion in the valley.

He declared that the Purple Seductress wine that he had been brewing was ready, and he wanted everyone to have a taste.

Han Li initially turned down the invitation, but Daoist Master Jingyang was very persistent, sending him two more invitations, so Han Li had no choice but to oblige in the end.

The Wave Ripple Pavilion was situated quite deep in the Leisure Valley, and it was closest to Mo Wuxue's cave abode. It was a waterside pavilion constructed at the center of a pond, and it wasn't very large, but it was a beautiful display of intricate craftsmanship.

By the time Han Li arrived, everyone had already gathered in the pavilion.

Duan Yuzai and the others were seated around a stone table that was laden with immortal fruits, beside which was a green jade wine flagon that contained fragrant dark purple wine, while Yu Ziqi was seated with his legs crossed behind a guqin further away from everyone else.

His slim fingers were gently strumming the strings of his guqin, and there was a warm smile on his face as he occasionally glanced at the only woman in the pavilion.

"Fellow Daoist Li, you are the only one in this valley whose taste is on a comparable level to mine. If you didn't show up, I would've been absolutely distraught!" Daoist Master Jingyang complained at Han Li's tardy arrival.

"My apologies, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. I only just came back from Jade Gathering City, and I still had some errands to attend to. Otherwise, I wouldn't have turned down your initial invitation," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute.

Mo Wuxue was a beautiful young woman in a white dress, and she asked, "I hear you went to Jade Gathering City to find a Floral Heart Stone. Did you manage to find one?"

"I'm afraid not, Celestial Maiden Mo," Han Li replied with a wry smile and a shake of his head.

Duan Yuzai was in his usual pristine black robe, and he said, "None of my old friends were able to provide any news on a Profound Zoysia Crystal, either."

"I suppose there isn't much that we can do aside from wait. Let's not discuss this matter today. Otherwise, it would spoil the mood and do a complete injustice to Fellow Daoist Yu's music and Fellow Daoist Jingyang's exquisite Purple Seductress,'" Han Li said with a faint smile.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Li! I propose a toast!" Daoist Master Jingyang said with a wide smile as he presented a filled jade cup to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the cup, then took a slight whiff of its contents before listing out a string of ingredients, then concluded, "You've truly added a whole host of exceptional ingredients to this wine, Fellow Daoist Jingyang."

"That's extraordinary, Fellow Daoist Li! You've just listed almost all of the ingredients in my wine brewing recipe, and you haven't even taken a sip yet! How did you manage to do that?" Daoist Master Jingyang exclaimed.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Jingyang, this is nowhere near as impressive as you make it sound," Han Li chuckled in a modest fashion.

Back in the Blaze Dragon Dao, Han Li had tasted a vast array of exceptional wines with Daoist Hu Yan, and the two of them had discussed wine brewing extensively, thereby allowing Han Li to develop a very deep and comprehensive understanding in this field.

The wine soon began to flow, and as everyone was enjoying the Purple Maiden brew, Daoist Master Jingyang suddenly turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame with a gloating look on his face as he asked, "Old Man Hot Flame, you've been in Jade Gathering City for a long time, have you ever attended a Jade Kun Pagoda auction?"

"The auction only takes place once every three thousand years, and the spots are always limited. The Golden Jade Silk Squares required for entry to the auction is exceptionally rare, and I recall one time that someone was reselling a Golden Jade Silk Square for as high as six hundred Immortal Origin Stones!

“I may be the grand elder of the Fire Leaf Sect, but even I can't just go wasting six hundred Immortal Origin Stones on a Golden Jade Silk Square, so I've naturally never attended one of these auctions," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied.

"So that means you've never seen a Golden Jade Silk Square before, right?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked with a smug smile.

"What are you trying to say?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked as a disgruntled look appeared in his eyes.

"I wanted to show you something..."

Daoist Master Jingyang raised a hand as he spoke, and a palm-sized golden silk square appeared amid a flash of golden light.

The silk square looked as if it had been woven out of countless incredibly thin silk threads, and an octagonal pagoda design was embroidered onto its center, surrounded by images of various types of birds, beasts, insects, and fish.

It was immediately apparent to Han Li that the octagonal pagoda was the Jade Kun Pagoda.

"Impossible! There are still over two hundred years until the next auction, there's no way the Golden Jade Silk Squares would be released this early!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame exclaimed as he sprang to his feet with a stunned expression.

"What? Are you saying that my Golden Jade Silk Square is fake?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked as a displeased look appeared on his face.

"Of course I know it's not fake. These Golden Jade Silk Squares were created by the Hundred Creations Mountain, and there's no way this level of craftsmanship can be faked. On top of that, with the Black Mountain Immortal Palace overseeing these auctions, who would dare to make a counterfeit? Only someone with a death wish would do that!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame grumbled.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing mention of the Hundred Creations Mountain.

He wasn't unfamiliar with this sect. In fact, the Hundred Meridian Refinement Mantra that he had cultivated back in the Spirit Realm had come from the Hundred Creations Mountain, and he had also heard mention of this sect on multiple occasions since then.

Even in the context of the entire True Immortal Realm, the Hundred Creations Mountain was an extremely prominent tool refinement sect, and it was extraordinarily powerful, with branches set up in many major immortal regions.

Yu Ziqi also stood up and made his way over to Mo Wuxue's side upon seeing this.

With everyone's attention focused on him, Daoist Master Jingyang was feeling even more smug, and he feigned an expression of modesty as he said in a nonchalant voice, "It's no big deal..."

"You didn't invite all of us here to drink wine, you old fart! You made all of us come here so that you could show off your Golden Jade Silk Square!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame denounced.

"No, no, I'm showing all of you this Golden Jade Silk Square because I wanted to tell Fellow Daoist Li that I'll be keeping an eye out for any Profound Zoysia Crystals during the Jade Kun Pagoda auction, and that if I see one, I'll be sure to secure it for him," Daoist Master Jingyang explained.

"In that case, why don't you just do Fellow Daoist Li another favor and give him this Golden Jade Silk Square outright?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a sly grin.

"Well... I also want to see if any treasures that are to my liking will show up during the auction," Daoist Master Jingyang said with a faint smile as he stowed the Golden Jade Silk Square away.

Han Li was naturally quite eager to secure the Golden Jade Silk Square for himself, and he transmitted his voice directly to Daoist Master Jingyang as he asked, "Would it be possible for you to give me the Golden Jade Silk Square, Fellow Daoist Jingyang? I can repay you in anything, whether that be Immortal Origin Stones, pills, treasures, or even the wine recipes that you've always wanted."

Chapter 611: True Identity

Daoist Master Jingyang was silent for a long while, seemingly mulling over Han Li's offer, but ultimately, he replied, "My apologies, but this Golden Jade Silk Square was quite difficult to come by, so I can't give it to you. Rest assured, I'll definitely secure a Profound Zoysia Crystal for you if it shows up during the auction."

"In that case, can you at least tell me how you managed to obtain this Golden Jade Silk Square?" Han Li asked.

"Even though the auction is set to take place over two hundred years later, the preparations for the event have already begun. I hear that they're missing a pill refinement master for pill appraisals, and I can see that you're a very competent pill refinement master, so perhaps you can apply for the role," Daoist Master Jingyang replied.

"Is that how you were able to secure your Golden Jade Silk Square, Fellow Daoist Jingyang?" Han Li asked.

"I'm trying to do you a favor here, Fellow Daoist Li, please don't pry into my personal matters," Daoist Master Jingyang replied in a resigned manner.

"My apologies. You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist."

Immortal Lord Hot Flame and the others were naturally oblivious to the conversation that had just taken place, and they continued to drink wine while denouncing Daoist Master Jingyang for being too stingy.

......

Half a month later, Han Li left the Leisure Valley once again.

In accordance with the instructions provided to him by Daoist Master Jingyang, he traveled directly to the Jade Kun Pavilion upon entering Jade Gathering City.

Just like last time, the doors of the Jade Kun Pagoda were tightly shut and sealed with talismans.

Han Li made his way around the Jade Kun Pagoda, then traveled down a street behind the pagoda until he entered a dead-end that was around six feet wide.

He strode over to the wall at the conclusion of the dead-end, then conjured up some immortal spiritual power over the palm of his hand before pressing it against the wall, upon which his entire body sank into the wall.

Han Li's vision turned dark for a moment, following which he arrived in a spacious courtyard.

Immediately thereafter, the sound of clanging armor rang out, and several warriors clad in suits of bright silver armor converged to surround him.

Han Li swept his gaze over these warriors and was surprised to discover that none of them were living beings. Instead, they were all Dao Warriors, and what was most remarkable about them was their suits of armor were riddled with spirit patterns that were giving off formidable energy fluctuations.

Each one of them seemed to possess Grand Ascension Stage power, which was naturally completely insignificant in the face of a Golden Immortal, but there were potentially some other special restrictions concealed in their bodies.

"Who goes there?" one of the Dao Warriors asked in a rather mechanical voice.

"I heard that the Jade Kun Pagoda requires a pill refinement master, so I've come here to try my luck," Han Li replied in a direct and straightforward manner.

"Come with me," the Dao Warrior instructed, then began to make its way toward a hall at the back of the courtyard.

Han Li followed along behind the Dao Warrior, while the other Dao Warriors also trailed along, continuing to surround Han Li in a loose encirclement.

Upon arriving at the entrance of the hall, the Dao Warriors formed two lines on either side of the entrance before falling still, while Han Li took a brief glance at his surroundings before entering the hall.

The interior of the hall was brightly lit, and there were three large chairs placed at its entrance. The chairs on either side were occupied by a thin elderly man wearing a tall hat and a burly elderly man with a dark red complexion, while the middle chair was vacant.

Both of the men were wearing the same attire with a flame design embroidered onto the chest of their robes, within which was what appeared to be a pair of iron hammers crossed over each other.

"You're here to apply for the role of pill appraiser?" the thin man on the left asked in a slightly raspy voice.

"That's right," Han Li replied.

"Do you know what prerequisite must be satisfied for the role?" the burly man on the right asked.

"No," Han Li replied.

"We need a pill refinement master that can refine at least High Zenith Stage pills. Do you fit the bill?" the thin man asked.

"Does that mean that if I can refine High Zenith Stage pills, I'll receive a Golden Jade Silk Square?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. If you can do that, then you'll be able to attend the auction, but of course, you have to fulfill your duties as a pill appraiser at the event," the burly man confirmed with a nod.

Han Li didn't waste any more time, cutting straight to the chase as he asked, "Do you have a pill refinement chamber here that I can use?"

"You can use the side hall to your left," the burly man replied.

Han Li did as he was told, making his way into the side hall before closing the door.

Right at this moment, a figure slowly emerged from the back of the hall, then sat down casually onto the middle chair. He then took a glance at the side hall to the left and chuckled, "It looks like he's set up an isolation restriction of quite a high caliber. How cautious..."

"Is he really able to refine High Zenith Stage pills, Deputy Mountain Master?" the thin man asked as he turned to the man in the middle chair.

"Who knows? We'll just have to wait and see..."

......

Close to half a year flew by in the blink of an eye, and on this day, the door of the side hall finally swung open.

After one failure, Han Li used his final remaining batch of ingredients to refine three Clear Jade Pills.

"These pills are of an exceptional quality and contain tremendous spiritual qi! Out of all of the Clear Jade Pills I've seen, these definitely rank among the top three!" the thin man praised in an ecstatic voice as he examined the freshly refined batch of pills.

The burly man was far more calm and composed, but there was still a pleased smile on his face as he agreed, "Indeed! You definitely possess the pill refinement nous required to take on the role of pill appraiser during the auction."

Han Li accepted the Clear Jade Pills that were being handed back to him by the thin man, then smiled as he asked, "In that case, it's about time that Fellow Daoist Jingyang came out to see me, right?"

The expressions of both men stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and they exchanged an awkward glance with one another.

Right at this moment, Daoist Master Jingyang emerged from the back of the hall as he chuckled, "As expected of you to have correctly guessed my identity right away, Fellow Daiost Li."

He was also wearing a robe of the same style as the other two men in the hall, except the flame design embroidered onto the chest of the robe was golden in color.

"It was quite obvious. Back when I first arrived here, they didn't even ask who I was before allowing me to commence my pill refinement attempt right away, so they clearly already knew who I was in advance. On top of that, they were already aware that I would come here.

“To make things even more obvious, the main chair in the hall had been left vacant, all but telling me that there was someone else overseeing the proceedings from behind the scenes," Han Li said with a smile.

"You really should learn to be more subtle and tactful, Fellow Daoist Li," Daoist Master Jingyang chuckled as he took a glance at the vacant chair in the hall.

After that, he dismissed the other two men, then began making his way toward the back of the hall.

"I wanted to lay things out to you in a more direct fashion, but this auction is being jointly held by the Black Mountain Immortal Palace and our Hundred Creations Mountain, and there are some rules that I have to follow. I'm already aware of your pill refinement prowess, so I only asked you to come here as a formality more than anything else," Daoist Master Jingyang explained.

"Thank you for giving me this opportunity, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. May I ask what you true identity is?" Han Li asked.

Daoist Master Jingyang heaved a faint sigh upon hearing this, and he pulled out a wine gourd from beneath his robe, then took a sip of wine before replying, "I am one of the 72 deputy mountain masters of the Hundred Creations Mountain, and I'm responsible for overseeing our Black Soil Immortal Region branch."

"Black Soil Immortal Region? Not the Black Mountain Immortal Region?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression.

"The Black Soil Immortal Region, the Black Mountain Immortal Region, the Concealed Lake Immortal Region, and the Origin Contention Immortal Region are very close to each other, and aren't separated by any primordial lands, so they're collectively known as the four allied immortal regions.

“Our Hundred Creations Mountain branch is set in the Black Soil Immortal Region, but it oversees all of the four allied immortal regions. Otherwise, a deputy mountain master like myself wouldn't have been assigned to this place," Daoist Master Jingyang explained.

"In that case, why have you concealed your identity and settled in the Leisure Valley?" Han Li asked.

"I'm a lot like Old Man Hot Flame, I can't stand having to deal with a bunch of official responsibilities. I came to the Black Mountain Immortal Region because I had heard that the Floating Cloud Mountain Range was a great place to escape from worldly responsibilities, and I met Yu Ziqi and became close friends with him on the way here," Daoist Master Jingyang explained.

Daoist Master Jingyang could see that Han Li was still looking a bit skeptical, and a disgruntled look appeared on his face as he exclaimed, "Quit suspecting me of foul play! I didn't even have to personally oversee this auction, nor did I want to get involved, but I did so anyway just to gather information about Floral Heart Stones for you! You should be grateful rather than suspicious!"

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, and he asked, "Is that really the case?"

"Well, I suppose that's not entirely true. I always come to attend these auctions, but only on my own behalf, it's just that this time, I'm getting involved in the official side of things," Daoist Master Jingyang admitted as a sheepish smile appeared on his face.

"In any case, I must thank you, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. You can have the brewing recipes for Fire Drop Wine and Red Mulberry Wine in return for what you've done for me. As for everyone else in the Leisure Valley, rest assured, I won't speak of this to anyone," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

Daoist Master Jingyang immediately gave Han Li a thumbs up as he praised, "You're a good man, Fellow Daoist Li! Come, let's go and have a drink together. Neither of us is going home until we're both drunk!"

Chapter 612: Insider Information

Two hundred years was nothing more than the blink of an eye in the Floating Cloud Mountain Range.

Over the past two hundred years, the residents of the mountain range continued to while away their days, engaging in various hobbies and leisurely activities, enjoying life in the ways that they saw fit, as opposed to focusing on cultivation.

During this time, some more residents had moved into the mountain range, while some had left, but not much attention was paid to these personnel shifts.

The True Immortal Realm was still the same True Immortal Realm, but several generations had already passed by in the mortal world, and perhaps even dynasties had come and gone.

Every once in a while, Han Li would return to Jade Gathering City to search for Profound Zoysia Crystals, and during those trips, he had sold and bought pills and spirit medicines from many of the shops in the inner city.

As a result, they had all become quite familiar with him, and it soon became common knowledge that there was an outer sect elder of the Fire Leaf Sect searching for a Floral Heart Stone.

However, during his past few visits to the city, Han Li noticed that many places in the city were under repair, and decorations had already been put up on some of the main streets in anticipation for the celebratory ceremony that was to take place in the city once every three thousand years.

In particular, over the past few months, ships had been flying into the city from all parts of the Black Mountain Immortal Region and even from the neighboring few immortal regions, so all of the docks in the city had become very busy.

There were also all types of signs and banners hung up outside the shops in the city, carrying phrases like "great quality and fair prices" and "all immortals and mortals welcome". There were also some more unique advertisements like "buy one get one free", "big discounts inside", and "don't miss these once-in-three-thousand-years savings".

Compared with the past, there were more people in Jade Gathering City, and all of the immortal inns in the city had already reached full capacity. As a result, many of the sects in the city had opened up their spare courtyards for visiting merchants and cultivators to live in, earning some rent in the process.

Even the usual peace in the Floating Cloud Mountain Range had been broken, with many of its residents planning to enter Jade Gathering City during the festivities to see if they could acquire some items to their liking.

Even though they lived quite close to Jade Gathering City, they were anticipating the celebrations just as eagerly as all of the foreign cultivators who had gathered from far and wide.

This was because during the seven days in which the celebrations were held, all of the restrictions in the city were lifted, and everyone was allowed to visit the outer and inner cities as they pleased.

On top of that, hundreds of auctions hosted by various different powers were going to be held in the city, and the most prominent one of all of them was none other than the auction jointly held by the Black Mountain Immortal Palace and the Hundred Creations Mountain in the Jade Kun Pagoda.

The reason why this auction was garnering so much attention wasn't just because of its powerful official backing. Instead, it was because there were several premium items that appeared in virtually every single auction that were highly sought after even for High Zenith Stage Jade Immortals.

Whenever such a treasure appeared, a fierce bidding war would inevitably follow, and regardless of who managed to secure the item in the end, it would be a story that was told for a long time to come.

Seven days before the commencement of the ceremony, Han Li arrived in the Jade Kun Pagoda with Daoist Master Jingyang.

There was an underground palace inside the pagoda, within which were all types of intricate arrays and restrictions, and there were also three Golden Immortal Stage elders stationed inside at all times. This was where all of the auction items were being stored.

Han Li and the other two pill appraisers began to appraise the pills and spirit medicines among the auction items with Daoist Master Jingyang in accompaniment, cataloging the items one after another.

Only on the eve of the ceremony were all of the auction items finally cataloged and stored away appropriately.

Having already grown accustomed to a peaceful life of leisure, the past few days of toil had taken quite a toll on Daoist Master Jingyang, and as soon as all of the tasks that he had to attend to were completed, he immediately made his way to the courtyard that Han Li was staying in.

Even before he announced his arrival, Han Li had already opened the door before inviting him into the room.

After Daoist Master Jingyang had taken a seat, Han Li poured a cup of tea for him, then jibed, "It's a good feeling to be doing everything in person, isn't it?"

"It's been a very long time since I've had to conduct official duties like this, and I have to say, it's quite exhausting," Daoist Master Jingyang replied with a wry smile.

He then took a slightly disdainful glance at the tea that Han Li had poured for him before asking, "Do you have any more Fire Drop Wine?"

"Didn't I already give you the wine recipe? Why are you still asking me for wine?" Han Li asked.

"Don't be so stingy! Your wine is much more aged than mine! My wine is only less than 150 years old, so it doesn't taste anywhere near as good. Also, I'm not just drinking your wine for free, I have some insider information to divulge to you," Daoist Master Jingyang said as he lowered his voice in a mysterious manner.

Han Li could only give a wry smile upon hearing this, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon a dark gray wine jar.

"This is the final jar in my collection, and it's even older than the one I treated you to last time, so whatever insider information you have for me better be worth my while," Han Li said as he removed the clay seal of the jar.

As the rich fragrance of the wine filled the entire room, Daoist Master Jingyang's eyes immediately lit up, and he eagerly filled a teacup with wine before downing it in one go, then smacked his lips with a blissful expression as he savored the residual flavor of the wine.

"This is truly some exceptional wine," Daoist Master Jingyang praised as he reached out for the wine jar again, only to be stopped by Han Li.

"What insider information do you have to tell me?" Han Li asked.

"Can't you wait for me to have a few more cups of wine first?" Daoist Master Jingyang complained.

"Hurry up!" Han Li urged.

"Fine... The Profound Zoysia Crystal that you're looking for has turned up. The final batch of auction items that arrived this afternoon just so happened to include a Profound Zoysia Crystal," Daoist Master Jingyang revealed.

An ecstatic look immediately appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

"Don't celebrate just yet!" Daoist Master Jingyang continued. "The projected starting price for the crystal will be one thousand Immortal Origin Stones, and the final selling price could easily be several times the starting price. Do you have enough money to afford it?"

Han Li was internally rather amused to hear this. For the average Golden Immortal, several thousand Immortal Origin Stones would indeed be a significant sum, but it wasn't a concern at all for Han Li.

"Don't forget that I'm a pill refinement master, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. My spending is very extravagant, but I can earn money just as quickly. I've already planned for this for a very long time, so I'm naturally well prepared," Han Li replied with a smile.

Despite Han Li's reassurance, Daoist Master Jingyang wasn't entirely convinced that Han Li wasn't being overconfident. Having attended so many of these auctions himself, he had seen far too many people going in with what they perceived to be more than sufficient funds, only to fall well short in the end.

However, instead of directly expressing his skepticism, Daoist Master Jingyang said, "If you don't have enough Immortal Origin Stones on the day, you can pawn some pills to our Hundred Creations Mountain, and I'll make sure to offer you some good prices. If you wish to buy back the pills, you can do so at the same price. How does that sound?"

"That's very kind of you, Fellow Daoist Jingyang," Han Li replied as he pushed the entire jar of Fire Drop Wine toward Daoist Master Jingyang.

......

The next morning, a resounding bell chime rang out across the entirety of Jade Gathering City.

All four of the inner city's gates were opened, and the cultivators stationed at the city gates had also been removed, but the number of cultivators patrolling the city walls had increased by severalfold.

As the restrictions on the city gates faded, all of the cultivators that were already waiting outside eagerly poured into the inner city.

The peaceful streets and alleys of the inner city instantly became very rowdy and lively as throngs of people spread throughout the inner city, with some visiting the shops that lined the streets, while others went to attend the auctions being held.

All of a sudden, the inner city had become even more lively and bustling than the outer city.

At night, the decorative lanterns in the inner city were lit, basking the entire place in a bright red glow, and fireworks were also set off atop the city walls to further enhance the celebratory atmosphere.

Six days flew by in a flash, and it was finally time for the heavily anticipated Jade Kun Pagoda auction.

As part of the auction's organizer panel, Han Li and Daoist Master Jingyang were able to enter the auction venue ahead of everyone else.

From the outside, the Jade Kun Pagoda appeared to be no different from an ordinary pagoda, but it was extraordinarily spacious inside.

At the center of the pagoda was a large circular stone platform that was clearly going to be used to display the auction items, and there was a tight and orderly circle of small guest suites around the stone platform.

Overall, there were several hundred of these guest suites on the first, second, and third floors.

Each suite contained a table and a cushion, and on each table was placed an incense burner, as well as some spirit fruits and a flagon of fine wine.

Han Li and Daoist Master Jingyang made their way into a guest suite on the second floor, and inside was a young woman in a palace dress, who immediately brought in an additional cushion before filling their cups with wine.

Han Li took a glance at the woman, and to his surprise, she was not an actual person. Instead, it was a puppet that was giving off a Core Formation Stage aura.

Han Li withdrew his gaze from the puppet, then asked, "Are you really not going to host the auction, Fellow Daoist Jingyang?"

Chapter 613: Unexpected First Item

"Have I not been busy enough these past few days?" Daoist Master Jingyang harrumphed in an indignant manner. "Right now, all I want to do is participate in the auction in peace and acquire whatever catches my eye."

"If your Hundred Creations Mountain is overseeing this auction, then why are you taking such a roundabout route by attending the auction? Why not just purchase whatever you want before the auction begins?" Han Li asked.

"Not all of the auction items come from our Hundred Creations Mountain, Fellow Daoist Li. Some were sent here from elsewhere by the Black Mountain Immortal Palace, while others came from certain major sects in the immortal region. There are many significant parties involved in this auction, so I can't just do whatever I please," Daoist Master Jingyang explained with a shake of his head.

"In that case, it sounds like I won't be able to save any Immortal Origin Stones through my connection to you," Han Li said with an amused smile.

"There's a set of rules that dictate how the auction is run, and the event is also overseen by people from the Immortal Palace, so no one has an unfair advantage over anyone else. The only thing that any of us can do is prepare as many Immortal Origin Stones as possible. Just like fine wines, fine treasures are priceless, and if you spot one, you have to make sure to claim it so you don't come to regret it in the future," Daoist Master Jingyang replied.

As the two of them were chatting with each other, some of the auction-goers had already begun filing into the venue, and they were making their way into the guest suites on the third floor.

Around two hours later, all of the hundreds of guest suites in the entire Jade Kun Pagoda had been occupied, and after a brief examination, Han Li discovered that all of their occupants were at or above the early-Golden Immortal Stage, including some unfathomable figures whose cultivation bases were undetectable to him.

Given how precious those Golden Jade Silk Squares were, they were all but unobtainable for the average cultivator, so it made sense that everyone attending the auction possessed such lofty cultivation bases.

Having said that, there were hundreds of other auctions that those other cultivators could attend, so their visit to the inner city certainly wouldn't be in vain.

Right at this moment, the thin elderly man from the Hundred Creations Mountain and a white-robed male representative of the Black Mountain Immortal Palace stepped onto the round stone platform together.

"That man's name is Fu Yuhai, and he's the head of the Black Mountain Immortal Palace's northern branch. He's also a late-Golden Immortal cultivator, but he doesn't have much actual jurisdictive power here. The one that's truly calling the shots is still that immortal envoy from the Heavenly Court that's stationed in the city, but he rarely ever makes an appearance," Daoist Master Jingyang explained.

"Do you know the cultivation base of that immortal envoy?" Han Li asked in a seemingly nonchalant, conversational manner.

"I do not. He's very mysterious, and even I've never had the chance to meet him," Daoist Master Jingyang replied with a shake of his head.

During the brief course of their conversation, Daiost Master Jingyang had already downed an entire flagon of wine on his own, and the puppet immediately brought out another flagon.

At this point, Fu Yuhai had already completed his introduction of the event, and the thin man from the Hundred Creations Mountain stepped forward to take his place as he declared, "Make sure to stay within your means during the auction and don't bite off more than you can chew. Once a bid is made, it cannot be revoked, so if anyone is found to be unable to afford a bid that they've made, then there will be consequences."

Fu Yuhai swept his gaze over the surrounding area, then took over from the thin man again as he declared, "Let the auction begin!"

With that, both of them stepped down from the stage, and they were replaced by a foreign male being dressed in colorful attire.

The man had a very strange appearance with an extremely wide face and a huge mouth, but a long and slender neck that made it resemble a colorful bird with the head of a toad.

This foreign being was the auctioneer that was going to be hosting the auction.

"Welcome to the Jade Kun Pagoda, esteemed guests. Today, I have the honor and privilege of serving as your auctioneer..."

Despite his rather unsightly appearance, the auctioneer had a very clear and engaging voice that was extremely pleasing to the ears.

"Without further ado, allow me to present our first item, the Phoenix Call Guqin."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a beautiful female cultivator stepped onto the stage while holding a red guqin with a professional smile on her face.

Everyone's attention was instantly drawn to the guqin.

Han Li swept his gaze over the instrument to find that it had been crafted out of a type of precious wood known as Chicken Blood Wood, and the head of the guqin had been carved into the shape of a phoenix's head, while its tail resembled a spruce of phoenix tail feathers.

The entire guqin was as translucent as jade, and there were crimson cloud-like patches within the material, presenting a gorgeous sight to behold.

Under instructions from the auctioneer, the female cultivator began to gently play the instrument, and even those who weren't well-versed with guqins could tell from the music that this one produced that it was of an exceptional quality.

However, arguably the most remarkable thing about the guqin was that it was just a normal instrument that was completely devoid of spiritual power fluctuations.

It was very puzzling to Han Li that the first item being sold in this prestigious auction was an ordinary, albeit high-quality, guqin.

"I'm sure all of you have heard of Pei Qingling, the Thousand Finger Goddess. Prior to embarking on her cultivation journey, this guqin was the instrument that she cherished the most. Only after she began cultivating did it gradually fall into disuse before ending up here today. The starting price is fifty Immortal Origin Stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least five Immortal Origin Stones."

As soon as the introduction was complete, a bid of fifty Immortal Origin Stones was instantly made by someone in a guest suite on the third floor.

The price was then immediately raised to sixty Immortal Origin Stones.

"Seventy!"

"Seventy-five!"

"Who is this Pei Qingling, Fellow Daoist Jingyang? Why is it just a normal instrument used by her is going for such a high price?" Han Li asked.

While it was true that the instrument displayed exceptional quality and craftsmanship, it was still just an ordinary instrument, and it wasn't even worth several dozen spirit stones, let alone Immortal Origin Stones.

For this sum of money, even certain Golden Immortal Stage pills or precious spirit materials and immortal treasures could be purchased.

"You've never heard of Pei Qingling?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked with a surprised expression. "She came from a family of musicians in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, and she possessed outstanding cultivation aptitude from birth, but chose to pursue music over cultivation during her formative years.

“On her sixteenth birthday, she performed the Soaring Phoenix Ballad, then suddenly declared that she was going to begin cultivating. From there, she made extraordinary progress, mastering the laws of sound and ultimately reaching the Great Encompassment Stage."

"I see..." Han Li replied with a contemplative expression.

"You may think this item isn't worth the price, but if someone ever gets the opportunity to present something like this to its original owner, then that would be a gift that's unmatched in terms of sentimental value. If Pei Qingling becomes the Sound Dao Ancestor, then this guqin's value will increase by an immeasurable degree," Daoist Master Jingyang continued.

Han Li nodded in agreement with this notion.

"I've heard that Pei Qingling is also a woman of extraordinary beauty, and that explains why there are so many male cultivators fighting over this instrument. It's clear that they're hoping that this guqin will somehow give them an outside chance of starting a blossoming romance with her, but of course, that's nothing but a naive dream," Daoist Master Jingyang chuckled.

In the end, the guqin was sold to a scholarly middle-aged man for 120 Immortal Origin Stones.

"Congratulations on securing the Phoenix Tail Guqin, Fellow Daoist. Our second auction item is a batch of Purple Yang Pills."

The female cultivator carried the guqin off the stage, and she was replaced by another female cultivator holding a purple platter, atop which sat a palm-sized white jade box.

"The Purple Yang Pill can be taken by both Golden Immortals and Jade Immortals, and there are thirteen in total in this batch. These pills are of an exceptional quality, and they're not to be missed. The starting price is one hundred Immortal Origin Stones," the auctioneer declared as he opened the jade box to reveal thirteen intricate pills that were shimmering with faint purple light, and a fragrant medicinal aroma instantly spread through the entire venue.

This was one of the many pills that Han Li had appraised, and they were indeed of an outstanding quality, so the starting price of one hundred Immortal Origin Stones was very reasonable.

"110!"

"120!"

"130!"

Before long, the price for the batch of Purple Yang Pills had been bid up to 160 Immortal Origin Stones.

This was a roughly suitable price, and any higher than this would be crossing into the territory of overbidding. Hence, no further bids were made beyond this point, and the pills were sold to a black-robed cultivator.

The third auction item was an Acquired Immortal Treasure of an extremely high quality. It was a formidable lightning fire badge that could be used even by late-Golden Immortal cultivators, and the starting price was 130 Immortal Origin Stones, while the final selling price turned out to be two hundred.

Chapter 614: Abnormal Occurrence

As one auction item was brought out after another, the atmosphere in the venue became more and more electric.

Han Li's mind was focused solely on the Profound Zoysia Crystal, so he couldn't work up any interest in the treasures before him.

However, right at this moment, the auctioneer suddenly declared, "Our next item is called a Time Severing Flagon, a treasure that contains some time law powers. Anything put into the flagon, whether that be ordinary items or spirit and immortal treasures, will be preserved in their original state as if time has been stopped, and no change will occur even after millions of years. The starting price is five hundred Immortal Origin Stones."

"510!"

"520!"

"550!"

The price was quickly bid up to 670 Immortal Origin Stones.

Right at this moment, a black-robed figure placed a bid of seven hundred Immortal Origin Stones, and a brief silence ensued in the wake of this bid, only to be quickly broken again.

"710!"

This bid had been made by Han Li.

The black-robed man, who was also on the second floor, took a glance at Han Li, then placed a bid of 720 Immortal Origin Stones, to which Han Li immediately responded with a bid of 750.

The black-robed man remained unfazed and bid the price up to 760.

"Eight hundred!"

Once again, Han Li was raising the price by a significant increment, and almost everyone in the entire venue instantly turned to look at him with surprised expressions.

The black-robed man finally backed out of the bidding war.

"Is that flagon really worth that many Immortal Origin Stones?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"For pill refinement masters like myself, we often have to refine certain special spirit liquids that are very expensive to make and can't be preserved for long, resulting in a great deal of waste. With this flagon, I'll be able to save far more Immortal Origin Stones down the line than what I'm paying for it now," Han Li explained.

In reality, he wanted to see if this flagon could store the spirit liquid or time crystals produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial, and even if it couldn't, this was still a rare item that contained time law powers, so it was worth the price for Han Li.

After that, the auction continued, and each subsequent auction item was more remarkable than the previous one, while the prices also steadily rose.

The bidding was becoming more and more intense, and among the auction items were two that had soul nourishment effects. Han Li participated in the bidding for both of them, but it seemed as if the black-robed man were intentionally targeting him, raising the prices until Han Li backed out of the bidding war on both occasions.

Han Li wasn't in desperate need for those items anyway, and he didn't want to attract too much attention, so he didn't insist on securing them.

Six hours flew by in a flash, and at this point, the auction had already progressed past the halfway mark, but the Profound Zoysia Crystal still hadn't appeared.

Han Li was unable to suppress his agitation, and he asked through voice transmission, "When will the Profound Zoysia Crystal appear, Fellow Daoist Jingyang?"

Daoist Master Jingyang suppressed his amusement as he replied, "Rest assured, as long as my memory serves me correctly, it should be the next auction item."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the auctioneer declared, "The next item is no ordinary treasure. It comes from a near bottomless ravine where countless living creatures have lost their lives. Despite the filth and decay that ran rampant in its environment, it remained pristine and untarnished. It is referred to as the essence of the soul, and just a single one can enhance the soul of a Golden Immortal by 10% to 30%."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he cast his gaze toward the stage as the auctioneer concluded, "The item that I am referring to is a Myriad Soul Herb, and the starting price is one thousand Immortal Origin Stones."

Han Li turned to Daoist Master Jingyang with a perplexed expression upon hearing this, and the latter was also looking back at him with a stunned expression, clearly completely taken aback by this turn of events.

"What's going on here, Fellow Daoist Jingyang? Could it be that you misremembered the sequence of items?" Han Li asked.

"I do enjoy my wine, but I'm not such a drunkard that I would misremember something so simple, particularly when it pertains to something that's so important to you. Hold on a second, I'll ask them what's happening," Daoist Master Jingyang replied with a slightly awkward expression, then immediately closed his eyes.

Meanwhile, a fierce bidding war was taking place, and it didn't take long before the price was bid up to over two thousand Immortal Origin Stones.

Treasures with soul nourishment effects were quite appealing to Han Li as well. With this Myriad Soul Herb, perhaps he would be able to speed up his progress in the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Hence, after a brief hesitation, he decided to also participate in the bidding, but right at this moment, Daoist Master Jingyang opened his eyes, seemingly having just communicated with someone through voice transmission.

Han Li immediately turned to Daoist Master Jingyang with an inquisitive gaze, and the latter looked back at him with a slightly apologetic expression as he explained, "Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, this item was a last-minute addition to the auction catalog. The next item should be the Profound Zoysia Crystal for sure."

"I see. Does this happen often?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Not at all. The final list of auction items is generally not going to be altered in any way. After all, last-minute additions need to be appraised on a last-minute basis as well, and that can be rather troublesome to arrange," Daoist Master Jingyang replied.

"I've already waited for so long, I can wait for a while longer. Having said that, whoever requested for this last-minute addition must be quite an important figure to have been granted such a privilege," Han Li said with a smile.

"Indeed. I was told that this person has some connection to the immortal envoy in the inner city, but if you ask me, I think this Myriad Soul Herb came directly from the immortal envoy himself. Only someone of his unfathomable cultivation base would be willing to put up such a precious item for auction," Daoist Master Jingyang said.

Han Li nodded in response, and he suppressed the urge to participate in the bidding for the Myriad Soul Herb.

All abnormal occurrences had to be treated with caution, and his instincts were telling him that something wasn't quite right here.

After a fierce bidding war, the black-robed man ultimately secured the Myriad Soul herb for the price of 3,500 Immortal Origin Stones.

The auctioneer seemed to be quite excited by the unexpectedly high price that the Myriad Soul Herb had been sold for, and he declared in an enthusiastic voice, "The next item is something that I'm sure many of you have been anticipating for a very long time."

As he was speaking, a green brocade box was delivered onto the stage by a yellow-robed young woman, and there were several talismans plastered to the box.

The young woman removed the talismans on the box, and it opened up on its own to reveal a fist-sized green crystal sitting inside.

The crystal was giving off a faint green glow, and it wasn't all that remarkable in appearance. Deep inside the crystal was a system of veins that formed the image of a flower.

The green crystal was giving off a peculiar fragrance, and everyone who caught a whiff of this fragrance instantly felt as if all of their internal organs had been cleansed.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of the crystal, and he reflexively sat up a little straighter.

"This is a Profound Zoysia Crystal, otherwise known as a Floral Heart Stone, and it's a premium ingredient for refining pills that can help one expel baleful qi and overcome their baleful decay. I'm sure there's no need for me to tell you all just how valuable something like this is for fellow daoists seeking to reach the High Zenith Stage.

“On top of that, this Profound Zoysia Crystal came from a Profound Zoysia Flower that was over two hundred thousand years of age, and our Jade Kun Pagoda had to go to great lengths to secure it, so it's not to be missed. The starting price is one thousand Immortal Origin Stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least one hundred Immortal Origin Stones," the auctioneer declared.

"One thousand!"

"1,100!"

"1,300!"

A string of bids immediately came rolling in.

Just as the auctioneer had described, this was a highly sought after item for anyone wishing to make a breakthrough to the High Zenith Stage, so it was naturally going to be very hotly contested.

In the blink of an eye, the price was elevated to beyond two thousand Immortal Origin Stones, and at this point, the rate at which the bids were being made began to slow down.

"Haven't you been searching for this crystal all this time, Fellow Daoist Li? Why have you still not made a bid?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked.

"I'm determined to secure this crystal, but there's no need to get involved in the bidding war right away," Han Li replied in a calm manner.

As the price breached the 2,500 mark, the entire venue suddenly fell silent.

The bid had been made by a portly man dressed in lavish clothes. He appeared to be more like a merchant than a cultivator, and in his arms was a pair of extremely beautiful female cultivators who were feeding him tea and snacks, which he devoured with glee.

"Fellow Daoist Gui of the Heavenly Treasure Trade House has made a bid of 2,500 Immortal Origin Stones. Is anyone going to make a higher bid?" the auctioneer asked as he scoured the venue.

"Three thousand!"

The same black-robed man who had purchased the Myriad Soul Herb was also getting involved in the bidding war, and he had raised the price by five hundred Immortal Origin Stones in a single bid, causing quite a stir in the process.

A Profound Zoysia Crystal was extremely precious, for sure, but this price was already slightly higher than what it was worth.

"3,100!" the portly man retaliated.

"3,500!" the black-robed man harrumphed coldly, and it seemed like a sum of several hundred Immortal Origin Stones was nothing to him.

The portly man's expression darkened slightly, and he didn't place any further bids.

The two female cultivators beside him could see that he was quite incensed, and they sat beside him in a still and obedient manner, not daring to make any moves for fear of irking him even further.

"3,600!"

Yet another auction-goer was tossing their hat in the ring, and this one was an elderly man with a head of gray hair.

Han Li turned to take a glance at the gray-haired elderly man to discover that the latter possessed a tremendous aura, and it was one of the people whose cultivation base had been unfathomable to him.

"Do you recognize this man, Fellow Daoist Jingyang?" Han Li asked in a seemingly casual manner.

"That man is Feng Tianyao, a High Zenith Stage elder of the Purple Lightning Sword Sect situated on the northeastern border of the Black Mountain Immortal Region. If he's also trying to get his hands on the Profound Zoysia Crystal, then I'm afraid that you're going to be facing some very stiff competition, Fellow Daoist Li," Daoist Master Jingyang replied with a slightly sympathetic look in his eyes.

Chapter 615: Another Beast Bone

"I see..." Han Li replied in an ambiguous fashion.

"3,800!"

As the two of them were speaking to one another, the black-robed man had placed another bid, this one only raising the price by two hundred Immortal Origin Stones.

"Four thousand!"

Han Li had finally placed his second bid.

He had already secured two auction items prior to this, and this latest bid attracted the attention of many of the people present, including Feng Tianyao and the black-robed man, both of whom were clearly less than pleased.

"4,100!" Feng Tianyao declared.

"4,200!" the black-robed man immediately retaliated.

"4,300!" Han Li declared in an unhurried manner.

Before long, the price had been raised to five thousand Immortal Origin Stones, and the bid had been made by the black-robed man.

Many of the cultivators present were very surprised to see this. While it was true that this was an extremely precious spirit material, this was still far too steep a price to pay.

Such an enormous sum of Immortal Origin Stones could be spent on a whole host of other things, and it seemed that the price was still set to increase even further.

"Five thousand Immortal Origin Stones for a Profound Zoysia Crystal? The two of you clearly have too much money on your hands!" Feng Tianyao sneered before backing out of the bidding war.

Han Li paid no heed to Feng Tianyao's mockery as he calmly placed another bid of 5,100 Immortal Origin Stones.

"5,200!"

The black-robed man refused to relent.

"5,500!" Han Li declared, and at this point, many of the other auction-goers had begun shaking their heads.

"Fellow Daoist Li, as a word of advice from one friend to another, while this Profound Zoysia Crystal is of quite a high quality, this is still far too steep a price to pay for it. Under normal circumstances, 4,500 Immortal Origin Stones should be the upper limit, so there's really no point in making any further bids," Daoist Master Jingyang said.

"Thank you for the advice, Fellow Daoist Jingyang, but this is something that I must acquire. Just as you said earlier, fine treasures and fine wines are priceless, so they must be secured to avoid future regrets," Han Li said with a smile.

"You're using my own words against me! Fine, do as you please. If you don't have enough Immortal Origin Stones, feel free to tell me," Daoist Master Jingyang chuckled.

The black-robed man was silent for a moment, then placed a bid of 5,600 Immortal Origin Stones, only to be immediately outdone by Han Li with a bid of six thousand.

The black-robed man took a long glance at Han Li, then finally fell silent and made no further birds.

The auctioneer was a little disappointed to see the fierce bidding war come to an end, but this was already a far higher price than he expected the Profound Zoysia Crystal to fetch, and after three calls were made with no further bids placed, the crystal was sold to Han Li.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was lamenting the enormous sum of Immortal Origin Stones that he had been forced to part with.

"You're really going all-out, Fellow Daoist Li. It looks like you're far wealthier than I imagined! Then again, I suppose some things must be done. After all, this is something that you may never encounter again," Daoist Master Jingyang consoled.

"Please don't make fun of me, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. In terms of personal wealth, how could I possibly compare with a deputy mountain master of the Hundred Creations Mountain like yourself?" Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"Speaking of our Hundred Creations Mountain, we're constantly on the search for brilliant individuals like yourself. If you're interested, you can come and serve as a guest elder for us," Daoist Master Jingyang offered.

"It's been a very long time since I've affiliated myself with any sect. Otherwise, I wouldn't have come to a place like the Leisure Valley. I'm already content just to cultivate in such a peaceful paradise, surrounded by friends like you, Fellow Daoist Jingyang," Han Li replied, tactfully turning down the offer.

Meanwhile, the auction continued.

Several more precious items were carried out one after another, with all of them fetching high prices, further heating up the atmosphere in the venue.

At this point, the auction was close to reaching its conclusion.

"Coming up next is one of our final three auction items, and of course, we've saved the best three for last. This is a cultivation art by the name of the Rippling Horizon Arts," the auctioneer declared as he set down a blue box onto the stage, within which was an antiquated blue jade slip.

Many of the auction-goers were rather perplexed, seemingly having never heard this name before, while flashes of recognition appeared in the eyes of others.

"Is this the cultivation art used by the Clear Sea True Lord who once reigned supreme over the Black Mountain Immortal Region?" a blue-robed man asked in an excited voice.

"That's right, this was indeed the primary cultivation art used by the Clear Sea True Lord several million years ago. It can support one's cultivation to the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage, and it can definitely rank among the top five water-attribute cultivation arts of the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

“Not only can this cultivation art allow one to master the laws of water, there's a chance that the cultivator can even master the more advanced laws of tides, allowing them to unleash the Horizon Tidal Wave, which was once the Clear Sea True Lord's signature ability.

“During the battle in the Moon Sea, the Clear Sea True Lord had used this very same ability to strike down tens of thousands of primordial beasts with a single attack, so its power cannot be overstated.

“The mantra for this ability is naturally enclosed in this cultivation art, but of course, the prerequisites for using the cultivation art are quite stringent. For one, the cultivator must possess a water-attribute spirit physique, and a water-attribute immortal physique would be even better.

“On top of that, prior to reaching the True Immortal Stage, they had to have exclusively used water-attribute cultivation arts, and the True Immortal Physique that they've attained must not be contaminated with spiritual power of any other attributes.

“That's all I'm going to say about this cultivation art. The starting price is three thousand Immortal Origin Stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least two hundred Immortal Origin Stones."

Han Li wasn't aware of this Clear Sea True Lord, but it was clear that the mention of his name had stirred up a great deal of excitement among the auction-goers, and the bidding immediately commenced.

It was extremely rare to encounter a cultivation art of such a high caliber, and if it could be used well, then perhaps it could serve as the foundation of a powerful cultivating clan or sect.

Han Li wasn't swept up by the hype, and he continued to chat with Daoist Master Jingyang.

While this was an exceptional cultivation art, it clearly didn't suit him, so he was content to serve as a bystander.

As more and more people began to participate in the bidding, the price was quickly raised to over seven thousand Immortal Origin Stones, and Han Li was quite surprised to see this.

"Ten thousand!"

All of a sudden, the price was raised by three thousand Immortal Origin Stones in a single bid, and all of the other bidders immediately fell silent.

Han Li turned to discover that the one who had made the bid was none other than the blue-robed man who had asked the question from before.

He was only at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, so it was very remarkable that he possessed such immense wealth.

The blue-robed man was ecstatic to see that no further bids were being placed, but right at this moment, a bid of eleven thousand Immortal Origin Stones was made by a daoist priest holding a horsetail whisk.

The man possessed a tremendous High Zenith Stage aura, but the blue-robed man wasn't intimidated by his competitor's lofty cultivation base as he raised the price further to twelve thousand Immortal Origin Stones.

"Thirteen thousand!" the daoist priest declared in a calm voice.

"Fourteen thousand!"

"Fifteen thousand!"

......

Both of them seemed determined to secure the cultivation art for themselves, and in the blink of an eye, the price had been bid up to in excess of twenty thousand.

All of the auction-goers present were shaking their heads upon seeing this. This was far too steep a price to pay, and one could easily purchase two cultivation arts of the same caliber for the same price.

"Twenty-two thousand!" the daoist priest declared, and it seemed that he wasn't even close to reaching the limit of his budget.

In contrast, the blue-robed man was breathing rather heavily, and it seemed that he was at his limit.

"Elder Zhu of the Water Mirror Sect has made a bid of twenty-two thousand. Is anyone going to outbid him?" the auctioneer asked, and his question was met with silence.

After waiting for a while longer, the auctioneer was just about to declare the cultivation art as sold when the blue-robed man suddenly rose to his feet, then flipped a hand over to produce a beast bone that was as green as jade before declaring, "Hold on, I don't have enough Immortal Origin Stones on me, so I wish to pawn this item!"

The auctioneer faltered slightly upon hearing this, but this was indeed within the rules of the auction, so he hurriedly called for the auction to be put on pause, then instructed the female cultivator on the stage with him to deliver the beast bone to a nearby appraiser.

Han Li immediately sat up straighter as an intrigued look appeared in his eyes.

The green beast bone produced by the blue-robed man was extremely similar in both size and appearance to that bone that he had secured from the skeleton of the giant green rat.

However, his spiritual sense wasn't able to detect any spatial fluctuations or spiritual power fluctuations from this beast bone, and it was as if it were nothing more than a bone from a mortal beast.

Maybe it's only similar in appearance...

Han Li had examined the green beast bone extensively over the years, and he had become more and more convinced that it was a spatial treasure, but some extremely advanced secret technique had been cast upon it, making it inaccessible to Han Li.

All of a sudden, Daoist Master Jingyang abruptly rose to his feet, and he was staring at the beast bone intently with a fervent look in his eyes.

The intrigue in Han Li's eyes grew even more pronounced at the sight of this reaction from Daoist Master Jingyang.

"Do you recognize this beast bone, Fellow Daoist Jingyang?" he asked in a casual manner.

Daoist Master Jingyang immediately realized that he had lost his composure, and he hurriedly sat down again, but instead of answering Han Li's question, he lowered his head in deep thought as if he were pondering something extremely important.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, but didn't say anything further.

Shortly thereafter, the beast bone was taken to a long table, seated behind which were three cultivators dressed in black attire, namely a middle-aged scholar, a white-haired elderly man, and a young woman whose face was concealed behind a veil.

These were all appraisers from the Black Mountain Immortal Palace.

The Jade Kun Pagoda auctions had always reeled in immense profits that were very tantalizing to the Black Mountain Immortal Palace, and in order to get a share of these profits, it had been sending more and more personnel to these auctions with each passing edition.

For this auction, close to half of the personnel involved had come from the Black Mountain Immortal Palace, and this was something that Han Li had heard from Daoist Master Jingyang over the course of one of their conversations.

Chapter 616: Astonishing Turn of Events

The three appraisers took turns inspecting the green beast bone, and all of them were rather perplexed, seemingly unable to identify the item.

The three of them exchanged a glance with one another, following which the white-haired elderly man asked, "How many Immortal Origin Stones are you planning to pawn this item for?"

"Thirty thousand!" the blue-robed man declared, immediately creating quite a stir in the venue.

Thirty thousand Immortal Origin Stones was not a small sum. In fact, it was higher than the price of the majority of the treasures sold during this auction thus far, and it was even higher than the current price that the Rippling Horizon Arts had been bid up to.

"This is a rather interesting item, but it has no spiritual power fluctuations at all. May I ask exactly what's so special about this bone that you're asking thirty thousand Immortal Origin Stones for it?" the middle-aged scholar asked.

"This bone is something that I obtained from a set of primordial ruins, almost at the cost of my own life. It may not possess any spiritual power fluctuations, but as far as I can tell, it's completely indestructible, able to remain completely unscathed even in the face of attacks from immortal treasures.

“I tried to have the bone refined into an immortal treasure, but no one is able to mold it at all. Hence, I'm certain that this bone is an exceptional treasure," the blue-robed man declared, but it was clear that he was flailing a little.

A hint of mockery flashed through the middle-aged scholar's eyes upon hearing this, and he exchanged another glance with his two colleagues.

Having worked as an appraiser for so long, he had seen countless people who proclaimed something to be a priceless treasure just because it possessed certain special attributes.

"It sounds like you're also unaware of the value of this item. In order to ensure a policy of fairness and openness, we'll only accept items with clear values, so I'm afraid we can't accept this bone," the middle-aged scholar declared.

"Fei Bin, you idiot!" Daoist Master Jingyang cursed under his breath as a frustrated look flashed through his eyes.

A furious look immediately appeared on the blue-robed man's face upon hearing this, and he was even more embarrassed by all of the mocking looks that were directed his way.

He had actually approached several appraisers with this beast bone in the past, and all of them had given him the same response.

However, with so many powerful figures gathered in one place here, he was hoping that someone would be able to identify the item, but it seemed that his hopes were misplaced.

At the same time, he couldn't help but waver slightly in his own conviction. Could it be that this bone really was a valueless piece of junk?

Right at this moment, a middle-aged man wearing a golden crown suddenly declared, "Hold on, I'll take that bone from you for thirty thousand Immortal Origin Stones."

The man was a High Zenith cultivator, and he was staring intently at the beast bone with a bright gleam in his eyes.

The entire venue immediately erupted into chatter upon hearing this, and everyone turned their attention back to the beast bone.

The three appraisers behind the table also faltered slightly upon hearing this, while the blue-robed man was ecstatic, and he was just about to agree to the offer when Daoist Jingyang interjected, "I'll give you thirty-five thousand!"

The blue-robed man's mouth immediately gaped open in astonishment upon hearing this, and before he had a chance to recover, the man wearing the golden crown increased the price to forty thousand!

"Fifty thousand!" Daoist Master Jingyang immediately retaliated.

"Sixty thousand!"

"Seventy thousand!"

......

The two of them were going back and forth in increments of ten thousand Immortal Origin Stones, and at this point, it had become clear to everyone that his beast bone was definitely some type of extraordinary treasure.

Before long, several more High Zenith cultivators had also entered the bidding war, and the blue-robed man was excited beyond belief.

Meanwhile, the three Immortal Palace appraisers behind the long table were left feeling a little awkward. The beast bone that they had deemed to be completely worthless was now the center of an astronomical bidding war, and each bid that was placed was like a slap across their faces.

Even the auctioneer was looking on in a completely stunned silence.

In the blink of an eye, the price for the beast bone had been bid up to two hundred thousand Immortal Origin Stones.

At this point, Daoist Master Jingyang and the man wearing the golden crown were the only ones who were still persisting.

"220 thousand!" Daoist Master Jingyang spat through gritted teeth.

The man wearing the golden crown could see that Daoist Master Jingyang was reaching his limits, and a cold sneer appeared on his face as he raised the price to twenty-five thousand.

"260 thousand!"

"270 thousand!"

"280 thousand!"

"Three hundred thousand!"

At this point, it was clear from the expression of the man wearing the golden crown that he was also nearing his limits.

"350 thousand!" Daoist Master Jingyang declared with a hint of strain in his voice, and all of the auction-goers instantly drew a collective sharp breath upon hearing this.

"350 thousand Immortal Origin Stones? Do you really possess such immense wealth? If you can bring out that many Immortal Origin Stones or things of equivalent value right here, then I'll concede the bone to you, but if you can't, then you'll be liable for intentional meddling!"

Daoist Master Jingyang's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, while Fu Yuhai turned to him with slightly furrowed brows, then declared, "Of course. The rules of the auction cannot be broken by anyone without consequences."

"Good. Let's see the Immortal Origin Stones now," the man wearing the golden crown said with a cold sneer.

Han Li took a glance at Daoist Master Jingyang.

Perhaps this wasn't apparent to others, but he was seated right next to Daoist Master Jingyang, so he could tell that the latter was feeling very uneasy.

It seemed that he really didn't have enough Immortal Origin Stones to support his bid.

"I'll present the Immortal Origin Stones to this blue-robed fellow daoist here after the auction," Daoist Master Jingyang harrumphed coldly.

"This bone is not an auction item, so there's no need to wait until the end of the auction. If you truly possess sufficient wealth to support your bid, then why not show everyone? Could it be that you don't actually have as much money as you claim?" the man wearing the golden crown sneered.

"Fine, if you insist, then take a good look!" Daoist Master Jingyang said as he rose to his feet, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of white light, enveloped within which were around a dozen items, most of which were materials, but there were also two immortal treasures and a vial of pills.

The collection of items descended onto the appraisers' table, and every single one of them was giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations.

"Please appraise these items to determine how many Immortal Origin Stones they're worth," Daoist Master Jingyang requested.

The three appraisers exchanged a glance with one another upon seeing this, then commenced the appraisal process, while the man wearing the golden crown looked on with slightly furrowed brows.

At the same time, Daoist Master Jingyang's voice rang out in Han Li's mind. "Fellow Daoist Li, do you have any spare Immortal Origin Stones? I need to borrow some from you."

"How much do you want?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"Eighty thousand," Daoist Master Jingyang replied.

"That's not a small sum," Han Li mused.

Daoist Master Jingyang was ecstatic to see that Han Li hadn't turned him down, and he immediately said, "I know, but rest assured, I can return the entire sum to you within 10 years."

"That beast bone must truly be an exceptional treasure for you to have spent so much money on it. I've examined it carefully with my spiritual sense, but haven't discovered anything remarkable about it. May I ask exactly what it can be used for?" Han Li asked.

"Truth be told, the beast bone is a spatial treasure, but its aura has been concealed by an extremely advanced restriction, and that's why you can't detect anything from it," Daoist Master Jingyang explained after a brief hesitation.

"I see..."

"How about this? If you lend me the eighty thousand Immortal Origin Stones, regardless of what's inside the beast bone, you can have a third of its contents," Daoist Master Jingyang proposed.

"Given the sincerity of your offer, it would be downright rude of me to refuse. Having said that, I want to be present when you're opening this spatial treasure," Han Li said.

Daoist Master Jingyang's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, but ultimately, he nodded in response. "Alright, but please don't tell anyone about what you see when the time comes."

Han Li also nodded in response, then pulled out a small storage ring before covertly stuffing it into Daoist Master Jingyang's hand.

Daoist Master Jingyang inspected the contents of the storage ring momentarily, following which a hint of elation flashed through his eyes.

The appraisal was quickly completed, and the middle-aged scholar declared, "We've appraised these items to be worth no less than 120 thousand Immortal Origin Stones."

Daoist Master Jingyang swept a sleeve through the air once again, and two streaks of light containing a pair of storage rings descended in front of the three appraisers.

"The rest of the Immortal Origin Stones are in there," he declared.

The three appraisers briefly examined the pair of storage rings, and it was declared that one ring contained eighty thousand Immortal Origin Stones, while the other contained seventy thousand, and that was sufficient to cover the cost of the beast bone.

"If you're still not convinced, then I invite you to examine the storage rings yourself, Fellow Daoist," Daoist Master Jingyang said as he turned to the man wearing the golden crown.

The man merely gave a cold harrumph and didn't respond.

With that, the impromptu auction for the green beast bone drew to a conclusion.

Chapter 617: Trap

The bone was quickly delivered to Daoist Master Jingyang by a beautiful female cultivator, and he held it in a white-knuckled grip as he examined it intently as if he were looking over a priceless treasure.

However, it then seemed to have occurred to him that he wasn't alone, and he carefully stowed the beast bone away before giving Han Li a faint smile.

At the same time, the enormous sum of Immortal Origin Stones and the collection of valuable items from Daoist Master Jingyang were delivered to the blue-robed man, who gave the three appraisers a disdainful sneer, then loudly declared, "I'll pay 23 thousand Immortal Origin Stones for the Rippling Horizon Arts!"

The daoist priest made no further bids upon seeing this, and in the end, the Rippling Horizon Arts was sold to the blue-robed man for exactly twenty thousand Immortal Origin Stones above its starting price.

The auction continued, and the final two items were brought out in succession.

The two items turned out to be a scroll capable of summoning Dao Warriors and a formidable golden ax, both of which were naturally sold for very high prices, but in the wake of the stunning impromptu auction for that green beast bone, these two treasures were made to look rather lackluster in comparison, and the reception was also rather lukewarm.

Following an enthusiastic final address from the auctioneer, the auction drew to a conclusion, and at this point, the three appraisers had already departed.

Daoist Master Jingyang and Han Li had both gotten what they wanted, and they began to make their way toward the exit of the venue, as did all of the other auction-goers, some of whom were clearly very content and cheerful, while others were less elated.

Having said that, no one was overly frustrated. Good things were always hard to come by, and the search was also a part of the process.

On top of that, there were still some other auctions and exchange events scheduled to take place in the, so they weren't entirely without chances to secure the items that they were searching for. Additionally, the prospect of being able to meet up with some old friends that they hadn't seen for thousands of years was also quite an exciting one.

Many of the auction-goers filing out of the venue were still discussing the events of the auction in a spirited fashion, and of course, the subject of most of these conversations was the beast bone that had been sold for 350 thousand Immortal Origin Stones. As a result, Daoist Master Jingyang also became a center of attention, and quite a few people approached him to strike up a conversation, trying to figure out exactly what that beast bone was.

However, Daoist Master Jingyang had no interest in making any conversation. At this moment, the only thing on his mind was returning to his cave abode as soon as possible. If he were approached by anyone that he knew or someone of a lofty status, then he would briefly respond in an amicable fashion, while the rest were outright ignored, and everyone else quickly learned not to approach him.

With Daoist Master Jingyang drawing all of the attention, Han Li had become nothing more than an afterthought to everyone, and he was quite happy to see this, trailing along behind Daoist Master Jingyang as they left the auction venue together.

Right at this moment, a black-robed man strode past Han Li, and it was none other than the black-robed man who had competed against Han Li for a couple of auction items.

The man's appearance had previously been concealed by the hood of his black robe, but now that they were in close proximity to one another, Han Li could see that this was a thin and handsome young man, but his face was rather abnormally pale.

The black-robed man just so happened to look at Han Li right as Han Li was looking at him, and the two of them exchanged a polite nod before the black-robed man continued onward.

Trailing along behind him was a purple-robed cultivator, and the two of them seemed to be companions.

The purple-robed figure had a head of shoulder-length purple hair and skin that was as fiar as jade, as well as a set of intricate features that made it impossible to tell whether they were male or female.

The purple-robed cultivator also took an expressionless glance at Han Li, then quickly withdrew his gaze before departing, but Han Li had stopped cold in his tracks to look at the two parting figures with slightly furrowed brows.

At this moment, Daoist Master Jingyang's mind was completely preoccupied with that beast bone,so he didn't notice the two men that had just passed them by, and he asked, "What is it, Fellow Daoist Li? Have you spotted some acquaintances?"

"No, it must've just been my imagination," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"In that case, let's go," Daoist Master Jingyang urged, clearly very eager to get back.

Han Li nodded in response, and the two of them made their way out of the auction venue.

"Come with me," Daoist Master Jingyang said to Han Li in a quiet voice, then turned in a certain direction, but right at this moment, a crimson cloud abruptly appeared in the sky before rapidly revolving.

At the same time, a series of crimson spirit patterns appeared over the surrounding ground, forming a red array that resonated with the cloud up above.

At this point, all of the auction-goers had only just emerged from the Jade Kun Pagoda, and all of them were instantly rooted to the spot by the tremendous restrictive force released by the array.

"What's going on?"

"It's a restrictive array!"

"Who dares to do something like this in the inner city?"

A chorus of alarmed and angry voices instantly rang out, while Han Li turned to Daoist Master Jingyang and asked, "What's happening?"

"I'm not sure, but no one would dare to do something like this in the inner city for no good reason, so let's wait and see what happens," Daoist Master Jingyang replied in a calm manner.

Han Li didn't say anything further, but his mind was racing.

He could sense that the surrounding crimson array was an extremely formidable restrictive array that also seemed to contain a burst of tremendous law powers that he hadn't noticed at all prior to the array's activation.

Before Han Li had a chance to think about anything else, two figures, one red and one azure, descended out of the sky.

Han Li immediately turned to the two figures to discover that both of them were wearing suits of golden armor identical to the ones worn by the Heavenly Court immortal envoys that he had seen during his latest instance of spiritual transmigration.

The duo was led by a man with a head of red hair. There were crimson flames burning all over his body, and his aura was so immense that the space around him was warping slightly.

This man's aura was far superior to even Gongshu Jiu's, indicating that he was a mid-High Zenith cultivator.

He was holding a giant crimson sword that was even taller than himself, and it was riddled with crimson scales. Furthermore, the sword was curved to resemble a fiery wyrm, the tail of the wyrm serving as the tip of the sword, while its head was the hilt.

Bursts of crimson light were flowing over the sword like blood, and it was clearly an extremely formidable weapon.

The other figure was a man who was as tall and thin as a reed stick, and his body was enveloped in a layer of radiant azure light.

His aura wasn't inferior in the slightest to that of his companion, and their distinctive attire immediately revealed their identities as immortal envoys.

"Don't be alarmed, everyone. We've come here to capture criminals of the Reincarnation Palace, who are among you right now. Everyone else, please wait for a moment, and we'll be releasing you shortly," the red-haired man said as his sharp gaze combed through the crowd.

Han Li's heart immediately jolted slightly upon hearing this.

Could it be that he had been exposed?

His mind was racing as he secretly channeled his immortal spiritual power, but his expression remained unchanged.

"You, you, and you, come with us for interrogation," the red-haired man ordered as he pointed at several people in succession, one of which was none other than the black-robed young man.

Han Li turned to the people that the red-haired man had pointed out, and a hint of relief instantly welled up in his heart.

All of these cultivators had placed bets on the Myriad Soul Herb from earlier. It seemed that his intuition had been correct, and that Myriad Soul Herb had indeed been a trap.

After picking out that selection of people, the red-haired man's gaze continued to rake through the crowd, and everyone who came under his scrutiny felt a sharp, pricking pain in their eyes.

All the while, Han Li remained calm and collected.

Even though he had cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique, and he possessed such immense baleful qi that he was close to a Gray Immortal, he had been consuming Origin Void Pills this entire time, so as long as he didn't channel his Spirit Refinement Technique, he shouldn't be exposed.

Sure enough, the red-haired man's gaze swept over Han Li without pause, but a hint of panic flashed through the eyes of a pair of red-robed cultivators beside him.

Even though it was only for an instant, it had failed to escape the red-haired man's notice, and he immediately picked them out of the crowd as well.

"Why are you detaining us? We're not members of the Reincarnation Palace!" one of the red-robed cultivators protested.

The red-haired man paid no heed to his complaints as he continued to comb through the crowd before picking out several more people.

"Everyone that I just picked out needs to come with me, the rest of you can leave," the red-haired man declared as he made a hand seal, and the restrictive array that had bound everyone to the spot instantly faded.

Everyone that hadn't been picked out heaved a collective sigh of relief before hurriedly departing, including Han Li and Daoist Master Jingyang.

The two of them quickly departed from the area where the Jade Kun Pagoda was situated, and at this point, many people had already gathered around the area to see what was happening.

Han Li's duo quickly made their way into the crowd, and Daoist Master Jingyang wanted to leave right away, but Han Li wanted to stay and find out what was happening.

Daoist Master Jingyang was quite reluctant to stay, but he couldn't just rebuke Han Li after borrowing such a large sum of Immortal Origin Stones from him, so he could only begrudgingly stay.

Thus, the two of them began to look on at the unfolding scene from within the crowd.

Chapter 618: Strange Thief

At this point, only around a dozen people were left standing in front of the Jade Kun Pagoda, all of whom had been picked out by the red-haired man.

Most of them had participated in the bidding for the Myriad Soul Herb, but for some reason, the blue-robed cultivator who had sold the beast bone for 350 thousand Immortal Origin Stones was also among them, and he was looking downright terrified.

Aside from that, the purple-robed cultivator with the black-robed young man hadn't been picked out, but he hadn't departed, either.

Han Li was in the crowd of spectators close to 10 kilometers away, and his pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this.

The red-haired man paid no heed to the bystanders as he swept a sleeve through the air, summoning a white jade flying boat before commanding, "Get on the boat."

There was a crimson cage of light on the flying boat with arcs of crimson lightning flashing over its surface, presenting a formidable sight to behold.

All of a sudden, a hint of alarm flashed through Han Li's eyes.

Earlier, he had felt like the red-haired man looked a little familiar, and upon closer inspection now, he realized that his facial features were quite similar to Gongshu Jiu's, so the two of them were most likely related.

Right at this moment, a blue-robed elderly man stepped forward as he harrumphed coldly. "You immortal envoys can't just do whatever you please! We're not members of the Reincarnation Palace, we've only come here for the Jade Kun Pagoda auction! You can detain anyone else you want, but I'm not just going to hand myself over!"

At the same time, bright blue light erupted out of his body alongside his peak Golden Immortal Stage aura, and a burst of glacial power swept through the surrounding area, instantly freezing the nearby space.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of blue ripples that were giving off glacial law power fluctuations surged out of the elderly man's body, basking the entire area in a radius of over a hundred feet around in a cold blue glow.

A dull thump then rang out as the elderly man propelled himself up into the heavens.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and all of the bystanders only saw a flash of blue light before the elderly man rose up into the sky.

"Did I say you could leave?" the red-haired man asked in a cold voice, and the giant sword in his hand began to glow brightly as he slashed it through the air.

A resounding boom instantly rang out above the elderly man's head, and a massive fiery wyrm projection emerged out of thin air.

A burst of tremendous heat erupted out of the wyrm projection's body alongside a tremendous aura, and it came swooping down upon the elderly man with unmatched power.

The blue spirit domain around the elderly man instantly began to tremble violently, and despite his headstart, the fiery wyrm projection had caught up to him in an instant.

In his desperation to get away, the elderly man opened his mouth to release a short blue spear immortal treasure, which shot forth toward the wyrm projection as a streak of blue light.

The fiery wyrm projection opened its mouth up wide, releasing a ball of crimson flames that rapidly swelled to form a fiery cloud the size of a house.

A resounding boom rang out as the fiery cloud and the streak of blue light clashed before both instantly exploded, and the fiery cloud swelled up even further to devour the blue spear, then continued to rumble directly toward the blue-robed elderly man.

In the blink of an eye, the elderly man was inundated by the fiery cloud, and a roar of fury and agony rang out from within.

Immediately thereafter, the fiery wyrm projection up above swooped into the fiery cloud as well, and an explosion rang out, following which the elderly man's voice abruptly faded.

The fiery cloud then disintegrated into countless specks of red light that quickly dissipated, and no trace of the blue-robed elderly man was left behind.

Everyone else was stunned into silence upon seeing this.

"Don't make me repeat myself," the red-haired man said in a cold voice.

After that display of intimidation, no one dared to raise any further objections, and they quickly flew onto the green flying boat before entering the crimson cage.

All of the bystanders in the distance were also stunned by what they had seen.

The red-haired man was even more powerful than Han Li had anticipated, but his gaze only lingered on him for a moment before he turned his attention to the black-robed young man, who hadn't flown onto the boat like everyone else.

The red-haired man turned to the black-robed young man with a cold look in his eyes, and the latter remained completely unfazed as he said with a nonchalant smile, "I have an avid interest in all flying spirit treasures, but I'm afraid I'm not a fan of cages."

The red-haired man exchanged a glance with his companion, following which the latter instantly appeared behind the black-robed young man.

"You were the one who purchased the Myriad Soul Herb, right, Fox 3 of the Reincarnation Palace?" the red-haired man asked.

"Fox 3? Are you speaking to me? You have the wrong guy, but that's not a bad name. I like it," the black-robed young man said with a relaxed grin.

"Ever since you snuck into the Vast Heavens Immortal Palace to steal that precious treasure a hundred thousand years ago, you've been periodically committing crimes across various immortal regions. We've finally managed to lure you out this time!

“If you know what's good for you, then surrender right away, and if you hand over the treasure that you stole, I can grant you a swift and painless death!" the red-haired man declared as the crimson flames around him began to steadily brighten.

A tremendous, scorching aura resembling that of a volcanic eruption surged out of his body, and the nearby ground instantly split open while becoming charred black.

A terrifying wave of heat swept forth in all directions, and all of the bystanders hurriedly retreated even further.

"So he's the renowned thief, Silver Fox!" Daoist Master Jingyang murmured to himself.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this. Back on the Immortal Slaying List in the city, he had indeed seen a man by the monicker of "Silver Fox".

According to the enclosed description, he was a member of the Reincarnation Palace, and he specialized in stealing all types of precious treasures, most of which belonged to the immortal palaces of various immortal regions.

Furthermore, before each of his crimes, he would always openly broadcast what he was going to do, but he had never been foiled, and he had already committed countless crimes to date.

"A treasure stolen from the Vast Heavens Immortal Palace? Now that you mention it, I do recall hearing about this. If I recall correctly, it was a Profound Heavenly Treasure that had been discovered by Palace Master Situ Bowen of the Vast Heavens Immortal Palace, and he was planning to offer it to the Heavenly Court.

“For that occasion, he had even held a grand ceremony with many Golden Immortals and even several immortal envoys sent from the Heavenly Court in attendance. Unfortunately, the treasure was stolen the day before the ceremony. What a pity!

“How embarrassing must that have been for that palace master and those immortal envoys? Having said that, why are you blaming me for this? Are you trying to find some random person to play the role of scapegoat?" the black-robed young man asked.

This had always been an extremely embarrassing incident that the Heavenly Court had tried to keep secret, yet the black-robed young man had just revealed the details of the incident in front of so many people.

This revelation naturally created quite a stir among the crowd of bystanders, and no one dared to say anything in the presence of these immortal envoys, but the ridicule and amusement in the eyes of some of the bystanders was very apparent.

Veins began to bulge on the red-haired man's forehead, and the killing intent in his eyes was growing by the second.

"No matter what you say, you're not getting out of Jade Gathering City alive!" the thin man standing behind the black-robed young man declared in a cold voice, while the red-haired man stepped forward with a cold sneer on his face.

The thin man also began to make his way forward, and the two of them approached the black-robed young man together while releasing their tremendous spiritual pressure.

"What a pain in the backside. Why am I always being harrassed by you people? All I want is to be able to live in peace, even if it's only for a short while. Is that really too much to ask?" the black-robed young man sighed in a resigned manner.

As soon as his voice trailed off, his body suddenly transformed into a warped silver line that vanished from the spot in the blink of an eye.

Meanwhile, the purple-robed cultivator was standing with his hands clasped behind his back while looking up at the sky, and it seemed that he had no intention of stepping in.

"You're not getting away!" the red-haired man roared as the flames burning over his body swelled up even further while rapidly spreading in all directions, instantly forming a crimson spirit domain that encompassed most of the Jade Kun Pagoda and several of the nearby buildings.

The crimson spirit domain was filled with incredible heat, and all of the buildings encompassed within it with the exception of the Jade Kun Pavilion were quickly incinerated into nothingness.

The bystanders looking on from afar retreated even further upon seeing this, but thankfully, they were already a sufficient distance away that they weren't encompassed within the crimson spirit domain.

After summoning his spirit domain, a hint of surprise flashed through the red-haired man's eyes.

He was unable to detect the presence of the black-robed young man through his spirit domain or his spiritual sense, and it seemed as if he had truly vanished.

In the instant that the black-robed young man made his escape, the thin man also immediately made a hand seal before releasing a beam of azure light that pierced into the space up ahead, and in the next instant, an enormous azure light barrier that encompassed an area with a radius of several dozen kilometers emerged.

It was a hemispherical light barrier with countless tornado projections raging through it amid bursts of thunderous rumbling.

Spatial fluctuations were emanating out of the azure light barrier, and it was clear that there were spatial restrictions inside that prevented the black-robed young man from using any teleportation techniques.

The two immortal envoys were clearly very well prepared in their bid to capture Silver Fox.

After doing all of that, the thin man also began searching for the black-robed young man, but all of a sudden, he noticed that the purple-robed cultivator was still standing with his hands clasped behind his back inside the red-haired man's fiery spirit domain.

He hadn't channeled any cultivation arts to protect himself, but the surrounding crimson flames were somehow kept three feet away from him by a burst of invisible force.

The thin man raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and he was just about to conduct a closer examination when a loud roar suddenly rang out as the red-haired man swiveled around while slashing his giant sword through the air.

A sharp clang rang out as the giant sword clashed against a streak of silver swordlight that was as thin as a cicada's wing, and it was giving off a faint glow, as well as a flurry of silver runes.

A cold sneer appeared on the red-haired man's face as the flames on his giant sword reared up with tremendous force, and the streak of silver swordlight was instantly shattered.

However, at the exact same moment, a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted behind the red-haired man, and two identical streaks of silver sword light emerged out of thin air before hurtling directly toward him from behind.

Chapter 619: True Appearance

The red-haired man's brows furrowed slightly, but he remained composed as he opened his mouth to release a burst of crimson light, which instantly swept through the air until it was behind him.

The burst of crimson light then transformed into a round crimson shield, and two sharp clangs rang out as the streaks of silver swordlight pierced into the shield, sending sparks flying in all directions.

The round shield shuddered slightly, but it was instantly able to stabilize itself again.

However, before the red-haired man even had a chance to catch his breath, four more identical streaks of silver swordlight emerged on either side of him before piercing toward him as well, and they were even faster than the precious streaks of swordlight.

The red-haired man's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and the giant sword in his hand suddenly began to glow radiantly as four fiery crimson sword projections were released.

All of the sword projections were giving off bursts of law power fluctuations, and they positioned themselves directly in the path of the four streaks of silver swordlight.

Three dull thumps rang out in succession as three streaks of silver swordlight were intercepted before exploding alongside the sword projections that they had crashed into, but right as the final streak of silver swordlight was about to clash against the sword projection that was in its path, the latter was suddenly moved slightly to the side.

The streak of silver swordlight just barely passed by the fiery sword projection, then abruptly appeared in front of the red-haired man's lower abdomen before plunging down at an incredible speed.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

In the instant that the crimson sword projection was diverted to the side, Han Li had sensed the aura of spiritual sense chains.

Right at this moment, a burst of radiant azure light abruptly appeared beside the red-haired man, then transformed into an azure spear that struck the streak of silver swordlight.

A dull thump rang out as the streak of silver swordlight exploded, while the thin man appeared beside the red-haired man before asking, "Are you alright, Brother Gongshu?"

A layer of cold sweat had beaded up on the red-haired man's forehead, and there was a hint of lingering fear in his eyes as he replied, "I'm fine. Thank you, Brother Wang."

At the same time, he made a hand seal, and his giant sword rose up into the air above his head, where it released a burst of radiant crimson light that conjured up countless streaks of crimson sword qi, forming an enormous sword array that began revolving incessantly around him.

At the same time, the crimson shield behind him transformed into a thick crimson light barrier around his entire body in case of further sneak attacks.

"Silver Fox may only be an early-High Zenith cultivator, but his powers are nothing to be scoffed at. Otherwise, he wouldn't have been able to avoid capture for all these years, so do be careful, Brother Gongshu," the thin man cautioned.

At the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air to release an azure bamboo tube immortal treasure, which transformed into a cylindrical azure light barrier around him.

The red-haired man nodded in response, and any complacency in his heart had been completely erased.

Right at this moment, the black-robed young man's mocking voice rang out.

"Gongshu Tian, I heard that you're supposed to be the number one prodigy of the Gongshu Clan and a renowned figure even in the Immortal Prison. Is this all of you've got? You have to rely on your companion to protect you? How disappointing..."

His voice was reverberating throughout the entire surrounding space, making it impossible to pinpoint where it was coming from.

A furious look appeared on the red-haired man's face, but he then took a deep breath and paid no heed to the taunts being directed at him.

"Even my spirit domain is unable to detect Silver Fox's presence. What type of law power has he mastered?" he asked through voice transmission while scouring his surroundings.

"I'm not sure. I've heard that he possesses a powerful spatial treasure that can allow him to fuse as one with space itself, making it impossible to track him down using spiritual sense or spirit domains. Having said that, it's not entirely impossible to determine his location," the thin man replied.

A hint of realization instantly appeared in the red-haired man's eyes upon hearing this.

All of a sudden, a burst of azure light emerged over the thin man's body, and it spread outward to form an azure spirit domain that stacked on top of the surrounding crimson spirit domain.

Immediately thereafter, he made a hand seal, and a series of azure tornados instantly emerged within the azure spirit domain.

The red-haired man also sprang into action, chanting an incantation, and a series of pillars of crimson fire rose up within his spirit domain, quickly intertwining with the azure tornados.

The fiery pillars quickly fused with the azure tornados, and the flames reared up significantly as the entire crimson spirit domain brightened by severalfold, but no change could be observed in the azure spirit domain.

However, all of the swirling crimson flames were obstructing everyone's view while also keeping out the spiritual sense of the bystanders, and everyone was quite disappointed to see this.

For the vast majority of the bystanders, witnessing High Zenith cultivators in battle was an extremely precious learning experience, but it seemed that the spectacle had become inaccessible, at least for now.

A hint of disappointment also flashed through Han Li's eyes, and a contemplative look appeared on his face as he thought back to the instant that the crimson sword projection had been shifted to the side.

He hadn't managed to catch a clear glimpse of the process the first time, but if he could see it a few more times, then he was confident that he would be able to make sense of what had happened.

This was clearly a very advanced use of one's spiritual sense, and if he could master it, he would have another potent weapon that he could use in battle.

Inside the crimson spirit domain, the red-haired man made a hand seal, and the crimson flames within the spirit domain instantly began to churn violently, then converged to form a giant white fireball that resembled a scorching sun hanging in mid-air.

A terrifying fiery law aura was emanating from the white sun, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

The red-haired man's complexion was slightly pale, clearly indicating that this was a very taxing ability for him to unleash, and he chanted an incantation while abruptly making a grabbing motion with one hand.

Countless strands of white light instantly shot out of the white sun, then pierced through the space down below in a flash.

The strands of white light were extremely fast, and they instantly permeated throughout the entire crimson spirit domain.

"There he is!"

The red-haired man's eyes suddenly lit up as he switched to a different hand seal, and countless strands of white light suddenly stretched taut as they dragged the black-robed young man out of thin air.

Those strands of white light were wrapped around his body, and there was a surprised look on his face.

"Die!" the thin man roared as he swept a sleeve through the air, sending an azure badge hurtling toward the black-robed young man.

A dull thud rang out as the azure badge transformed into an azure beastly projection with the head of a snake and the body of a tiger mid-flight, then opened its mouth up wide as it pounced at the black-robed young man.

The aura emanating from this projection was far more formidable than that of the thin man himself, and it was almost at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage.

A grim look appeared on the black-robed young man's face as he hurriedly made a hand seal, and two bursts of bright silver light appeared in his eyes before quickly spreading over his entire body.

Immediately thereafter, his body exploded into countless specks of silver light that dissipated in all directions.

As a result, the azure beastly projection missed its target, and it let loose a frustrated roar before quickly reverting back to the same azure badge from before, except this time, the azure light emanating from it had dimmed significantly.

Meanwhile, the specks of silver light converged in the distance to form Silver Fox's body once again, but his appearance had changed drastically.

His hair had turned silver, as had his previously black pupils. His ears had elongated drastically, and a layer of silver fur had emerged over them.

Wisps of misty silver light were revolving around him, giving him a rather indistinct and mysterious appearance.

The thin man's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he drew his azure badge back to himself while sweeping a sleeve through the air to release an antiquated azure mirror.

As soon as the mirror appeared, a burst of azure light instantly flashed over its surface, and it swelled to the size of a house in the blink of an eye.

Countless azure runes surged out of the mirror, then transformed into balls of azure light.

At the same time, the thin man opened his mouth to release a ball of azure light, which intertwined with all of the balls of azure light, instantly transforming them into giant blades of azure wind with arcs of azure lightning flashing over them.

All of the blades of wind swept toward Silver Fox with incredible speed and tremendous power, while the red-haired man made a hand seal, and a second flurry of strands of white light erupted out of the white sun before hurtling toward Silver Fox as well.

A disdainful sneer appeared on Silver Fox's face, and a burst of silver light flashed over his body before transforming into several dozen silver figures, all of which appeared to be clones of himself.

These silver figures darted away in all directions, leaving trails of afterimages in their wake, and the blades of azure wind instantly swept through them, but were unable to inflict any damage at all.

The strands of white light were also completely ineffective as they pierced through the silver figures.

"You two aren't half bad, but I've spent enough time playing with you. I still have things I need to do, so I'll be leaving now. See you never!"

Silver Fox's mocking voice rang out once again as the silver figures abruptly sped up while continuing to dart away, and they seemed to be completely unaffected by the two surrounding spirit domains.

"You're not getting away!" the thin man roared as he flew into the air, appearing above the antiquated azure mirror while making a hand seal, then opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence that fused into the mirror.

The mirror instantly lit up as a vast expanse of azure radiance surged forth from within. It was as if it had been set alight, and it took on a semi-transparent appearance before fusing into the azure spirit domain in a flash.

The entire azure spirit domain instantly transformed into an enormous azure mirror surface, and bursts of translucent azure light surged out of the mirror while giving off peculiar law power fluctuations.

All of the silver figures were instantly rooted to the spot, and at the same time, the thin man switched to a different hand seal before thrusting both of his palms down toward the mirror surface.

Countless translucent azure threads shot out of the azure mirror surface before piercing through the silver figures, and this time, they were finally able to harm those silver figures, which dissipated one after another until there was only a single one left.

Chapter 620: Spectating

"Now, Brother Gongshu!" the thin man yelled.

At this point, his complexion had paled significantly, and his arms were trembling as he pressed the palms of his hands down onto the mirror surface, clearly indicating that he was severely exerting himself.

Gongshu Tian began to chant a rapid incantation, then made a grabbing motion with both hands before dragging them downward, and a layer of white flames emerged over the white sun that was hovering in mid-air, which came crashing down upon the silver figure.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the white sun exploded to inundate the silver figure with radiant white light, which also filled the entire spirit domain.

A burst of unfathomably formidable law power fluctuations erupted out of the explosion before spreading through the surrounding area, and countless rifts instantly began to appear in the nearby space.

The azure mirror surface instantly vanished and reverted back to an azure spirit domain, but in the face of this burst of formidable law power fluctuation, the azure spirit domain quickly disintegrated as well.

After destroying the azure spirit domain, the burst of law power fluctuations struck the crimson spirit domain, and Gongshu Jiu let loose a fierce roar as he held the crimson spirit domain together with all his might.

If he couldn't contain the power of this explosion, then at least half of the entirety of Jade Gathering City was going to be razed to the ground.

A few seconds later, the law power fluctuations finally subsided, and the radiant white light that filled the entire spirit domain also faded.

At this moment, Gongshu Jiu's complexion was looking deathly pale, but there was an elated look in his eyes as he withdrew his crimson spirit domain before casting his gaze toward the silver figure.

That white sun was something that had been conjured up by the combination of his and his companion's law powers. Even though their law powers weren't perfectly compatible with each other's, that attack was still comparable in power to an all-out blow from a late-High Zenith cultivator.

Silver Fox was only at the early-High Zenith Stage, so there was no way that he would've been able to survive a direct strike from the white sun. Having said that, Gongshu Jiu was hoping that Silver Fox's body wasn't too severely damaged. Otherwise, there would be insufficient proof that he had actually completed his mission.

As the spirit domains and the dense wall of fire faded, a stir immediately began to run through the crowd of bystanders. At this point, even more people had gathered around the scene, and they were all staring intently at the epicenter of the explosion.

Before long, the white light had completely faded, and a charred black body was revealed on the ground.

However, as soon as Gongshu Tian caught sight of the body, his smile instantly stiffened. As it turned out, the body belonged to his companion.

At this moment, his entire body was charred black and riddled with cracks, but there was no longer any blood flowing out of those gashes. He resembled a burned rucksack, and the only silver lining was that he was still breathing, albeit very faintly.

"Senior Martial Brother Wang!" Gongshu Tian exclaimed, then immediately rushed over to the thin man's side before flipping a hand over to summon a pair of talismans, one green and one red.

Both talismans were giving off astonishing spiritual power and law power fluctuations, indicating that they had to be very precious talismans, but in this urgent situation, Gongshu Tian put them to use without any hesitation.

The two talismans lit up at his behest, then vanished into the thin man's body as two balls of light, one green and one red.

The thin man's charred body instantly began to revert from black to red, and all of the gashes on his body also began to heal, while his aura was also steadily recovering.

Gongshu Tian was very relieved to see this, but all of a sudden, he turned his attention to the spot where the thin man had been standing just a moment ago, and it was Silver Fox who was standing there instead.

His hands were clasped together in a seal in front of his chest, and they were releasing blinding silver light.

All of a sudden, Silver Fox undid his hand seal, and the silver light immediately faded, revealing a faint smile on his face.

Meanwhile, the purple-robed cultivator remained at the exact same spot as before with his hands still clasped behind his back. His clothes were completely spotless and undamaged, and he hadn't been affected by the battle that had just taken place around him at all.

He turned to take a glance at Silver Fox and the two immortal envoys, then quickly looked away again.

All of the bystanders were astonished to see this.

It seemed like Silver Fox had taken on two immortal envoys at once and come out on top!

"I can't believe you've mastered the laws of illusion to such an advanced degree!" Gongshu Tian exclaimed with a stunned and furious expression.

He then scooped up the thin man's body from the ground before flying back in retreat.

"Did I say you could leave?" Silver Fox asked as he raised a hand, and his fingertip began to glow with bright silver light.

Right at this moment, a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted overhead, and a bolt of five-colored lightning appeared before crashing down upon Silver Fox at an astonishing speed.

Silver Fox immediately darted back in retreat with an alarmed expression, but the bolt of five-colored lightning was too fast for him to evade, and it wrapped itself around his raised left arm as if it were a living creature.

A dull thump rang out as Silver Fox's arm was snapped into pieces before being incinerated into ashes, but at the same time, he had retreated to over a thousand feet away.

However, the bolt of five-colored lightning wasn't done there, and it shot forth in hot pursuit before attempting to strike other parts of Silver Fox's body.

A cold look appeared on Silver Fox's face as he swept his right arm through the air, and a translucent chain shot out of his glabella, instantly diverting the bolt of lightning to the side so that it glanced past him before burrowing into the ground.

A bottomless hole was instantly punched into the ground with plumes of smoke billowing out of it.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up with intrigue upon seeing this.

This was the second time that Silver Fox had unleashed this spirit sense secret technique.

Immediately thereafter, Silver Fox darted back another thousand or so feet, then opened his mouth to release a burst of crimson light that fell upon his left shoulder, where his arm had been severed.

A series of crimson threads instantly shot out of his shoulder, then rapidly intertwined to form a new arm, following which he looked up into the sky, where a figure emerged amid a flash of five-colored lightning.

It was an enormous middle-aged man who was almost twice the height of the average grown man. His skin was bronze in color, and his facial features were so sharp and angular that they looked as if they had been chiseled out of stone.

He was wearing a suit of golden armor, indicating that he was also an immortal envoy.

"Su Liu!" Silver Fox spat through gritted teeth.

"That's Immortal Envoy Su Liu!" Daoist Master Jingyang exclaimed with a surprised expression.

"Immortal Envoy Su Liu? Is he the immortal envoy stationed in Jade Gathering City?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. Immortal Envoy Su Liu is at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage. I don't think Silver Fox will be able to get away this time," Daoist Master Jingyang sighed.

"Silver Fox is a wanted fugitive of the Heavenly Court, while you're a deputy mountain master of the Hundred Creations Mountain, which is affiliated with the Heavenly Court, so why is it that you seem rather concerned that Silver Fox is going to be captured?" Han Li asked.

Daoist Master Jingyang shuddered slightly upon hearing this, and he hurriedly looked around, but much to his relief, everyone's attention was currently focused on Su Liu, so no one had overheard their conversation.

"Please don't make such damning jokes, Fellow Daoist Li. If someone from the Heavenly Court overhears you, I'll be in a world of trouble," Daoist Master Jingyang implored through voice transmission.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Jingyang, I've already cast a soundproofing restriction around us, so no one would've been able to overhear our conversation. I'm not so careless that I would discuss such sensitive matters without taking the necessary precautions," Han Li replied with an amused smile.

Daoist Master Jingyang faltered slightly upon hearing this, then looked around to discover that there was indeed a barely visible restriction around them, a discovery that left him feeling both relieved and astonished.

The two of them had been standing so close to each other, yet Han Li had cast this restriction completely without his detection, indicating that Han Li was most likely even more powerful than he anticipated.

Meanwhile, a wary look appeared in Silver Fox's eyes as he conjured up dozens of identical silver figures once again, all of whom fled in different directions.

"Why are you in such a hurry to get away?" Su Liu sneered as he reached out with both hands, and dozens of arcs of five-colored lightning instantly shot out of his fingertips before hurtling toward those silver figures.

The silver figures were extremely fast, but those arcs of lightning were even faster, and they caught up to the silver figures in a flash before wrapping themselves around them.

Immediately thereafter, the arcs of lightning exploded violently to eradicate all of the silver figures in the blink of an eye, leaving only one behind.

That final silver figure was Silver Fox's true body, and he was in the process of fleeing the scene.

A cold sneer appeared on Su Liu's face as he brought his fingers together, and the arcs of five-colored lightning instantly converged to form four five-colored lightning dragons, each of which was over a hundred feet in length.

The four lightning dragons swooped down before appearing directly above Silver Fox in the blink of an eye, then pounced on him at an astonishing speed.

A burst of tremendous power erupted out of the lightning dragons' bodies to significantly hamper Silver Fox's speed, and his expression changed drastically as he hurriedly made a string of hand seals.

Several spiritual sense chains shot out of his glabella in a flash, and four lightning dragons were diverted ever so slightly to create a small opening.

Silver Fox's eyes immediately lit up as he darted through the opening, but right at this moment, an earth-shattering boom rang out, and an enormous ball of radiant five-colored lightning emerged.

Thick arcs of five-colored lightning flashed through the air, instantly eradicating everything that they came into contact with, and the ball of lightning was like an all-devouring giant beast.

However, in the instant that the ball of five-colored lightning appeared, Silver Fox shot out from within, looking rather disheveled.

His complexion had paled even further, his clothes were in tatters, and a series of charred gashes had appeared over his body, but they weren't severe injuries.

All of a sudden, he turned around and yelled, "I did tell you not to get involved, but you can't just stand there and do nothing but watch!"

Chapter 621: It's Him

Su Liu took a glance at the purple-robed cultivator upon hearing this, and his expression changed ever so slightly, but he continued with what he was doing without pause as the ball of five-colored lightning split back up into four lightning dragons at his behest before hurtling toward Silver Fox.

Silver Fox was clearly quite apprehensive of these lightning dragons, and bright silver light erupted out of his body as he rushed toward the purple-robed cultivator, leaving a trail of afterimages in his wake.

"Alright, but let's make this clear: you're asking for my help, so after this, I don't owe you anything anymore," the purple-robed cultivator said with a faint smile, and his voice indicated that he was a man.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this. The purple-robed cultivator's voice struck him with a sense of familiarity.

"Fine!" Silver Fox snapped as he drew to a halt beside the purple-robed cultivator, who rubbed his hands together, and bright purple light surged out of his body before forming a vast cloud of purple radiance.

A burst of formidable devilish qi fluctuations erupted out of the purple light, and Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this.

Not only was this burst of devilish qi tremendously powerful, it was also exceptionally pure, far more so than the devilish qi that he released while unleashing his Provenance True Devil Arts.

The purple light rippled slightly, then immediately swept back toward the purple-robed cultivator to form a huge purple projection with three heads and six arms behind him.

The projection's three heads were all different from one another. One of the heads had a single horn with a furious look on its face, another wore a flame-shaped helmet with its eyes shut, seemingly in a state of slumber, while the final head wore a sympathetic expression with a vertical eye on its forehead.

In fact, all three heads had a vertical eye on each of their foreheads, but at this moment, these eyes were tightly shut.

The six arms were also all wielding different weapons, and right at this moment, the purple-robed cultivator's sleeves rolled up on their own to reveal a fine layer of purple scales on the skin of his arms.

A hint of recognition flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he murmured to himself, "It's him..."

The purple-robed cultivator was most likely Shi Chuankong, the man that he had met back in Primordial Origin City.

At this moment, the purple scales on his arms were also glowing brightly as a series of purple veins spread over his entire body, and he swelled to several times his original size. Originally, he had a tall and slender build, but his body became extremely muscular and imposing, and a series of devilish patterns had appeared over his skin, while his eyes had also turned a dark purple color.

An enormous aura erupted out of his body, but it was only at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage.

He made a hand seal to release two beams of purple light into the devilish projection behind him, and the projection's horned head suddenly began to glow brightly, while the vertical eye on its forehead also sprang open.

A beam of silver light shot out of the vertical eye, giving off incredible formidable spatial law power fluctuations that caused the nearby space to ripple incessantly.

The silver light then instantly vanished into thin air, and in the next instant, a ball of bright silver light appeared behind Silver Fox before transforming into a swirling silver vortex.

The four lightning dragons converged onto the scene, but the silver vortex abruptly expanded to encompass the lightning dragons, and in the next instant, the lightning dragons and the silver vortex vanished in unison.

A hint of surprise appeared on Su Liu's face upon seeing this, and right at this moment, a silver vortex suddenly appeared behind him.

The four lightning dragons shot out of the vortex, catching him completely off guard and striking him on the back to send him flying forward with tremendous force.

"Bravo! Su Liu's really shot himself in the foot there!" Silver Fox chortled with glee.

"We have to get out of here. Su Liu is not someone that we can take on right now," the purple-robed cultivator said as he made a hand seal, and the purple projection behind him wrapped its six arms around him and Silver Fox, then fled into the distance as a ball of radiant purple light.

"Get back here!"

A thunderous roar of fury rang out as arcs of five-colored lightning instantly spread through the surrounding area to form a lightning spirit domain that encompassed the purple lightning within it.

The lightning spirit domain was virtually substantial in form, and once again, it obstructed the view of all of the bystanders.

Arcs of five-colored lightning converged from all parts of the spirit domain, lashing viciously against the ball of purple light like whips.

The ball of purple light rippled violently, and it was being rapidly whittled down by the relentless lightning strikes.

All of a sudden, Su Liu appeared at the center of the lightning spirit domain.

The armor on his back was damaged, revealing a large section of his bronze-colored skin, but he was clearly unscathed.

However, he seemed to have been infuriated by the fact that his own attack had been used against him, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which all of the five-colored lightning in the spirit domain converged to form a giant ax.

Bursts of thunderous rumbling erupted out of the ax, and a tremendously fearsome aura spread through the entire surrounding area.

Su Liu raised an arm before bringing it down again in a swift and forceful motion, and the lightning ax came crashing down with unmatched power, tearing through the nearby space as it descended upon the ball of purple light.

Almost at the exact same moment, a giant crimson sword the size of a mountain came hurtling forth from afar, and wrapped around it was an enormous fiery wyrm projection that was giving off tremendous fire law power fluctuations.

The crimson sword wasn't as powerful as the lightning ax, but it was certainly nothing to be scoffed at, and it was also leaving a spatial rift in its wake as it swept toward the ball of purple light.

The sword had come from none other than Gongshu Tian, and at this point, the thin man had also regained consciousness, but he was still yet to recover from his injuries, so he refrained from entering the fray.

Right at this moment, a burst of bright silver light suddenly appeared within the ball of purple light, then quickly spread outward to form a silver spirit domain.

The spirit domain had only just taken shape before both the lightning ax and the giant sword arrived, and the silver spirit domain immediately began to warp and twist.

All of the surrounding space within a radius of several thousand feet also began to twist and elongate, and the lightning ax and the giant sword were swept up by the twisted space, diverting them away from their original trajectories.

As a result, they glanced past the silver spirit domain, then clashed against each other with a an earth-shattering boom.

The silver spirit domain also dimmed significantly, indicating that it had been severely exerted. However, at the same time, it rapidly elongated into the shape of a spear, then pierced into space and vanished without a trace in the blink of an eye.

Almost at the exact same moment, the azure light shuddered violently before a cracking sound rang out from inside, it exploded into countless specks of azure light that quickly dissipated.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and all Su Liu and Gongshu Tian saw were a few flashes of silver light before Silver Fox and the purple-robed cultivator vanished out of sight.

"Shit!" Gongshu Tian cursed to himself with a frustrated look on his face, and the thin man was also looking far from pleased.

Su Liu's brows were slightly furrowed, and the fury in his eyes slowly abated as the giant lightning ax faded at his behest.

"Fellow Daoist Su, your laws of lightning were the perfect counter to Silver Fox! If the three of us had joined forces from the very beginning, Silver Fox wouldn't have gotten away, and Brother Wang wouldn't have been injured, either!" Gongshu Tian said as he turned to Su Liu.

"Are you questioning me?" Su Liu asked as he turned to Gongshu Tian with a cold expression.

Gongshu Tian's expression stiffened slightly, and the tone of his voice softened a little as he replied, "No, I'm just stating the facts. The three of us were assigned the mission of capturing Silver Fox, yet now, not only has he gotten away, he's taken the Myriad Soul Herb as well. How are we going to answer to our higher-ups?"

Su Liu took a glance at the severely ravaged inner city, then at the people in the cage on the flying boat, and he sneered, "Capturing Silver Fox is your mission, I was only instructed to help you.

“I did everything I needed to do, and it's up to you to think about how to answer to our higher-ups. As for everyone on that boat, they're all esteemed guests who came to attend the Jade Kun Pavilion auction, so you'd better think carefully about what you want to do with them."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he withdrew his lightning spirit domain, then vanished from the spot before Gongshu Tian had a chance to say anything.

With the lightning spirit domain gone, Gongshu Tian and the thin man were revealed to everyone.

At this point, an enormous crowd of bystanders had gathered at the scene, and the two immortal envoys clearly weren't very pleased with all the attention.

Gongshu Tian gave a cold harrumph, and the two immortal envoys promptly departed as two streaks of light.

The flying boat beside them also flew away after them, while the people in the cage were dumped out in a rather unceremonious fashion.

All of the freed cultivators were extremely relieved, and they immediately departed, as did the crowd of bystanders.

"Judging from their expressions, it seems that they failed to capture Silver Fox," Han Li remarked as he watched the departing the immortal envoys.

At the same time, the thought of Shi Chuankong flashed through his mind.

It seemed that the three-headed projection that he had conjured up was somehow related to the Provenance True Devil Arts, and on top of that, he had also mastered the laws of space.

It was a real pity that Su Liu's lightning spirit domain had obstructed everyone's view and prevented him from seeing the final moments of the battle.

"The fun's over now, so let's get out of here, Fellow Daoist Li. I don't think it would be wise to linger here," Daoist Master Jingyang urged.

"Sorry to keep you waiting, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. Let's go," Han Li agreed.

Chapter 622: Flower, Bird, Fish, Insect

At the center of Jade Gathering City was a white pagoda that stretched all the way up into the clouds.

All of a sudden, Su Liu appeared in a side hall within the pagoda, and beside him was a white-robed young man who was seated in a chair, sipping on some spirit tea.

Upon spotting Su Liu, he remained seated as he remarked, "You intentionally let those two get away, didn't you?"

Su Liu took an indifferent glance at the white-robed man, then asked, "You saw everything?"

"That man in purple had spatial law powers up his sleeve, but with your powers, you were perfectly capable of preventing him from getting away. Why did you do that? Those old geezers aren't as easy to fool as Gongshu Tian. If the higher-ups find out about this, it could be bad for you," the white-robed man said.

"That man's identity is quite sensitive, so capturing him would've spelled far more trouble. Even if the higher-ups find out about this, they won't blame me for what I did," Su Liu replied.

"Oh? Who is he?" the white-robed man asked with a surprised expression.

"He's from the Vast Origin House," Su Liu repiled.

The surprise in the white-robed man's eyes became even more pronounced upon hearing this, and he asked, "Are you sure?"

"I know what I'm doing," Su Liu assured.

"Then what about Silver Fox? He's a renowned fugitive on the Immortal Slaying List. You could've easily captured Silver Fox while letting his companion go," the white-robed man said.

Su Liu's expression darkened slightly in the face of the white-robed man's persistent questioning, and he said, "I told you that I know what I'm doing. I have my reasons for letting Silver Fox go. Everything will become clear to you in the future."

The white-robed man could see that he wasn't going to be able to get an answer out of Su Liu, so he could only shake his head with a wry smile.

......

In a certain secret chamber in Jade Gathering City.

"What a farce that turned out to be! After what just happened, who's going to dare to attend the Jade Kun Pagoda auction in the future? I'll be sure to report this matter to my superiors. If worse comes to worst, we'll just have to cancel our collaboration with the Black Mountain Immortal Palace. Otherwise, the reputation of our Hundred Creations Mountain will be swept to the ground sooner or later!" Daoist Master Jingyang grumbled.

"Don't get so worked up, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. You were never all that interested in overseeing affairs related to the auction anyway, so why not just return to your life of relaxation in the Leisure Valley and leave this to someone else?" Han Li chuckled.

Despite his relaxed and casual facade, internally, there was a great deal of lingering fear in his heart. If he had outbid Silver Fox for that Myriad Soul Herb during the auction, he would've been the one detained by the Immortal Palace.

"I'm afraid the Leisure Valley is also no longer the place it used to be," Daoist Master Jingyang sighed.

"Let's not discuss these vexing matters anymore. How about we take a look at the beast bone that you purchased at the auction?" Han Li proposed.

"Fellow Daoist Li, why does it feel to me like you're more of a businessman than you are a pill refinement master?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Which cultivator isn't a calculating businessman?" Han Li countered with an amused smile.

"I suppose you're right," Daoist Master Jingyang sighed with a wry smile.

With that, he flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized octagonal box, then pressed his palm down onto the center of the box, upon which the box immediately split open into eight triangular pieces that resembled the petals of a flower.

Han Li stood off to the side with blue light flashing in his eyes, intently observing all of the spirit patterns on the octagonal box, as well as every single motion that Daoist Master Jingyang performed.

Daoist Master Jingyang laid the octagonal box upside-down onto the ground, then joined his index and middle fingers before pressing down them toward the box, only to suddenly stop what he was doing.

Han Li could see what he was thinking, and he jibed, "What? Are you feeling apprehensive about showing me how to open this treasure? Setting aside the fact that I have no idea what you're doing, even if I did, where could I possibly find an identical spatial treasure to this one?"

"You're right," Daoist Master Jingyang chuckled with a self-deprecating expression. "To be honest, no advanced techniques are required to open this treasure. It's just that the process is very specific, and not many people in the Hundred Creations Mountain are willing to learn it as they'll most likely never get to use it anyway."

"How did the Hundred Creations Mountain find out this method then?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Daoist Master Jingyang hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then explained, "Earlier, I told you that this beast bone is a spatial treasure, but that's actually not correct. Strictly speaking, it's actually a domain treasure."

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, and the Domain Bead instantly sprang into his mind. [1]

The Domain Bead was the most prized artifact of the Space Fish Race, an exceptional treasure capable of housing even mountains and seas. If this beast bone were also a treasure of the same nature, then it would truly be a priceless treasure.

Unfortunately, Han Li was unable to bring the Domain Bead with him during his ascension to the True Immortal Realm, so he could only leave it in the Spirit Realm.

"In contrast with normal spatial treasures, domain treasures often have larger internal spaces, and the world's origin qi inside can circulate freely, so even living beings can survive inside, making it perfect for raising spirit plants and spirit beasts," Daoist Master Jingyang explained.

Han Li was naturally already aware of the distinction between the two types of treasures, but he still nodded in response.

"In the immortal regions, domain treasures are often extremely expensive, but they're not exactly rare. If I were to purchase one through my connections in the Hundred Creations Mountain, then I could do so with ease, so do you know why I was so eager to acquire this particular domain treasure?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked with a hint of excitement in his eyes.

"How could I know the answer to that?" Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"This beast bone is called the Fish Branch, and it was created by the third mountain master of our Hundred Creations Mountain, Jie Jinyuan. This is one of a set of four domain treasures that he crafted, and the other three are the Flower Branch, the Bird Branch, and the Insect Branch, collectively known as the Four Branches. With this branch recovered, only the Flower Branch is still lost," Daoist Master Jingyang explained.

"That's a set of rather romantic names. This third mountain master must've been quite an interesting person," Han Li remarked with a smile.

"Our third mountain master had the strangest personality out of all of our past mountain masters, but he's also the one most revered by the disciples of our Hundred Creations Mountain, second only to our founder.

“It was said that he had always possessed exceptional aptitude in tool refinement, and even back when he was a disciple, he was constantly coming up with new and innovative ideas. For that, he was often denounced as lackadaisical and unfocused by the elders.

“However, he later went on to catch the eye of the second mountain master, who took him under his wing, and ultimately, he became an exceptional mountain master," Daoist Master Jingyang said with a smile.

"Where do these strange names come from? And how is this Fish Branch supposed to be opened?" Han Li asked.

"I already told you that our third mountain master had a very strange personality, so who knows how he decided on these names? Perhaps it was simply on a whim. I can see that you're eager to see what's inside this Fish Branch, so I won't waste any more time," Daoist Master Jingyang chuckled, then began to engrave a small array onto the ground around the octagonal box.

After that, he pulled out the Fish Branch before placing it onto the upside-down octagonal box.

"I didn't think the process would be so complicated," Han Li remarked with slightly furrowed brows.

"If it wasn't complicated, that clueless Golden Immortal would've already opened it," Daoist Master Jingyang replied.

"That's true," Han Li said with a nod.

"The array that I've engraved onto the ground is called the Eight Origins Unraveling Array. Following the demise of their original owner, some domain treasures cannot be opened by anyone else, and the only way to reopen such a domain treasure would be refine it using this array, after which one will be able to open and close the treasure at will like a storage ring," Daoist Master Jingyang explained.

"I see."

"Alright, I have to focus now, so don't distract me," Daoist Master Jingyang said as a serious look appeared on his face.

Han Li immediately made his way to the side of the room, where he continued to observe in silence.

Meanwhile, Daoist Master Jingyang began to make a hand seal while silently chanting an incantation.

Through observing his lips, Han Li was able to get a rough idea of what he was chanting, but this was clearly not a reliable method to learn the incantation, and with that in mind, Han Li's brows became slightly furrowed.

Moments later, Daoist Master Jingyang raised a finger to release a beam of white light into the beast bone, and a layer of resplendent silver light instantly appeared over its surface, then spread over the entire bone, while a golden fish design roughly the size of a copper coin appeared on the tip of the bone.

"Please wait a moment while I refine this treasure, and after that, we'll be able to open it," Daoist Master Jingyang said to Han Li as he picked up the Fish Branch.

Han Li was still pondering the incantation that he had just extrapolated, and he nodded silently in response.

Daoist Master Jingyang sat down with his legs crossed, then brought his palms together with the bone clasped between them to commence the refinement process.

Only after around six hours had passed did he rise to his feet. At this point, he was sweating profusely, and it seemed that he had just severely exerted himself.

Despite his weary expression, his eyes were glowing with joy, and he smiled as he declared, "It's time to reap the spoils, Fellow Daoist Li."

"I'm excited to see what's inside," Han Li replied with a smile of his own.

Daoist Master Jingyang swept a hand over the Fish Branch, and all of a sudden, it became completely transparent, while the bright silver light that was emanating from it transformed into a door of light that was around ten feet tall.

A glimmer of green could be seen within the door of light, and a gentle breeze was also blowing out of it.

"Come on in, Fellow Daoist Li," Daoist Master Jingyang invited, then stepped into the door of light, disappearing out of sight.

[1]. For more information on the Domain Bead, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2304: Domain Bead.

[Back]

Chapter 623: Island on a Lake

Han Li briefly inspected the door of light, then also stepped into it behind Daoist Master Jingyang.

As soon as he did so, he immediately found himself standing above a vast body of water, and the surrounding environment was filled with clean and refreshing air.

After inhaling a lungful of fresh air, he inspected his surroundings to find that the body of water down below was several dozen kilometers wide, so it could be referred to as a small lake.

Further in the distance around the lake was a vast expanse of mist that perhaps led to somewhere else, or perhaps they signified the boundaries of this space.

At the very center of the lake was a round island that was filled with lush greenery, and at the center of the island was an intricate courtyard with white walls and black roof tiles.

Han Li and Daoist Master Jingyang were hovering in the air above the lake, and they could see schools of plump golden carp swimming and playing through the water in a joyful manner.

"I didn't think that there would be such an abundance of spiritual qi in this domain," Han Li praised.

"Indeed, this place isn't inferior to some of the secret areas that are closely guarded by major sects. I can see that there are at least two spirit springs in this lake. It seems like legends about the third mountain master are true. He really was a genius far beyond fools like myself," Daoist Master Jingyang sighed, then picked up his wine gourd before taking a long swig.

"Why do you always speak of him in the past tense, Fellow Daoist Jingyang? Is he no longer the mountain master of the Hundred Creations Mountain?" Han Li asked while appreciating the beautiful scenery around him.

"Indeed. The third mountain master is nothing more than a legendary figure of the past now. Our current mountain master is the fifth mountain master," Daoist Master Jingyang sighed.

As the two of them were speaking, they had already glided through the air to the small island at the heart of the lake.

Upon reaching the island, they were immediately greeted by the sound of pleasant birdsong and the sweet fragrance of flowers. The two of them made their way down a small pebble path on the island deep into the forest, and they quickly arrived at the black and white courtyard.

To the front left of the courtyard was a small spirit field, around which was a purple light barrier, and there were various types of different spirit plants and spirit medicines growing inside.

Daoist Master Jingyang's eyes lit up slightly as he approached the spirit field. The light barrier hadn't been maintained for countless years, and he was able to dispel it with ease before turning back Han Li as he asked, "Fellow Daoist Li, you're a pill refinement master, so I'm sure you recognize everything in here, right?"

Han Li stepped into the spirit field, then swept his gaze over the surrounding spirit plants, and his eyes immediately lit up slightly as he replied, "Almost all of the spirit plants in this field are over a hundred thousand years old, particularly those Nine-leaf Cornelian Cherries and that Ink Fragrance Herb. They're at a perfect age to be used, and they're an exceptionally rare find."

"I knew I could count on you, Fellow Daoist Li. In accordance with our prior agreement, you can pick out a third of the spirit plants in here. If you think that's not enough, I can sell some to you in Immortal Origin Stones as repayment for the debt that I owe you," Daoist Master Jingyang said.

"Could it be that back when you were borrowing money from me, you had already thought of the idea of repaying me using the treasures in this domain treasure? As expected of a shrewd businessman of the Hundred Creations Mountain, your foresight is truly outstanding," Han Li praised.

"You're mistaken, Fellow Daoist Li. The main reason why I decided to purchase this Fish Branch for such a steep price is due to its ties with our sect. As for what's going to be in it, that's nothing more than a blind gamble for me. After all, there's no way for me to tell if someone else has already accessed this space before this Fish Branch fell into the hands of that Golden Immortal," Daoist Master Jingyang replied.

"I can't allow you to repay this favor so easily, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. I'll stick by our original agreement and pick out only a third of the spirit plants here. As for the Immortal Origin Stones that you owe me, you can repay me over time," Han Li said with a smile, then began to pick out the spirit plants that he wanted from the field.

Meanwhile, Daoist Master Jingyang had already opened the restriction on the gate of the courtyard, but he didn't make his way inside on his own. Instead, he stood by the entrance while sipping on wine and appreciating the surrounding scenery, seemingly not in a hurry at all.

Only after Han Li had secured the spirit plants that he wanted did the two of them make their way into the courtyard together.

In contrast with the average immortal abode, the layout of this courtyard was more similar to what one would expect to see in a mortal courtyard.

Around a dozen paces away from the entrance stood a white screen wall, upon which was painted a pair of carp, one black and one red. Their heads and tails were interconnected to form a ring, and there was a layer of translucent white light shimmering over the screen wall.

Han Li briefly activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and he noticed a layer of white mist that was invisible to the naked eye rising up from beneath the screen wall. Rich spiritual qi was gathering and dissipating there, and it seemed that this screen wall was the key to the entire domain treasure's operation.

After making their way around the screen wall, Han Li and Daoist Master Jingyang stepped into the first section of the courtyard, where they saw a series of puppets strewn over the ground, with their spirit cores completely spent.

Daoist Master Jingyang approached those puppets for a brief inspection, then shook his head with a disappointed look on his face.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Jingyang?" Han Li asked.

"These puppets weren't crafted by our third mountain master, and there are no signs to indicate who it was that left them here. The craftsmanship is quite remarkable, but they're nothing more than a pile of scrap metal now," Daoist Master Jingyang replied.

"According to your description, this Fish Branch has already been around for countless years, and it could've had multiple owners during that time, so there's naturally no way that everything could be preserved in their original state," Han Li said.

"That's true," Daoist Master Jingyang replied with a nod.

The two of them continued to make their way through the courtyard, and during the course of their exploration, they discovered that the former owner of this domain treasure had been an avid collector of paintings and calligraphy pieces from mortal masters.

Many of them were extremely important pieces in the world of art and calligraphy, and there was no lack of pieces from extremely renowned masters among them.

Hanging in the main hall was a piece of calligraphy from a small mortal nation that had existed in the Golden Origin Immortal Region over a hundred thousand years ago, and it had been written to pay homage to the calligrapher's ancestors.

The strokes were extremely masterful and diverse, making the characters resemble roaming ink dragons, to the point that it almost resembled an immortal talisman.

Han Li wasn't very well versed in the art of calligraphy, but even he could tell that the former owner of this place had very good taste.

Aside from these mortal pieces, there was also a secret chamber in the domain treasure that was dedicated to storing immortal artifacts, including treasures, pills, and spirit materials.

Han Li briefly examined the collection in the secret chamber to find that all of the items were of quite a high caliber, most of which could even be used by High Zenith cultivators. The two most valuable pieces among them were a crimson fan that contained fire law powers and a wooden ruler that contained time law powers.

The former had been fashioned out of the feathers of some type of spirit bird, and it contained immense fire law powers, allowing it to easily melt the average Golden Immortal Stage treasure into molten liquid.

The latter was green in color and as smooth as jade, with densely packed markings etched onto its surface. However, prior to refining the treasure, it was impossible to tell what it could be used for.

Daoist Master Jingyang's attention was immediately drawn to the fan, and he said, "Fellow Daoist Li, I recall that you were particularly interested in time-attribute treasures during the auction.

“Out of these two treasures, I think this wooden ruler suits you best, so how about you leave this fan to me? I'll admit that I've become quite lazy of late, but I'm still a tool refinement master, after all, and this fan will be of great help to me in my tool refinement endeavors."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he replied, "I only purchased that Time Severing Flagon for its ability to store spirit liquids. This wooden ruler is a treasure of an even higher caliber than the flagon, but it's not very useful to me. In contrast, this fan can also be very useful in my pill refinement."

Daoist Master Jingyang was silent for a moment, then proposed, "How about this, Fellow Daoist Li? If you leave this fan to me, you can choose an additional three items out of everything here after you've picked out your share of a third of these items?"

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he acquiesced, "Alright, we'll do as you say."

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Li," Daoist Master Jingyang hurriedly said with a grateful expression.

After that, Han Li stowed the azure wooden ruler into his storage bracelet, then collected his share of the treasures in the secret chamber.

After splitting the spoils, Daoist Master Jingyang reopened the door of light, and the two of them emerged from the domain treasure one after the other.

Upon returning to the secret chamber, Daoist Master Jingyang turned to Han Li with a smile, then suddenly said, "It's rare that I find someone that I get along so well with, Fellow Daoist Li. I have a proposal for you."

"You're not going to ask me to serve as a guest elder at your Hundred Creations Mountain again, are you?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"Precisely! This time, it's an official invitation. With your skills in pill refinement, you'll most definitely be held in very high regard in our Hundred Creations Mountain, and in exchange, you'll have access to the immense resources at our sect's disposal," Daoist Master Jingyang said with a serious expression.

"I'm afraid I'll have to turn down your kind offer once again, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. At the moment, I'm still troubled by my baleful decay, and my top priority right now is to resolve this issue," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"Have you not already obtained the Profound Zoysia Crystal? Once you've refined that pill, you'll be able to expel all of the baleful qi in your body, and the baleful decay will no longer be a concern," Daoist Master Jingyang said.

"I certainly hope so. Once I get back to the Leisure Valley, I'll be going into seclusion to refine the pill in question, and that will be my focus for the immediate future," Han Li said.

"I suppose that makes sense. I also have some matters to take care of in the wake of the auction, so let's part ways here. Once you successfully expel the baleful qi from your body, I'll open a jar of my Green Fermented Wine to celebrate," Daoist Master Jingyang said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

Han Li nodded in response, and with that, Han Li departed.

Upon returning to the inner city of Jade Gathering City, he discovered that the unrest in the wake of the recent incident had already completely subsided, and the city was still as lively and bustling as ever.

After leaving Jade Gathering City, he returned straight to the Leisure Valley.

Chapter 624: Flower Branch

Upon returning to his cave abode, Han Li paid a visit to Mo Guang, only to find that the latter was still cultivating in seclusion. Hence, he returned to his own secret chamber, then strode over to the table inside and began drawing on a sheet of paper.

Under the tip of his brush, a design of an octagonal box gradually took shape, and it appeared to be quite complex and profound.

After completing a design of one side of the box, Han Li briefly examined it before setting it aside, then pulled out another sheet of paper to continue the process.

Before long, seven or eight designs had been completed, each of which depicted the octagonal box from a different angle.

Han Li swept his gaze over the designs, then nodded with a pleased expression before pulling out yet another sheet of paper.

On this one, he replicated the array that Daoist Master Jingyang had engraved onto the ground around the octagonal box earlier.

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out from behind him.

"Is that the Eight Origins Unraveling Array?"

"You recognize this array, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked while continuing to draw the array.

A hint of befuddlement flashed through Daoist Xie's eyes, and it seemed that it was just as perplexed about how it had managed to identify the array.

"I don't know how, but I suddenly recalled the array as soon as I saw these designs," it explained.

"Could it be that some of the memories that your former owner sealed away were awakened?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not sure," Daoist Xie replied, then strode over to the table to pick up a few of the designs for a closer examination.

All of a sudden, it said, "This part isn't quite right. It needs to be adjusted, or the effect of the array will be hampered."

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he asked, "You know how this thing is made?"

"I should be able to make it as long as I have the right materials," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

It then took Han Li's brush before writing out a long list of materials onto a sheet of paper, then handed it to Han Li as it said, "If you can prepare these materials, I'll be able to craft this Eight Origins Key."

"Eight Origins Key..." Han Li murmured to himself as he read through the list of materials, and it immediately made sense to him why Daoist Master Jingyang wasn't concerned about showing him the Eight Origins Unraveling Array. If he didn't have this list of materials, he wouldn't even be able to make an Eight Origins Key.

That only made him more curious about how Daoist Xie had access to this knowledge.

However, it was clear from Daoist Xie's expression that it was just as confused as he was.

"I recall that the Eight Origins Unraveling Array is only effective on certain special domain treasures. What are you trying to open, Fellow Daoist Han?" Daoist Xie asked.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce the section of tailbone that came from the giant rat skeleton upon hearing this, and he handed the bone to Daoist Xie while observing its expression, trying to see if it displayed any reaction to the bone, but Daoist Xie's brows only furrowed slightly with befuddlement, and that was the extent of its reaction.

"Do you recognize this thing, Fellow Daoist Xie?" Han Li asked.

Daoist Xie examined the bone for a moment, then handed it back to Han Li with a shake of its head. "I wouldn't have been able to identify this object as a domain treasure at all if you hadn't told me."

"If I hadn't seen something that was identical to it in aura and appearance during the auction, I wouldn't have known that this was a domain treasure, either. Once I have these materials prepared, I'll have to trouble you to refine the key for me," Han Li said.

"I can do that," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

After that, Han Li asked some more questions about the Eight Origins Key, then left his cave abode to make another trip to Jade Gathering City.

......

Over two months later.

A small array had already been engraved onto the ground in Han Li's cave abode.

Daoist Xie was holding an octagonal box with one hand, and the box sprang open before being placed upside-down at the center of the array.

"Place your domain treasure on top of the box, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie instructed.

Han Li immediately obliged, summoning the beast bone before setting it down onto the box.

"Regarding the incantation..."

Before Han Li had a chance to finish, Daoist Xie interjected, "There's not much point in only knowing the incantation, it has to be used in conjunction with a specific method of channeling your immortal spiritual power."

"I'm assuming you know this method, right, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"Leave it to me," Daoist Xie replied with a nod, then began making a string of hand seals while silently chanting an incantation identical to the one used by Daoist Master Jingyang.

After that, a beam of white light shot out of its fingertip and into the beast bone.

A burst of green light flashed over the beast bone, followed by a burst of radiant silver light that flowed over the bone's surface like rippling water, while a flower design the size of a copper coin appeared at the end of the bone.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this.

Just as he had predicted, this was indeed the Flower Branch refined by the third mountain master of the Hundred Creations Mountain.

"The seal on this treasure has already been unraveled. All you need to do is refine it before you can open it," Daoist Xie said as it returned the bone to Han Li.

"Thank you, Brother Xie," Han Li replied with a nod, then inspected the Flower Branch momentarily before sitting down with his legs crossed.

After that, he joined his palms together with the bone held between them and began the refinement process.

Around four hours later, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open, and he wiped the sweat from his forehead before rising to his feet.

There was a hint of irrepressible elation in his eyes, and he took a glance at Daoist Xie before gently sweeping a hand over the Flower Branch.

The bone instantly shuddered before turning transparent, while the radiant silver light that it was releasing formed a door of light that was around ten feet tall.

"Why don't you come inside with me, Brother Xie?" Han Li proposed with a smile, then stepped into the door of light.

Daoist Xie was standing in front of the door of light, and it was just about to step inside as well when it suddenly stalled momentarily, then immediately returned to normal before vanishing into the door.

After entering the door of light, Han Li appeared on a spacious meadow.

He cast his gaze forward to discover a lush forest beyond the meadow, and there was faint smoke rising up from the forest, giving it a rather hazy and indistinct appearance.

Instead of immediately entering the forest, Han Li flew in a circle around the space first.

The sky in this space was only around a hundred thousand feet tall, and there was a spatial barrier beyond that altitude, preventing one from flying any higher. There were also spatial barriers surrounding the domain as well, creating invisible walls on all sides.

Through his exploration, Han Li discovered that the internal space within the Flower Branch was far larger than that of the Fish Branch, but the abundance of the world's origin qi was roughly on the same level in both domains.

Following his brief inspection, he descended into the forest with Daoist Xie, and as soon as he entered the forest, he could immediately feel the presence of faint baleful qi in the air.

On the ground in front of him was a small white path paved to form all types of strange designs, and it was extending deep into the forest in a winding fashion, seemingly leading to the source of the baleful qi.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he crouched down to give the stone path a closer inspection, upon which he discovered that it wasn't paved with white stone slabs or jade or anything like that. Instead, it was paved with human and beast bones of different sizes.

"Given this gruesome hobby, it's no wonder that rat carcass possessed such immense baleful qi," Han Li remarked.

As Han Li made his way down the bone path, the baleful qi in the forest began to diminish, and many different spirit plants appeared on either side of the path. Some of these spirit plants were familiar to Han Li, while unidentifiable, but all of them appeared to be quite advanced in age.

Instead of immediately picking these spirit plants, Han Li continued down the path until he reached a purple bamboo forest that was only several thousand feet in size.

The forest was teeming with spiritual qi, and a two-story pavilion could be seen inside. The area around the pavilion was completely devoid of baleful qi, and it resembled an immortal abode.

Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes to carefully examine the purple bamboo forest for a moment, and after making sure that there were no restrictions inside, he made his way into the forest.

After walking a few hundred meters, Han Li spotted a fenced courtyard up ahead. Upon entering the courtyard, he noticed a small pond with purple smoke swirling inside it, and at the center of the pond was a series of purplish-golden lotus flowers.

"It looks like the core of this domain treasure is this pond and these lotus flowers inside," Han Li remarked with a contemplative expression.

"That does appear to be the case," Daoist Xie agreed with a nod.

The two of them made their way over a purple bamboo arched bridge over the pond, then arrived in front of the two-story pavilion on the other side of the pond.

The entire pavilion was also constructed from purple bamboo, and its foundation seemed to be rooted to the ground. In fact, some roots could be seen burrowing into the ground from the underside of the pavilion, and it was clear from the layer of purple light around it that restrictions had been set up inside.

"This pavilion is quite remarkable. It draws upon the power of the lotus flowers in the pond, fusing as one with their roots. If we were to forcibly break this restriction, perhaps we'd be able to gain access to the pavilion, but in doing so, we'd surely damage the foundation of this domain," Han Li remarked after examining the pavilion briefly.

"That's not a problem. All we have to do is slightly modify the Nine True Spirits Technique, and we'll be able to unravel these restrictions without harming the lotus flowers," Daoist Xie said.

"It sounds like you have it all figured out. Can I count on you again, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked with a smile.

Daoist Xie nodded silently in response, then began to work on unraveling the pavilion's restrictions.

Chapter 625: Integrating the Flower Branch

A few minutes later, a faint thump rang out, and the entire purple bamboo forest shuddered slightly, following which the layer of faint purple light over the pavilion quickly receded before fading into the ground.

Only then did Daoist Xie's eyes spring open, and it proposed, "Let's go in and take a look."

With that, Han Li and Daoist Xie made their way up the staircase in front of the pavilion, then pushed the bamboo doors open.

Upon entering the bamboo pavilion, they were immediately greeted by a cool and refreshing sensation that struck them with a sense of relaxation and reinvigoration.

"This pavilion is able to draw upon the power of the lotus flowers in the pond to draw in all of the surrounding world's origin qi, resulting in a significantly heightened abundance of spiritual qi. I must say, I'm really impressed with the innovative mind of whoever created this domain," Daoist Xie suddenly praised.

"This pavilion can gather spiritual qi, but it doesn't trap it, so the circulation of the world's origin qi in the domain isn't affected. On top of that, the spiritual qi that seeps out of this pavilion will nourish the nearby bamboo forest, making this the area with the most abundant spiritual qi in the entire domain. This would be a perfect place to set up a spirit medicine garden," Han Li said.

Daoist Xie nodded in agreement.

The first floor of the bamboo building was rather barely furnished, with an antiquated scroll hanging on the wall directly opposite the entrance. A large "zen" character was inscribed onto the scroll in a rather wobbly script that resembled a piece of artwork more so than a piece of calligraphy.

At the foot of the scroll was a cushion woven out of coarse linen, and judging from the severe wear and tear that it displayed, it appeared to have been used very frequently.

To the left of the main hall was a side room, within which was a purple bamboo bed, upon which was a small square table that carried an unlit oil lamp, a black teapot, and a pair of matching teacups.

To the right of the bed was a staircase that led to the second floor of the pavilion.

On the second floor, Han Li and Daoist Xie discovered three storage cabinets, all of which were sealed using secret techniques.

After unraveling the seals, Han Li was ecstatic to discover that the first cabinet contained a huge amount of spirit medicines and spirit materials, among which were some Fire Vein Ganoderma and Jade Marrow Polygonatum that were hundreds of thousand of years old, as well large quantities of Heavenly River Stardust, Ice Soul Frost Crystals, and Nine Yang Flint.

These were the only materials that Han Li was able to identify, while the rest were all things that he had never seen or even heard of before, and he presumed that they could be used for refining certain high-grade pills and treasures.

Han Li stowed all of the materials into his storage bracelet, then moved onto the second cabinet, which contained around a dozen cultivation arts, only a small number of which were fit for human cultivators, while the vast majority were meant for demonic cultivators and other foreign cultivators.

Han Li only briefly flipped through these cultivation arts and didn't study them in any fine detail. At the moment, he was already far too busy working on his time-attribute cultivation arts and his Spirit Refinement Technique, so he had no time to look at anything else.

As for Daoist Xie, it took interest in a cultivation art by the name of the Righteous Lightning Technique, and Han Li was more than happy to let it take the cultivation art.

After stowing all those cultivation arts away as well, Han Li opened the third cabinet, and just as he had anticipated, it was filled with immortal treasures, but all of them were damaged to different extents.

One of them was a bright longsword forged out of exceptional materials, and it had most likely been a very formidable Acquired Immortal Treasure, but there was a long crack that extended all the way down the blade of the sword, much to Han Li's disappointment.

The giant rat true spirit's physical body would've been sufficient to stand up against immortal treasures, so it most likely wouldn't have required such weapons. Hence, these were most likely the spoils that it had reaped from battle.

At the bottom of the storage cabinet, Han Li discovered a gray storage pouch, and after refining the pouch and opening it, he discovered that it contained dozens of transparent crystals that contained extremely pure immortal spiritual power.

"This is a huge haul of mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones! I barely saw any of these during all my time in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region," Han Li exclaimed with an elated expression.

"Mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones are far more difficult to create than normal Immortal Origin Stones, so it's no surprise that they're extremely rare. The Northern Glacial Immortal Region didn't even have many High Zenith Stage Jade Immortals, so mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones will naturally be in very short supply there," Daoist Xie said.

"Even in the Black Mountain Immortal Region, only some major sects are in possession of mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones, and all of them are cherished like precious treasures," Han Li said.

After that, Han Li carefully examined the entire bamboo building to ensure that he wasn't missing anything, then re-emerged from the bamboo forest with Daoist Xie.

He swept a sleeve through the air to release around a dozen giant ape puppets, and they immediately sprang into action at Han Li's behest, with some of them cutting down trees, while others dug out rocks from the ground, and before long, a large plot of empty land was created.

The puppets then used the felled bamboo trees to construct a fence around the entire plot of land, following which Han Li began to set up restrictions around the fence.

He was only setting up a simple array that sucked in the spiritual qi seeping out of the nearby purple bamboo pavilion, so it didn't take him very long at all to complete it.

After that, he summoned two large vats of spirit liquid that he had prepared in advance, but had never gotten a chance to use, then gave them to two of the giant ape puppets so that they could water the garden.

"It'll take at least a few decades for the soil to absorb the spirit liquid and become a spirit field fit for growing spirit plants, so let's get out of here for now," Han Li said, then made a hand seal, and the door of silver light hovering outside the forest instantly appeared in front of him.

As the connective point between the two spaces, it was impossible to close a domain treasure while the owner was still in it. This was something that Han Li had failed to notice while exploring the Fish Branch with Daoist Master Jingyang, but it had become quite apparent to him after he entered the Flower Branch.

On top of that, he could open up this door of light in any location in the domain as he pleased.

With that, he and Daoist Xie stepped through the door of light and returned to the cave abode together.

Standing inside his secret chamber, Han Li grabbed onto the Flower Branch again, and by the time he turned around, the door of silver light had already vanished.

He took a glance down at the Flower Branch, and a hint of elation flashed through his eyes.

"I'm very interested in that lightning cultivation art, so I'm going back to study it," Daoist Xie said.

Han Li nodded in response, and after Daoist Xie returned to its secret chamber, Han Li sat down with his legs in his own secret chamber.

As he gently massaged the Flower Branch, the thought of a cultivation art that he hadn't used for a very long time sprang into his mind, namely the Hundred Meridian Refinement Mantra.

This bone was a little too large to be made into a necklace or pendant, so it would be quite cumbersome to carry around, and given the enormous space that it contained, he didn't dare to put it in any storage tool.

Seeing as the giant rat was able to refine this item to become a section of its tailbone, then he should be able to do the same. On top of that, the Hundred Meridian Refinement Mantra came from none other than the Hundred Creations Mountain, and the giant rat had perhaps used a similar cultivation art to refine the domain treasure as well.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately went into seclusion to cultivate the Hundred Meridian Refinement Mantra.

Over thirty years flew by in a flash.

In the northern part of the Floating Cloud Mountain Range, a streak of radiant swordlight suddenly descended out of the sky. The swordlight was enveloped in a layer of golden lightning, and it crashed into a forest like a golden lightning dragon.

A resounding boom rang out as a vast expanse of golden lightning erupted in all directions, and all of the trees in the wake of the lightning were instantly incinerated out of existence, while the entire ground in a radius of several dozen kilometers had been charred black.

However, there was an ancient tree at the center of the charred area that remained completely unscathed, and atop the tree stood an azure-robed man with the index and middle fingers on his right hand joined together and pointed up at the heavens.

The man was none other than Han Li, and those two fingers of his were as translucent as jade, with silver flower design flashing upon them.

Clasped between the pair of fingers was the sharp edge of an azure longsword that was still flashing incessantly with golden lightning.

"I didn't think that refining this domain treasure into my fingers would have such an extraordinary effect. Even an attack from my Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword can be withstood with ease! No wonder even Jin Tong wasn't able to devour the domain treasure," Han Li remarked to himself as he stowed his longsword away, following which he sped away into the distance as a streak of azure light.

Upon returning to the secret chamber in his cave abode, the floral design on Han Li's two fingers flashed momentarily at his behest, following which a burst of silver light shot out from within to form a door of silver light.

Han Li immediately entered the Flower Branch domain through the door, but instead of flying through the air, he made his way down the small bone path on foot.

Over the course of the past few decades, he had been solely focused on cultivating the Hundred Meridian Refinement Mantra to fuse the Flower Branch into his fingers, and he hadn't entered the domain during this time.

Upon entering the domain, he discovered that the giant ape puppets in the spirit medicine garden had dispersed themselves around the forest to look after the spirit medicines growing there after watering the plot of land with the two vats of spirit liquid.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li ordered them to pick all of the spirit medicines littered along the small path in the forest before transferring them to the spirit medicine garden.

Chapter 626: A New Home for Mo Guang

After such an extensive period of care, the spirit soil within the spirit medicine garden had already completed the initial conversion process, and thanks to the array that Han Li had set up earlier, the world's origin qi in the garden was far more abundant than before.

Han Li was very pleased with the setup here, and he instructed the giant ape puppets to split the spirit medicines up into different categories before replanting them.

After that, he also planted many of the spirit medicines that he had previously sourced into different areas of the garden.

In the innermost section of the garden, Han Li planted that brownish-yellow spirit tree root that he had obtained from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, then pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial before pouring a drop of green spirit liquid onto it.

As the spirit liquid dripped onto the tree root, it was immediately absorbed amid a flash of green light and disappeared out of sight.

Han Li remained on the spot to observe the tree root for a moment, but didn't notice any special changes taking place, so he turned his attention to the other spirit medicines in the garden.

Some time later, he realized that he had collected so many spirit medicine seeds that the spirit medicine garden wasn't large enough to accommodate them all, so he could only summon another group of giant ape puppets to expand the garden.

The expanded section of the spirit garden hadn't been nourished with spirit liquid and also contained very little spiritual qi, thereby making it unfit for planting high-grade spirit medicines, so Han Li could only stop what he was doing for now.

He made his way over to a corner of this newly expanded section of the garden, then summoned clumps of dark purple mud that were enveloped within immortal spiritual power.

The mud fell onto the ground, and Han Li began to slowly wave his hands through the air above it. A pair of large palm projections formed by immortal spiritual power emerged, and it spread out and smoothed out the dark purple mud so that it could fuse as one with the spirit garden.

Before long, the expanded section of the spirit garden had been transformed into a muddy swamp, on the surface of which purple bubbles would occasionally burst to release waves of scorching heat.

Han Li observed the purple mist that was beginning to take shape above the swamp and the tiny arcs of lightning flashing within it, and he gave a pleased nod. Finally, he had somewhere to deposit the Lightning Aura Soil that he had collected.

After that, he replanted his Dao Warrior primary beans into the swampy soil.

After doing all of that, Han Li made his way into the purple bamboo pavilion and stayed in there for a while, and as he emerged from the pavilion, a thought suddenly occurred to him as he flipped a hand over to produce a jade box.

The box was opened to reveal the roots of a silver bamboo tree, and Han Li planted it on a plot of vacant land in the bamboo forest.

After that, he examined his new medicine garden once again like a diligent old farmer, then emerged from the Flower Branch Domain to return to his secret chamber.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li departed from his secret chamber and made his way to Mo Guang's secret chamber before rousing him from his cultivation.

Following such an extensive period of cultivation, Mo Guang had integrated himself very well with this Gray Immortal body, and his aura had stabilized at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage.

On top of that, through the use of a secret technique, he could reach the pinnacle of the early-High Zenith Stage for a duration of around forty-five minutes, so his powers were certainly nothing to be scoffed at.

"Do you need something from me, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang asked.

"I found a good place for you to go into seclusion, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang. With that new place set up, you won't have to be confined to this tiny space any longer," Han Li explained.

"Oh? Does that mean I can leave the cave abode now?" Mo Guang asked with a perplexed expression.

"No. The place I've arranged for you is inside a domain treasure with quite a large internal space for you to stay in," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"Looks like I'll have to congratulate you on securing such a precious treasure," Mo Guang said with a smile of his own.

Han Li didn't waste any more time with words, and the silver flower design on his fingers flashed momentarily, following which a door of silver light took shape in front of Mo Guang, who rose to his feet to examine the door of light.

"Come in. There's quite a bit of baleful qi left in this space, and you can use it during the course of your cultivation," Han Li said.

Mo Guang didn't hesitate any longer as he stepped into the domain, and upon setting foot on the small bone path, he inspected his surroundings before remarking, "This is quite an interesting treasure to be able to allow both spiritual qi and baleful qi to coexist in one place..."

Right at this moment, Han Li's voice rang out from outside.

"You can stay in that purple bamboo pavilion and cultivate in peace. I won't disturb you unless something important comes up."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the door of silver light vanished, and Han Li returned to his own secret chamber.

......

Half a month later.

Han Li was standing in his secret chamber with his hands clasped behind his back, observing a silver pill cauldron on the ground with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Moments later, he swept a sleeve through the air to release the Essence Fire Raven, which circled around in mid-air, then transformed into a tiny fiery figure that landed on top of the cauldron's lid.

An apologetic smile appeared on Han Li's face as he said, "Ever since I came to the Floating Cloud Mountain Range, I've had to constantly hide you, and I wasn't able to provide any spirit flames for you to devour, either, so you must be terribly bored. Once I successfully refine a Baleful Quelling Pill and resolve my baleful decay problem, we'll be able to leave this place."

It wasn't clear if the fiery figure had understood Han Li or not, but upon seeing his apologetic expression, it jumped onto his shoulder and gave him a gentle pat, as if it were trying to console him.

"I'm fine, I'm just a little unsure of whether the Baleful Quelling Pill is actually going to work. In any case, let's refine it first," Han Li said as he turned his gaze to the fiery figure, and it immediately jumped down onto the pill cauldron from his shoulder, following which a layer of scorching silver flames emerged over its body as if it were declaring its readiness to commence the refinement process.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he reached out toward the pill cauldron, upon which the fiery figure immediately sprang up into the air.

Its round cheeks bulged, and it blasted an enormous jet of flames far bigger than itself out of its mouth.

The silver flames formed a wave that surged to the underside of the cauldron, and it didn't take long before the air temperature within the secret chamber began to rise drastically from the scorching heat.

The spirit patterns on the silver pill cauldron lit up, as did the eight runes engraved onto its surface, and it gradually turned from silver into a crimson color.

At the same time, it was being lifted up into the air by the silver flames, and it hovered in mid-air while trembling incessantly.

The fiery figure was rather restless, springing into the flame beneath the cauldron one moment, then flying up to sit atop the lid of the cauldron the next moment to stare at Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li's attention remained focused solely on the cauldron and the silver flame, and once he determined the time was right, he made a beckoning motion with one hand, upon which several dozen ingredients, including the Profound Zoysia Crystal, flew out of his storage bracelet.

Those ingredients were all crushed into powder by a ball of azure light before being drawn into the cauldron, and shortly thereafter, Han Li began pouring a type of dark green spirit liquid into the mix as well.

As the spirit liquid entered the cauldron, a layer of light green powder instantly appeared over the cauldron's internal surface, but it then quickly vanished as an indescribable smell began to spread through the secret chamber.

As the smell began to gradually fade, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce three semi-transparent plants, each of which was around a foot tall.

Their leaves were as translucent as ice crystals, and the veins inside them were clearly visible. These were none other than the Bitter Ornament Herbs, and they were also crushed up by the ball of azure light before flying into the cauldron.

After doing all of that, Han Li took a glance at the cauldron, then summoned a cushion before sitting down on it with his legs crossed.

He took a glance at the ceiling of his secret chamber before suddenly joining the index and middle fingers of his right hand before thrusting them upward, and a beam of silver light instantly shot out of his fingertips before piercing into the ceiling up above.

A faint thump rang out as a hole that was roughly as thick as an infant's arm was punched through the ceiling of the secret chamber, allowing a ray of moonlight to shine down from above.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li removed the Heaven Controlling Vial from around his neck, then placed it under the moonlight.

......

Three years flew by in a flash.

At this moment, there was a vast expanse of silver fire in the secret chamber that enveloped the entire pill cauldron, and its lid was trembling incessantly, looking as if it could fly off at any moment.

However, the fiery figure was seated atop the lid of the cauldron while pressing down upon it with both hands, keeping it firmly in place.

Meanwhile, Han Li was standing beside the cauldron, observing it with a solemn expression.

Right at this moment, a cloud of black mist that resembled baleful qi seeped out of a small gap from under the lid of the cauldron before being incinerated into nothingness by the silver flames.

"It's done," Han Li immediately declared, and the fiery figure instantly sprang into the air upon hearing this, while the silver flames around the cauldron surged back into its body.

Without the support of the silver flames, the cauldron fell back onto the ground with a loud clang, while its lid flew off with a dull thump, and three balls of black light flew out from within before being drawn into Han Li's grasp.

Chapter 627: Finding Alternative Solutions

Han Li peered into the black light to find three longan-sized black pills sitting on the palm of his hand.

The three pills were as black as ink, and there was a rather spicy aroma wafting out of them.

Han Li inspected the pills for a moment long, then swept a hand through the air to stow the silver pill cauldron away before sitting down onto his cushion with his legs crossed.

The fiery figure flew over to him with a curious look in its eyes, drawing to a halt beside Han Li's hand as it stared at the three strange pills with a pair of wide eyes.

Han Li originally had very high hopes for these three Baleful Quelling Pills, but now that they had been successfully refined, he was starting to feel a little uneasy.

The pill recipe only stated that they had a chance to eradicate all of the baleful qi in the consumer's body, but as for how big that probability was, there was no definitive conclusion.

"I suppose there's only one way to find out," Han Li murmured to himself with a wry smile.

He then turned to the fiery figure with a smile as he said, "You can keep an eye on me to make sure nothing goes wrong."

The fiery figure immediately nodded in response, then flew to thirty feet away as it crossed its arms in front of its chest, wearing an expression that said: "you can count on me."

Han Li looked at it for a moment longer with an amused smile on his face, then closed his eyes to meditate.

Around an hour later, he tossed one of the Baleful Quelling Pills into his mouth, and an intensely spicy flavor instantly spread through his esophagus as the pill rolled down into his stomach.

Han Li felt as if he had swallowed a mouthful of fire, and his face turned bright red as a pained look flashed through his eyes.

Before the burst of scorching heat faded, a burst of glacial power began to spread throughout his entire body from his lower abdomen, making him feel as if he had been plunged into a glacial pit.

This baptism by fire and ice caught Han Li completely off guard, and all of his acupoints opened up without any conscious effort.

Immediately thereafter, black mist began to surge out of his acupoints, instantly forming a black vortex that enveloped his entire body.

The fiery figure immediately began to fly toward him upon seeing this, intending to eradicate the black mist with its flames, but Han Li extended a hand out of the black mist to stop it as he said, "It's fine, I'm alright."

His voice was slightly high-pitched, indicating that he was enduring immense pain, but there was also a hint of elation in his voice.

The black mist continued to surge out of his body, quickly permeating throughout the entire secret chamber, and some of it was even seeping out of the secret chamber through the hole in the ceiling.

Han Li immediately tossed out a pair of storage pouches, which began to suck in the black mist in the secret chamber, quickly restoring the room to its former state, but the black mist immediately surrounding Han Li remained as viscous as ink, resembling a huge black cocoon around him.

Time slowly passed by, and more and more baleful qi seeped out of the black cocoon before being sucked into the storage pouches.

After those two pouches were filled, Han Li released two more, and after he ran out of storage pouches, he turned to storage rings.

......

Over three years flew by in a flash.

Inside the secret chamber, a burst of black light flashed momentarily over the surface of the black cocoon, and no more baleful qi was released.

At the same time, the torturous combination of scorching and glacial agony faded from Han Li's body, and the baleful qi around him also dissipated.

At this moment, he was looking a little pale, and after taking a moment to collect himself, he slowly raised his head to reveal a disappointed look on his face.

Never had he anticipated that the Baleful Quelling Pill would be so limited in its efficacy.

While it was true that quite a bit of the baleful qi in his body had been expelled over the past three years, the job was nowhere near finished, and the baleful qi that remained in his immortal acupoints still posed a constant threat to his cultivation.

For the average person, the Baleful Quelling Pill would've been very effective. In fact, there was a decent chance that it would allow an average Golden Immortal to overcome their baleful decay altogether, but that was nowhere near the case for Han Li.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li raised his hand and swallowed both of the remaining Baleful Quelling Pills at once. A burst of agony that was even more intense than before instantly spread through his body, and before long, he was once again inundated within a cloud of dense black mist.

Ten more years passed by in the blink of an eye.

Han Li had remained seated in his secret chamber this entire time, and right at this moment, his eyes sprang open.

The three Baleful Quelling Pill that he had gone to such great lengths to refine had only cleared out part of the baleful qi in his body, thereby delaying the onset of his baleful decay, but they hadn't accomplished anything else in addition to that.

Han Li was already mentally prepared for such an outcome, so he wasn't overly disappointed. In any case, this was still a positive outcome, and the delay in the onset of his baleful decay would buy him more time to find another solution.

Looking back over his cultivation journey, he had encountered countless hardships of different magnitudes, and he was confident that this was going to be just another hurdle that he would eventually overcome.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flipped a hand over to produce his Dragon 5 mask, then released a mission in the Transient Guild, searching for ways to expel baleful qi and overcome the baleful decay.

After that, Han Li pulled out a communication array plate before injecting some immortal spiritual power into it.

......

There was a wooden pavilion in the Hundred Creations Mountain branch in Jade Gathering City.

Outside the pavilion was a huge garden of flowers of all types of vibrant colors, surrounding the pavilion like a floral sea.

Daoist Master Jingyang was seated on a reclining chair in the pavilion, and he made a beckoning motion to stow away the white array plate that was hovering in front of him.

"I didn't think that he would fail... Having said that, this is an opportunity," he murmured to himself as a faint smile appeared on his face, following which he snapped his fingers, and a green-robed young woman instantly appeared behind him.

The woman appeared to only be around sixteen to seventeen years of age with a set of beautiful facial features. She appeared to be mature beyond her years, and she extended a curtsey toward Daoist Master Jingyang as she asked, "What can I do for you, esteemed deputy mountain master?"

"Go tell the others to search for ways to expel baleful qi," Daoist Master Jingyang instructed.

A hesitant look appeared on the green-robed young woman's face upon hearing this.

"Is there a problem?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"You've already used up all of your Immortal Origin Stones, and the next resource allocation will only happen in a hundred years. All methods of baleful qi expulsion are quite expensive, so will you be using money from the inner mountain? If it's discovered that you're using those funds..."

"Don't worry about that," Daoist Master Jingyang interjected. "Just do as I say."

The green-robed young woman didn't say anything further upon hearing this, and she flew away as a petite green shadow, resembling a spritely green bird.

......

Inside Han Li's secret chamber.

Han Li made a beckoning motion to stow away his communication array plate.

Due to the incident concerning Silver Fox following the conclusion of the Jade Kun Pavilion auction, Jade Gathering City was still on high alert, so he was reluctant to go there. Hence, he could only turn to Daoist Master Jingyang for help.

He had already made use of all of the avenues available to him, and all he could do now was wait.

He cast his gaze directly forward as he planned out what he was going to do next.

At the moment, he had encountered a bottleneck in his cultivation. Without overcoming his baleful decay, he had no hope of reaching the High Zenith Stage. In terms of time-attribute cultivation arts, aside from the Mantra Treasured Axis, he wasn't that far away from complete mastery of the other two cultivation arts, but they weren't all that helpful to him, and the two cultivation arts were also incomplete.

As he considered his options, he recalled how Silver Fox had used the Spirit Refinement Technique to divert the attacks of Gongshu Tian and Su Liu, and a hint of excitement immediately welled up in his heart.

Even though he had a rough idea for what this advanced use of the Spirit Refinement Technique entailed, unfortunately, he still hadn't had a chance to put it into practice.

He hadn't been swept up in the Silver Fox incident, but it had served as a warning to him nonetheless. At this moment, he was situated in the Black Mountain Immortal Region, not the Northern Glacial Immortal Region or the primordial land, and there was a far greater Heavenly Court presence here.

Three immortal envoys had appeared at just a single auction, and it was impossible to tell exactly how much of the Heavenly Court's forces were lurking in the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

Even though Silver Fox had already escaped, those two immortal envoys could still be lingering near Jade Gathering City, and on top of that, Su Liu was also not someone to be messed with.

With that in mind, this was clearly not a good time to be cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique.

He had already verified that cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique wouldn't trigger the white plate treasure, but there was no guarantee that the immortal envoys didn't have other detection methods up their sleeve, so it was best to proceed with caution.

After some further contemplation, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to summon a damaged dagger, a small white flagon, and an azure wooden ruler, all of which were giving off faint time law power fluctuations.

The damaged dagger was something that he had found in Gongshu Jiu's storage tool, while the white flagon was the Time Severing Flagon, and the wooden ruler was the immortal treasure that he had just obtained from the Fish Branch.

Han Li made a hand seal to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis, and the Eye of Truth appeared at the center of the axis at his behest, then released a beam of golden light that fell upon the damaged dagger.

A burst of law power fluctuations instantly swept over the dagger, and it began to glow with radiant golden light before quickly being restored to its former condition.

A brand new dagger was presented to Han Li, and it was riddled with runes while also giving off a cold gleam that gave it an extremely sharp appearance.

Han Li closed his eyes as he carefully examined the time law powers within the dagger, and moments later, he opened his eyes as he gave a slight nod.

The dagger didn't contain much time law powers, but it was different from the three types of time law powers that he was currently cultivating, and there was a slightly chaotic aura about it.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li withdrew the beam of golden light, and the dagger returned to its original state before falling to the ground.

Chapter 628: Searching

Immediately thereafter, the Eye of Truth released another beam of golden light that vanished into the Time Severing Flagon in a flash, and a burst of radiant golden light appeared over its surface as well.

The flagon was looking rather old and battered, and it quickly reverted back to its brand new form while giving off a burst of formidable time law power fluctuations.

Han Li closed his eyes to examine the time law powers to discover that it was rather similar to that of the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Both time law powers had a time-slowing effect, and due to the overlap, there was no need for him to waste time on examining this treasure any further.

After setting down the Time Severing Flagon, he pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial, then tipped the drop of green spirit liquid into the flagon before closing his eyes to examine what was happening inside the flagon with his spiritual sense.

Some time later, he reopened his eyes and heaved a faint sigh.

The Time Severing Flagon was indeed able to slow down the rate of decay of its contents, but it couldn't completely counteract the effects of time. The drop of green spirit liquid was dissipating at a rate slower than normal, but it was still slowly dissipating, nonetheless.

With a shake of his head, he turned to the azure wooden ruler before gazing upon it with his Eye of Truth.

A beam of golden light shot forth before vanishing into the ruler, causing it to shudder slightly.

Externally, its appearance didn't change much, and it began to glow with radiant golden and azure light. Furthermore, the time law power fluctuations that it was giving off were even more formidable than that of the Time Severing Flagon.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately closed his eyes to conduct a closer examination.

In doing so, he discovered that the time law powers imbued within the wooden ruler had a time acceleration effect similar to that of his Reversal True Axis.

However, unlike his Reversal True Axis, which only affected the user, the time law powers within the wooden ruler could alter the rate of passage of time in an area.

In this regard, it was rather similar to the Illusory Dawn Sand Sea.

After stowing away his Mantra Treasured Axis, Han Li took a deep breath, then closed his eyes to ponder the three types of time law powers that he had just witnessed.

Around half a month passed by in a flash, and as Han Li opened his eyes, a hint of enlightenment flashed through them.

It seemed that he had further deepened his understanding of the laws of time.

In particular, after repeatedly examining the time law powers imbued within the azure wooden ruler, he had improved his understanding of the connection between the Mantra Axis Scripture and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture.

He made a hand seal to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis, and at the same time, he also summoned his Clear Time Vial.

Simultaneously, a burst of golden light emerged over his body before spreading outward to form countless grains of golden sand.

Channeling all three time-attribute cultivation arts at once, three bursts of different time law powers surged through the secret chamber before intertwining with one another.

Compared with last time, the three time law powers were resonating far more strongly than before, particularly the time law powers of the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Illusory Dawn Sand Sea.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he began to fuse the three time law powers once again.

The three bodies of golden light intertwined with one another to form a rumbling vortex, and given what had happened last time, Han Li decided it was best to take some precautionary measures.

With that in mind, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a string of azure array flags that were littered throughout the entire secret chamber to form a thick azure light barrier.

Immediately thereafter, he also released a flurry of yellow array flags that formed a semi-transparent yellow restriction in the air.

The azure and yellow restrictions fused with each other to form an even more resilient light barrier, while Han Li summoned several defensive immortal treasures to protect himself before he continued with what he was doing.

The golden vortex began to rapidly accelerate in its revolution while slowly shrinking in size, and countless golden runes of different sizes appeared within it before clashing violently against one another, sending violent time law power fluctuations surging through the air.

Given his previous experience, Han Li already knew what to expect, and he pressed on without pause, causing the golden vortex to brighten and contract even further.

A fearsome law aura surged out of the center of the vortex, and it seemed to be on the brink of exploding.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li continued to persevere, and the golden vortex abruptly shrank down even further, bringing it even closer to the verge of explosion.

Right at this moment, the three bursts of fiercely clashing time law powers suddenly mellowed out before fusing as one, while the churning golden runes stiffened before transforming into a tiny golden ring.

A hint of relief surfaced in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

With that, he had confirmed that he hadn't just fused the three time law powers by blind luck last time.

He had no idea what this golden ring was, but it clearly possessed extraordinary power.

Bursts of vast time law power fluctuations were surging out of the golden ring, causing the nearby azure and yellow light barriers to ripple violently, but they were able to hold themselves together.

Right at this moment, the Heaven Controlling Vial suddenly flew up from the ground before approaching the golden ring.

At the same time, the three time-attribute immortal treasures on the ground had also flown up alongside the Heaven Controlling Vial, much to Han Li's surprise.

The golden ring seemed to have detected something, and it began to glow more radiantly than ever.

The three immortal treasures were clearly far lighter than the Heaven Controlling Vial, and they were the first to be sucked into the golden ring.

A loud explosion rang out as the three immortal treasures instantly exploded upon flying into the golden ring, forming three balls of radiant golden light that vanished into the ring.

The golden ring lit up even further, and it abruptly expelled eight translucent golden threads. These were none other than time law threads, and they shot into Han Li's body in a flash before appearing around his Mantra Treasured Axis.

With that, the number of time law threads around the Mantra Treasured Axis had increased to twenty-six, and all of them were glowing radiantly, much to Han Li's shock and elation.

It seemed that this golden ring was capable of refining time-attribute immortal treasures into time law threads!

Right at this moment, the Heaven Controlling Vial began to glow with dazzling green radiance before being sucked into the golden ring, upon which it instantly swelled to the size of a house, and countless green runes emerged within the vial to form a churning green cloud.

A burst of formidable law power fluctuations erupted out of the green cloud, and the Mantra Treasured Axis behind Han Li abruptly lit up, following which the Eye of Truth appeared at its center.

The Eye of Truth released a translucent golden thread that shot into the Heaven Controlling Vial in a flash, and this golden thread was far thicker than the one from last time.

All of a sudden, a thick pillar of green light erupted out of the Heaven Controlling Vial to part the space up ahead, and a vast expanse of translucent light surged forth to form a translucent wall with countless scenes rapidly flashing over its surface.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

In the past, his spiritual transmigrations had taken place completely out of his control, but he had finally found a way to trigger the Heaven Controlling Vial into activating this ability.

The wall of translucent light glowed brighter and brighter, and an enormous rumbling vortex appeared on its surface.

The vortex released a burst of suction force that was far more tremendous than last time, and it enveloped Han Li's entire body before sucking him toward the vortex.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this. Could it be that this vortex was going to suck in his physical body as well?

However, it seemed like vortex's suction force wasn't sufficient to get the job done, and in the next instant, he landed back on the ground.

However, his soul was still sucked out of his body without being able to pose any resistance, and his consciousness instantly faded.

Some time later, he slowly returned to his senses, then began to inspect his surroundings, upon which he discovered that he had returned to that murky gray space once again, with the huge silver river flowing through the air beside him.

A contemplative look appeared on his face upon seeing this.

It seemed like whenever the Heaven Controlling Vial was triggered by the immense time law powers of the golden ring, his soul would be transported to this place.

He carefully thought back to what had taken place just now, and it occurred to him that during both of the latest transmigrations, the vortex on the translucent wall had displayed signs of sucking in his physical body.

On top of that, the suction force released by the vortex just now was clearly far more powerful than before.

Compared with the last transmigration, neither his powers nor his mastery over the laws of time had improved, and the only real difference was the eight time law threads that he had suddenly attained.

Could it be that if I can attain a sufficient number of time law threads, my physical body will also be transported to this place?

After mulling over this notion for a moment, Han Li quickly cast aside this train of thought before flying over to the silver river.

There were countless balls of light of different sizes flowing through the river, each of which depicted a different flashing image.

Given his previous experience, he now knew that each ball of light represented something that had happened in the past. He didn't know where these balls of light came from, but through them, he could choose where his soul was sent to.

Han Li made sure to keep his distance from the balls of light as he observed them from afar, and he also refrained from extending his spiritual sense toward them.

The balls of light flowed past peacefully without sucking in his soul, and Han Li was quite relieved to see this.

It seemed that as long as kept his distance and restrained his own spiritual sense, no transmigration would take place.

With that in mind, he began to carefully inspect the passing balls of light.

They were all traveling at an astonishing speed, but with his exceptional eyesight, he was still able to see many things.

Chapter 629: The Heavenly Court and the Devil Race

Through his observation, Han Li was able to make some new discoveries.

All of these balls of light contained different images depicting a vast array of different settings and beings.

Furthermore, these balls of light varied drastically in size, and it was clear that their sizes had to have something to do with the scenes depicted within them.

All of a sudden, Han Li raised an eyebrow as he cast his gaze toward a giant ball of light that was flowing toward him.

This ball of light depicted a black desert with a series of shadows flashing incessantly through it. It seemed that there were many people locked in a fierce battle there, and just now, a dark purple projection with three heads and six arms had flashed past.

Isn't that the cultivation art used by Shi Chuankong?

The giant ball of light passed by in front of Han Li without pause, and he decided to release a wisp of spiritual sense toward it.

As soon as his spiritual sense made contact with the ball of light, the latter immediately released a burst of suction force that sucked in Han Li's soul.

Some time later, he began to slowly recover his consciousness, and the deafening sounds of a ferocious battle rang out all around him, while the surrounding space trembled violently.

Han Li opened his eyes ever so slightly to inspect his surroundings, and sure enough, he was situated on the black desert that he had witnessed through the ball of light.

High up in the sky were thick black clouds that were extremely dense, resembling enormous chunks of lead that struck the beholder with a sense of foreboding.

Thick bolts of dark purple lightning were flashing through the clouds, and two groups of cultivators were locked in an intense battle beneath the clouds.

One side consisted mostly of humanoid cultivators clad in suits of purple armor, but there were also some among them who had strange appendages like beastly heads, wings, or long tails. All of them were giving off fierce devilish qi, and they were clearly all devilish beings.

There were at least two hundred to three hundred thousand of these devilish cultivators, and the majority of them were at the Spatial Tempering and Body Integration Stages.

There were also many True Immortals and Golden Immortals among them, and they were led by over ten Jade Immortals, all of whom were standing at the forefront of the devilish army with blinding purple light radiating from their bodies.

One of them had summoned a purple projection with three heads and six arms behind them, and that was most likely what Han Li had spotted just now.

This was clearly a battle of an enormous scale, and Han Li cast his gaze toward the opposing side to discover that all of them were clad in suits of golden armor, and they weren't outnumbered by the devilish army in the slightest.

Even though these suits of golden armor were somewhat different from the ones worn by immortal envoys, it was clear that these cultivators belonged to the Heavenly Court.

The Heavenly Court army wasn't inferior to the devilish army at all, and they were also led by over ten Jade Immortals who were locked in battle against the devilish Jade Immortals.

In the air behind the Heavenly Court army was an enormous golden vortex that was several dozen kilometers in size, and at its center was a giant pathway that was around half a kilometer wide.

The vortex was releasing formidable spatial fluctuations, indicating that it was a spatial passageway, and more cultivators clad in suits of golden armor were constantly pouring out of the vortex to join the Heavenly Court army.

The two armies continued to clash as lights of different colors erupted forth in all directions amid earth-shattering booms, and the battle between the High Zenith cultivators was particularly terrifying. The ground was already riddled with enormous trenches and craters with crimson lava bubbling beneath them, and countless spatial rifts were constantly being torn open, as if this very space itself were unable to withstand the intensity of the battle.

This is a battle between the Devil Race and the Heavenly Court!

At this moment, he had taken over the body of a deceased devilish warrior wearing a suit of lavish purple armor. He appeared to have possessed quite a lofty cultivation base, and he had perished from a hole that had been pierced through his lower abdomen.

All of a sudden, a thunderous roar of fury rang out from beneath the ground.

A massive bulge rapidly appeared on the ground in front of the devilish army before exploding, and an enormous figure slowly emerged from beneath the earth.

Han Li turned his gaze to that direction, and he couldn't help but draw a sharp breath at what he saw.

The giant figure was a rotund creature that was just barely humanoid in form. It had a pair of thin and long eyes, a flat nose, and a cavernous mouth that was filled with yellowish-black sharp fangs with viscous drool flowing out incessantly, presenting a disgusting sight to behold.

The creature was extremely tall, close to a hundred thousand feet in stature, and it had a bulging belly. Its skin was a withered yellow color that resembled coarse rock, and its body was covered in molten lava, but it appeared to be completely unbothered as it walked along while dragging an enormous club behind it.

A terrifying aura that wasn't inferior to any of the High Zenith cultivators in the sky was emanating from the creature's body, and it let loose an earth-shattering roar, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

Immediately thereafter, it began to lurch forward with extremely heavy footsteps that caused the entire earth to tremble, and it charged at the Heavenly Court army, creating such violent tremors that some of the nearer Heavenly Court cultivators were unable to remain on their feet.

What is that thing?!

In the next instant, the ground began to tremble violently once again, and more of those massive bulges appeared in front of the devilish army, following which a collection of twenty to thirty of those massive creatures emerged from the earth before charging at the Heavenly Court army with their clubs held aloft.

In the face of these enormous clubs, the Heavenly Court cultivators were crushed like insects, and the front of the army immediately began to collapse.

However, right at this moment, the sound of a loud horn rang out from within the Heavenly Court army, and all of the Heavenly Court cultivators immediately began to retreat, while several hundred silver giants emerged.

These silver giants were each close to ten thousand feet tall, with spiky silver hair that resembled steel needles on their heads. Furthermore, there were huge silver wings that were flashing with silver lightning on their backs.

In the left hand of each giant was a short silver awl, while in the right was a massive silver hammer, both of which were giving off astonishing lightning auras.

In the face of the small army of mountainous creatures, the silver giants remained completely expressionless, and they immediately raised their hands to aim their awls at the opposing creatures.

Immediately thereafter, they raised their hammers before striking them heavily against the backends of their awls, and bursts of rumbling thunder rang out as several hundred incredibly thick bolts of silver lightning erupted out of their hands before striking the rotund creatures like a volley of giant silver lightning spears.

Tremendous lightning law power fluctuations surged out of the silver lightning, causing the black lightning in the dark cloud up above to churn violently.

The rotund creatures were rather alarmed by this sudden assault, and they roared as they swung their clubs through the air, conjuring up countless club projections to defend themselves.

However, the club projections stood no chance against the silver lightning, and the latter was able to blast a series of huge holes into the seemingly indestructible bodies of the giant creatures.

In the blink of an eye, most of the giants exploded into countless scraps of flesh, and the few that survived had also suffered severe injuries.

However, the silver lightning on the bodies of the silver giants had also completely faded, and they were all looking quite weary. At the same time, their lightning hammers and awls had also become completely dull and devoid of luster. Some of them had even begun to crack, and they seemed to be disposable treasures.

Right at this moment, the dark clouds above the silver giants suddenly began to churn violently, and all of the black lightning within a radius of hundreds of kilometers converged to form a massive black lightning hand that was several dozen acres in size before swooping down upon the silver giants.

The giant black hand was giving off a terrifying aura that threatened to crush the entire space beneath it, but right at this moment, a ball of golden fire suddenly appeared above the silver giants.

It was a fiery golden figure that was entirely enshrouded in golden flames, and as soon as they appeared, they immediately reached up with one hand before making a grabbing motion.

A resounding boom instantly rang out as a giant draconic claw formed by golden flames took shape, then clashed against the massive lightning hand with tremendous force.

The giant lightning hand was instantly stopped cold in its tracks.

"You thought you could fool me with your little tricks, Li Mozi? Even a child would've been able to plainly see that you were using those Titanic Devils to lure out my Lightning God Brigade!" the fiery golden figure sneered.

"Is that so?"

A cold voice rang out from the black clouds up above, and right at this moment, one of the giant creatures that was on the verge of death opened its mouth to release a ball of radiant crimson light, which sped over to the silver giants in a flash before revealing itself to be a fist-sized crimson ball.

The ball was riddled with what appeared to be a system of blood vessels, and it was pulsating incessantly like a living creature.

An alarmed look instantly appeared on the face of the fiery golden figure upon seeing this, and they immediately attempted to flee, but the voice within the dark clouds up above rang out once again.

"You're not getting away that easily!"

The giant lightning hand began to glow brightly as it forced the opposing fiery draconic claw downward, and at the same time, one of the lightning hand's fingers twitched ever so slightly.

Two thick bolts of black lightning instantly sprang out of the tip of the finger, appearing in the path of the fiery golden figure in a flash before slicing toward him like the blades of a pair of giant lightning scissors.

Chapter 630: Evenly Matched

The fiery golden figure let loose a furious roar upon seeing this, and they instantly swelled to several times their original size, revealing themselves to be a burly man with a head of golden hair. His entire body was enveloped within a layer of murky golden light that was releasing formidable law power fluctuations, and it seemed to be his spirit domain, but only limited to a range of several dozen feet.

At the same time, a pair of golden dragon horns appeared on his head, and a layer of golden scales surfaced over his face, as well as the exposed sections of his arms. To complete the transformation, his hands turned into a pair of golden dragon claws.

A golden dragon projection appeared around him, then shot forth through the air before vanishing into the fiery draconic claw up above.

The fiery claw immediately lit up further, and it was able to keep the giant lightning hand at bay again.

The golden-haired man let loose a thunderous roar while thrusting a fist forward, summoning an enormous golden fist projection that instantly destroyed the two bolts of black lightning before reaching down toward the crimson bead below.

However, it was already too late.

A burst of crimson light flashed over the bead, following which it exploded with a deafening boom, releasing a giant crimson sun that encompassed all of the silver giants within it.

The golden-haired man up above was also inundated by the crimson sun, which was giving off bursts of tremendous law power fluctuations.

The ground down below was also unable to escape the crimson sun's incredible heat, and it melted away rapidly like wax, disintegrating into plumes of smoke.

Many of the combatants from both armies were also swept up in the crimson sun, and they were instantly melted into puddles of blood.

That bead contained blood law powers!

Han Li was astonished to see this.

The master of Red Moon Island had also been a user of the laws of blood, but he was only a True Immortal who had attained his law powers through the power of faith, so his blood law powers couldn't even begin to compare with that of the crimson sun.

A streak of golden flames shot out of the crimson sun before landing in the distance, then faded to reveal the golden-haired man.

The golden dragon scales on many parts of his body had become damaged, with some even splitting open entirely, and he immediately made a hand seal to conjure up a layer of golden flames over his own body.

As a result, his injuries began to rapidly heal, and in the blink of an eye, he had made a full recovery.

Meanwhile, the crimson sun was rapidly fading, but the silver giants within it had been completely wiped out with no trace left behind.

The golden-haired man's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he looked up into the sky right as a purple-robed middle-aged man slowly descended out of the dark clouds above.

The man appeared to be in his forties, and there was a series of purple devilish patterns all over his face. His eyes were long and thin, while his nose resembled a hook, and there was cold baleful qi surging out of his entire body.

Incredibly tremendous auras erupted out of the bodies of both men before clashing violently, causing the nearby space to tremble and ripple incessantly, while heaven and earth also began to tremble and sway.

Han Li was astonished to discover that both of them possessed auras far superior to that of the late-High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortal, indicating that they were most likely at the Great Encompassment Stage.

The battlefield down below was quite far away from the two of them, but both armies seemed to have been affected by the spiritual pressure that they were releasing, and a temporary ceasefire ensued as everyone cast their eyes upward.

The clashing High Zenith cultivators also disengaged themselves from battle before arriving behind the golden-haired man and the purple-robed man.

"Did you think that destroying my Lightning God Brigade would turn the tide of this battle? How naive!" the golden-haired man sneered as he swept a hand through the air, and golden light flashed within the spatial passageway behind him, following which a fleet of around forty to fifty golden ships emerged from within.

The ships were all glowing with radiant golden light that illuminated the dark clouds in the sky a golden color.

All of the ships were tens of thousands of feet in length and were riddled with golden and silver runes, resembling a pack of resting giant beasts.

The decks of all of the ships were packed with Heavenly Court cultivators that were busy at work, and there were thick golden pillars extending out of the front of each ship. All of these pillars were hollow in the center, resembling cannon barrels, and the ships spread out in a horizontal line with those barrels aimed straight at the devilish army.

The purple-robed man's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and even from afar, Han Li could sense that these ships were extremely dangerous.

"As long as this spatial passageway remains, more and more reinforcements will continue to come through, and it'll only be a matter of time before we destroy the entire Devil Realm. if you know what's good for you, then immediately pledge your allegiance to our Heavenly Court to oppose the Reincarnation Palace with us!" the golden-haired man threatened.

"Our Devil Realm has already made it plenty clear that we'll play no part in the conflict between your Heavenly Court and the Reincarnation Palace," the purple-robed man replied with a shake of his head.

"In that case, prepare to suffer the consequences of your decision!" the golden-haired man declared in a cold voice as he raised a hand high above his head, and the Heavenly Court army immediately began charging at the devilish army.

The devilish army stood firm in their path, and the battle resumed.

However, the purple-robed man refrained from entering the fray. Instead, he was observing the battlefield with a hint of purple light in his eyes.

All of a sudden, the golden-haired man in the distance burst into laughter as he shot forth through the air, appearing above the giant golden ships in a flash. At the same time, his right arm swelled to several times its original size, transforming into a giant golden dragon claw before grabbing viciously down upon the space beside him.

The purple-robed man's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

The golden dragon claw tore straight through the space there before vanishing into it, and an earth-shattering boom rang out, followed by an eruption of tremendous spiritual pressure that tore the spatial rift there ten times wider.

A purple figure stumbled out of the spatial rift, and it was none other than the purple-robed man. His left sleeve had been completely torn away, revealing several bleeding wounds.

Bursts of golden flames emerged from those wounds before attempting to burrow into his body as if they were living creatures, and his expression instantly changed slightly as purple light flashed over his wounds to snuff out the golden flames, following which he sped away into the distance.

Meanwhile, the purple-robed man who was standing in the distant sky above the devilish army vanished into thin air.

"You tried to use the same trick again? You must take me for a fool!" the golden-haired man sneered as he shot forth like a golden arrow, aggressively pursuing the purple-robed man while making a hand seal, upon which all of the runes on the surfaces of the dozens of giant golden ships lit up.

Bursts of golden light began to flow over the ships, while thunderous rumbling rang out within them.

The black barrels in front of the giant ships began to glow with golden light that was rapidly becoming brighter while giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations, and all of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out as over a hundred thick pillars of golden light erupted out of the ships before striking the devilish army.

Agonized howls instantly rang out in all directions as all of the devilish beings who came into contact with the pillars of golden light were instantly obliterated, and each pillar of golden light only slowly dissipated after piercing through hundreds of devilish beings.

In the wake of this first round of attacks, tens of thousands of devilish beings had disappeared without a trace.

At this moment, Han Li was laying behind the devilish army, so he wasn't affected, but he was still stunned to see this.

Each of those pillars of golden light had been comparable in power to an all-out attack from a High Zenith cultivator.

The purple-robed man was furious to see the pillars of golden light inflicting such extensive damage throughout the devilish army, and he loose a thunderous roar as he thrust a palm toward the oncoming golden-haired man.

An antiquated wheel flew out amid a flash of black lightning, and the wheel was entirely black in color with a diameter of around a foot.

There were all types of demon beasts engraved onto the edge of the wheel, while at the center was a black humanoid design.

The humanoid figure was wearing a tall hat, and his mouth protruded outward like the beak of a bird. There were four huge black wings on his back, and he was standing atop a pair of black lightning snakes. It was a very strange sight to behold, and it seemed to be depicting some type of ancient deity.

As soon as the antiquated wheel emerged, it immediately began to expand rapidly, swelling to over a hundred feet in size in the blink of an eye. At the same time, all of the designs etched onto its surface began to release radiant black lightning, and in particular, the humanoid deity was flashing incessantly, as if it had sprung to life.

A burst of incredibly formidable lightning law power fluctuations erupted forth, causing the nearby space to shudder violently, and bolts of black lightning came falling incessantly out of the sky before fusing into the black wheel, making it glow brighter and brighter.

A stunned look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he observed the black wheel from afar, and the golden-haired man had also adopted a far more serious expression as he made a hand seal to summon a golden flag that was around ten feet in size with a fiery river depicted on its surface.

Fire law power fluctuations that weren't inferior to the law power fluctuations released by the black wheel erupted out of the golden flag, yet before the golden-haired man had a chance to activate the flag, a sharp bird call rang out from the black wheel.

The sound wasn't very loud, but it had an excessively piercing quality, and the golden-haired man shuddered as a hint of disorientation flashed through his eyes.

Immediately thereafter, seven or eight tree-branched-shaped bolts of lightning sprang out of the black wheel before hurtling silently toward the golden-haired man.

Even though this lightning was still black in color, it was a far lighter shade that was almost transparent, but the lightning law powers that it contained were extremely formidable.

Chapter 631: Leverage

The golden-haired man immediately snapped back to his senses, then let loose a loud roar, and the golden flag in front of him instantly swelled to over a hundred times its original size, then released countless balls of golden light that formed a fiery golden river around him.

Several thick bolts of lightning struck the golden river, triggering violent waves, and the entire golden river began to tremble violently, looking as if it were about to disintegrate.

Radiant golden light erupted out of the golden-haired man's body, and he transformed into a giant golden dragon that was tens of thousands of feet in length.

The body of the dragon was long and sleek, yet still powerful in appearance, and it was entirely covered in a thick layer of golden scales. Every single scale was riddled with golden spirit patterns that gave them an indestructible appearance, while the dragon's claws were flashing with golden light and seemed to be able to tear through anything.

An enormous aura that was almost twice as powerful as that of the golden-haired man in his human form erupted out of the dragon's body, and it opened its cavernous mouth to send a thick pillar of golden light shooting into the golden river.

The golden river instantly brightened significantly while expanding to several times its original size, and the golden flames within it also began to flow several times faster than before.

The bolts of lightning were swept up in the golden river before quickly being inundated.

The purple-robed man made a hand seal upon seeing this, and a burst of black lightning erupted out of his body before quickly spreading outward to form a black lightning spirit domain that was dozens of kilometers in size, encompassing the golden-haired man within it.

Countless arcs of lightning were churning incessantly within the spirit domain, and there were around a dozen tall black humanoid figures standing amid the lightning, all of which were giving off astonishing lightning law power fluctuations.

The golden dragon's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, following which it prepared to also release its spirit domain as it roared, "If you insist on making this a battle of life and death, then I'm more than happy to oblige!"

However, the purple-robed man was a little faster, and he seized the initiative, chanting an incantation before pointing a finger at the black wheel, upon which all of the dozen or so humanoid figures in the spirit domain shot forth like lightning before vanishing into the black wheel in a flash.

The wheel instantly swelled drastically in size once again, and it turned semi-transparent while giving off blinding lightning.

Dozens of thick bolts of lightning shot out of the wheel, and most of them were hurtling toward the golden-haired man, but a small portion of them were being directed toward the giant golden ships.

"How dare you allow yourself to get distracted when facing me?"

The giant golden dragon was furious to see this, and the golden flames all over its body erupted outward, but instead of forming a spirit domain, it transformed into a giant golden fiery cloud.

Countless runes were churning within the cloud, producing an incessant rumbling sound, then converged before sweeping toward the purple-robed man with tremendous power, paying no heed to the lightning that was hurtling toward the giant ships down below.

The golden cloud clashed against the bolts of lightning, but there was no sound.

The bolts of lightning pierced through the golden cloud in a flash, then continued to hurtle directly toward the giant golden dragon without being slowed down at all.

However, the same applied to the golden cloud as well, and it continued to sweep toward the purple-robed man, appearing in front of him in a flash.

The fiery cloud then began to rapidly transform as if it were a living creature, taking on the form of a mountainous golden dragon's head that opened its cavernous mouth to devour the purple-robed man whole.

The purple-robed man's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he shot back in retreat while making a hand seal, upon which the black wheel swooped over from afar to block the golden dragon's head.

At the same time, all of the lightning within the spirit domain converged to form a massive black lightning net that enshrouded the dragon's head.

The dragon's head whipped to the side to force the black wheel back, then let loose a thunderous roar, releasing a burst of devastating soundwaves that conjured up countless indistinct blade and spear projections, which pierced through the net of black lightning before inundating the purple-robed man.

The black lightning net was torn apart, and the nearby space was also shattered like a mirror.

The purple-robed man's body trembled violently in the face of the torrent of soundwaves, and gashes began to appear over his skin, as if his body were about to be torn apart.

Blood began to spray out of those gashes in all directions, and he was sent flying back through the air.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and at this moment, the golden dragon's entire body was enveloped within the river of golden flames.

Dozens of thick bolts of lightning pierced into the fiery golden river amid an earth-shattering boom, stirring the river of fire up into a frenzy.

However, the bolts of lightning were ultimately no match for the raging golden river, and the former quickly subsided.

At the same time, a string of explosions rang out down below as most of the giant golden ships were destroyed by the remaining bolts of lightning.

The golden dragon paid no heed to this at all as it shot forth directly toward the purple-robed man.

A thunderous draconic roar rang out as a giant dragon claw projection appeared in the sky above the purple-robed man before crashing down with vicious power, but right at this moment, a black vortex suddenly appeared beneath the purple-robed man before instantly sucking him in.

As a result, the dragon claw projection struck nothing but empty air, much to the golden dragon's bewilderment.

Several dozen kilometers away, the black vortex reappeared, and the purple-robed man flew out from within, following which a pillar of green light also shot out of the vortex into the purple-robed man's body.

He was instantly enveloped in a layer of bright green light, and his injuries began to rapidly heal, vanishing in virtually the blink of an eye.

The golden dragon was just about to pounce at the purple-robed man, but it stopped in its tracks with a hesitant expression upon seeing this.

The purple-robed man was looking rather pale, but he was able to move just fine now, and he stood up before extending a deep bow toward the black vortex. "Thank you, esteemed Devilish Monarch."

The golden dragon's expression changed drastically upon hearing this, and it abruptly turned and fled toward the spatial passageway without any hesitation.

Right at this moment, a cold, seemingly omnipresent voice rang out. "You think you can just get away after slaughtering so many of my brethren?"

As soon as the voice trailed off the space above the fleeing golden dragon abruptly caved in, and a giant silver spatial hand that was several acres in size emerged before descending upon the golden dragon.

The golden dragon was instantly slowed down, and even though the silver hand still hadn't fully descended upon it, the surrounding space had become incredibly heavy as it compressed upon it from all directions.

In that instant, it was as if time were standing still. All sounds faded, and the only thing that the golden dragon could see was the giant silver hand expanding in its field of view.

"No!"

The golden dragon roared with all its might as bursts of ferocious golden flame erupted out of its body.

A series of massive holes were instantly scorched into the surrounding space that was compressing toward it, but the pressure weighing down on it wasn't lessened at all.

The giant silver hand gently descended upon the golden dragon, and the latter was instantly crushed into a huge pile of mincemeat like a fragile egg.

Everyone at the scene was completely rooted to the spot, unable to believe what they were seeing.

The entire battlefield had become deathly silent, but in the next instant, a chaotic commotion ensued as all of the Heavenly Courts High Zenith cultivators fled toward the spatial passageway as quickly as they could.

The giant silver hand gently flicked a finger through the air, and a burst of silver light shot out of its fingertip.

A string of dull thuds rang out as all of the Heavenly Court's High Zenith cultivators were abruptly rooted to the spot. A hole had appeared on each of their foreheads, and blood and intracranial fluids were gushing out from within.

The light in their eyes quickly faded, and they began to plummet out of the sky like dead weights.

The silver hand then flew toward the golden vortex before crashing into it with tremendous power, and the spatial passageway was instantly cast into a state of violent instability.

However, right at this moment, strips of golden runes surged out of the spatial passageway, forming a golden array that was doing everything in its power to stabilize the passageway, but it seemed that this was only delaying the inevitable.

A cold harrumph rang out from within the giant silver hand, following which it closed its fingers around the spatial passageway before grabbing down with unmatched power.

The spatial passageway finally completely collapsed, and it slowly closed amid a resounding boom, quickly vanishing into thin air.

The Heavenly Court army was cast into complete despair upon seeing this.

In contrast, the morale for the devilish army was significantly elevated, and they were able to easily tear through the ranks of the opposing army to commence a one-sided massacre.

The purple-robed man paid no heed to what was happening down below as he flew over to the giant silver hand with an embarrassed look on his face. "My sincerest apologies for my incompetence, esteemed Devilish Monarch. If you hadn't intervened, the consequences would've been catastrophic."

The silver hand transformed into a humanoid silver figure, then said, "Our Devil Realm still isn't powerful enough to stand toe to toe against the Heavenly Court, so even if someone else had been in your place, the outcome wouldn't have been any different."

The purple-robed man's expression eased slightly upon hearing this.

"Don't kill all of these Heavenly Court cultivators. Only kill a third of them, then restrict the cultivation bases of the rest and send them to Asura Island to serve as slaves," the silver figure continued.

"Why should we spare their lives? They've killed many of our brethren. If we spare them, that could elicit a great deal of dissent," the purple-robed man asked with a perplexed expression.

"Right now, the primary enemy of the Heavenly Court is the Reincarnation Palace. Even though they've sent out an army against our Devil Realm, there are no Dao Ancestors leading this army, which indicates that the Heavenly Court isn't going to fully declare war on us.

“Otherwise, they run the risk of having to face both our Devil Realm and the Reincarnation Palace at once, and that's not a situation that they want to be in. This battle is going to end very soon, and killing a third of the enemies will already be enough to satisfy most of our brethren.

“By keeping the rest alive, we'll have leverage that we can use in negotiations with the Heavenly Court, and we'll be able to enjoy some peace for the immediate future," the silver figure explained.

"Your wisdom is truly unmatched, esteemed Devilish Lord!" the purple-robed man praised with a slight bow.

"I'll leave things to you here. Make sure to continue to conduct stringent surveillance over the Heavenly Court," the silver figure instructed, then vanished into the nearby space.

The purple-robed man stood in silence for a moment, then descended toward the battlefield down below.

Behind the battlefield, the body that Han Li had possessed cracked open its eyelid a tiny sliver, then heaved an internal sigh of relief.

That giant silver hand had struck him with a far more formidable sense of pressure than even the two Great Encompassment Stage beings on the battlefield, and as soon as it appeared, he immediately retracted his spiritual power so that it was hiding in the deepest recesses of the body's mind, and only now did he dare to peek out ever so slightly.

Chapter 632: Devil Realm

After taking a moment to compose himself, Han Li carefully released his spiritual sense, spreading it in all directions to observe the current state of the battlefield.

After the golden-haired man and all of the Heavenly Court's High Zenith cultivators were struck down by the silver figure, all of the remaining Heavenly Court cultivators immediately began fleeing in all directions in a blind panic, while the devilish army set off in hot pursuit, led by their High Zenith cultivators.

Instead of directly participating in the battle, Li Mozi released his lightning-attribute spirit domain to encompass an enormous area, and all of the devilish cultivators within it had lightning garments draped over their bodies, significantly enhancing their speed. In contrast, all of the Heavenly Court cultivators were slowed down by the disruptive lightning in their way.

In the span of no more than fifteen minutes, the Heavenly Court army had already completely collapsed. However, instead of slaughtering all of the Heavenly Court cultivators, the devilish army took most of them as prisoners, sealing away their cultivation bases, then confiscated their storage treasures before throwing them into a fleet of giant flying ships to be sent away.

The remaining few giant golden ships from the Heavenly Court were also claimed by the devilish army, while others began to clean up the battlefield down below.

Han Li was encompassed within Li Mozi's spirit domain, so he didn't dare to move at all, and he continued to lay on the ground in a completely still fashion, allowing himself to be carried away by devilish cultivators into a giant ship that was filled with bodies.

Seeing as he wasn't going to be able to leave this place, Han Li decided to take this time to examine the memories of the body that he had possessed, and an enormous wave of memories instantly flooded into his mind.

This body contained far more memories than the ones from his previous few stints of spiritual transmigration, and even though he had already grown accustomed to this process, he was still struck by a sense of tearing agony.

He gritted his teeth to fight back the pain, and only after a long while did the agony recede.

At this point, countless memory fragments had already appeared in his mind, and he immediately began to search carefully through them.

He had many questions on his mind pertaining to what he had just witnessed, and he was hoping to be able to find some answers in these memories.

As it turned out, the body that he possessed belonged to a late-High Zenith Stage devilish cultivator by the name of You Ao, and currently, he was in a place known as the Devil Realm.

Even back before he ascended to the True Immortal Realm, he had made a journey through the Devil Realm. He had found it rather strange that he had encountered extremely few cultivators using devilish cultivation arts ever since his ascension to the True Immortal Realm, but You Ao's memories explained to him why this was the case.

Those who used devilish cultivation arts would always appear in the Devil Realm through normal ascension, and You Ao was precisely one of the cultivators who had ascended to the Devil Realm from a lower realm.

According to his knowledge, the Devil Realm was also situated somewhere in the True Immortal Realm, neighboring several of its immortal regions, but it had always been an independent, standalone region.

Han Li tried to search through the memories for some information pertaining to the owner of the giant silver hand, but was unable to find anything, perhaps because the memories were missing, or perhaps simply because You Ao didn't have such knowledge to begin with.

As for why this battle had taken place, Han Li had already gathered a rough idea from the conversation between Li Mozi and the golden-haired man. It seemed that the Heavenly Court wanted to recruit the Devil Realm as an ally to contend against the Reincarnation Palace, but the Devil Race wished to remain neutral and take no part in this conflict.

This revelation forced Han Li to see the Reincarnation Palace through new eyes. He had originally thought that the Reincarnation Palace was just an underground organization that wasn't all that powerful, but it seemed that the Reincarnation Palace posed far more of a threat to the Heavenly Court than he first imagined.

Given what he currently knew, not only did the Reincarnation Palace have certain core members in the form of Reincarnation Disciples, it also had many branch organizations like the Transient Guild and the Ubiquitous Pavilion. On the surface, these organizations appeared similar to trading houses, but in reality, they were trying to lure in members for the Reincarnation Palace.

With that in mind, Han Li couldn't help but wonder who was controlling the Reincarnation Palace behind the scenes, and what their objectives were.

Han Li shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, then continued to examine You Ao's memories.

All of a sudden, he made an interesting discovery, which was that You Ao was a cultivator under the Vast Origin House, and he had been sent here by none other than the Vast Origin House. Unfortunately, he was met with a sneak attack from two Heavenly Court High Zenith cultivators as soon as the battle began, thereby leading to his demise.

Isn't the Vast Origin House the organization overseen by Lan Ying? Is this just a coincidence, or could it be that the Vast Origin House in that lower realm is a branch of the Devil Realm's Vast Origin House? [1]

According to You Ao's memories, not only was the Vast Origin House the number one trading house in the entire Devil Realm, and it had many contacts in other immortal regions. It was an extremely powerful organization, so it would be no surprise for it to have developed some branches in lower realms.

The thought of Violet Spirit immediately sprang into Han Li's mind in association with the Vast Origin House. [2]

She was closely connected to the Vast Origin House in that lower realm, and Han Li couldn't help but wonder if she had also managed to ascend.

However, given that she was using devilish cultivation arts, if she were to ascend, she would most likely end up in the Devil Realm.

On top of that, it was also unclear what had become of Nangong Wan in the Spirit Realm.

Unfortunately, he was currently in no position to go and search for them.

With that in mind, he heaved an internal sigh before refocusing his attention on the task at hand. At this moment, most of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis projection hovering before him had already faded.

Watching the battle between the Devil Race and the Heavenly Court had taken a lot of time.

It seemed that You Ao had only perished recently, so there was a vast volume of memories left in his mind, and it was going to take a very long time to examine all of them.

Hence, there was no time to waste, and Han Li continued to search through the memories for any information that would be useful to him.

His top priority at the moment was to expel the baleful qi in his body and reach the High Zenith Stage, so he turned his focus to the memories related to You Ao's High Zenith Stage breakthrough.

Much to his elation, those memories had been preserved quite well, and he hurriedly began to examine them, but it didn't take long before his elation began to fade.

As it turned out, just like normal cultivators, devilish cultivators also had to expel the baleful qi in their bodies in order to make a breakthrough to the High Zenith Stage.

The method of baleful qi expulsion that had been chosen by You Ao was quite an interesting one. Instead of taking any pills to expel the baleful qi in his body, he tracked down a devilish beast found in the Devil Realm known as the Dream Tapir to devour all of his baleful qi.

The Dream Tapir was a very special devilish beast that was capable of devouring all things, including even dreams and memories.

These beasts were extremely rare, even in the Devil Realm, and whenever one was tracked down, it would immediately be captured by certain powerful figures to become their spirit pets.

After all, its ability to devour baleful qi was extremely useful, and even Great Encompassment cultivators held Dream Tapirs in very high regard as they were ideal for nurturing up-and-coming juniors.

You Ao was only able to secure an opportunity to use a Dream Tapir through the Vast Origin House, and in exchange, he had to pledge lifelong servitude to the Vast Origin House.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this. At the moment, he was situated in the Black Mountain Immortal Region, so this method of baleful qi expulsion was entirely unavailable to him.

He was feeling a little disappointed, but he continued to search through You Ao's memories in the hopes of making further discoveries.

As a late-High Zenith cultivator, You Ao's memories contained many precious nuggets of useful information, and Han Li soon found himself completely absorbed in examining all of You Ao's cultivation insights and experiences, particularly pertaining to devilish cultivation arts and secret techniques.

A short while later, an elated look appeared on Han Li's face as he discovered a secret technique called the Infernal Devilish Eyes in You Ao's memories.

As the name suggested, this was a spirit eye ability that granted one exceptional ocular powers.

However, the prerequisites for cultivating this secret technique were also extremely stringent, and even in the entire Devil Realm, not many cultivators had been able to master this ocular ability. Even though You Ao was in possession of this secret technique, he hadn't attempted to cultivate it.

In order to cultivate this secret technique, one had to first possess a certain spirit eye foundation. Otherwise, their eyes wouldn't be able to bear the power of the technique and would be destroyed, rather than enhanced.

Furthermore, cultivating this secret technique was an extremely lengthy endeavor, and one had to constantly inject their hard-earned devilish qi into their eyes to slowly nourish them.

On top of that, a special medicinal fluid was required to complement the cultivation of the Infernal Devilish Eyes, and all of the ingredients required for this medicinal liquid were extremely precious and had to be very advanced in age.

Given these three hurdles, it was no wonder that even a late-High Zenith cultivator like You Ao had decided against pursuing it.

However, a hint of excitement welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this.

While these three hurdles were indeed quite difficult to overcome, they were not entirely insurmountable for him.

In terms of a spirit eye foundation, he possessed the Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and he could cultivate devilish qi using his Provenance True Devil Arts, which should be enough to support the cultivation of the Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Thanks to his time law powers, Han Li no longer had much reliance on his Provenance True Devil Arts, so the devilish qi that it had cultivated would be perfect for nourishing his eyes.

As for the supplementary medicinal fluid, with the Heaven Controlling Vial in his possession, this wasn't a problem, either.

He had seen the recipe for the medicinal fluid, and while the required ingredients were all indeed quite precious, they were not impossible to find. The main obstacle in that regard was that all of the ingredients had to be of quite an advanced age.

Furthermore, in a very fortuitous turn of events, one of the primary ingredients on the recipe was the Farsight Weed, something that he had obtained a large supply of from the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor and planted in the Flower Branch space, so all that was left was to mature it.

Han Li read through the Infernal Devilish Eyes secret technique a few more times, ensuring that he had it well and truly memorized, and only then did he move on to You Ao's other memories.

Before long, all of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis faded, and a burst of tremendous suction force erupted out of the axis to suck Han Li's soul out of You Ao's body.

[1]. For more information on the Vast Origin House, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2124: Vast Origin House.

[Back]

[2]. For more information on Violet Spirit, please refer to https://a-record-of-a-mortal-is-journey-to-immortality.fandom.com/wiki/Wang_Ning

[Back]

Chapter 633: Cultivating the Infernal Devilish Eyes

Inside the secret chamber.

Han Li shuddered slightly as he found himself back in the real world once again.

As the translucent wall of light gradually faded, the Eye of Truth on the Mantra Treasured Axis also slowly closed, and Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to stow the axis away, along with the Clear Time Vial and the Illusory Dawn Sand Sea.

A contemplative look then appeared on his face as he summoned his Dragon 5 mask, and he released a series of missions in the Transient Guild interface, searching for the ingredients required to refine the medicinal fluid for the Infernal Devilish Eyes.

After releasing all of the missions, a floral pattern appeared over the index and middle fingers of his right hand, following which a burst of silver light shot forth to create a silver door of light that was around ten feet tall in front of him.

He made his way into the Flower Branch space through the door and arrived directly outside his spirit medicine garden.

The garden was filled with abundant spiritual qi, and around a dozen giant ape puppets were busy at work, having expanded the garden even further.

Han Li slowly made his way into the garden, and he noticed that most of the spirit plants had already grown accustomed to their new environment, while only a small number of them were looking a little withered and unhealthy.

He called upon one of the giant ape puppets, then gave it a jade vial and instructed it to water those slightly withered spirit plants with the spirit liquid inside the vial once every fifteen days.

After that, Han Li made his way to the section of the garden where the Farsight Weeds were planted.

At this point, all of them had been matured to tens of thousands of years old, so they were fit to be used.

However, according to the Infernal Devilish Eyes secret technique, when it came to many of the ingredients used in the medicinal fluid, the older they were, the more efficacious they would be.

With that in mind, Han Li removed the Heaven Controlling Vial from around his neck, then tipped it upside-down above the Farsight Weeds.

A drop of green spirit liquid flowed out of the opening of the vial, and as it began to descend, Han Li flicked a finger in its direction, causing it to explode into a small cloud of mist that sprayed down evenly upon all of the Farsight Weeds.

Han Li watched for a moment as the spirit liquid fell upon the Farsight Weeds, then continued deeper into the medicine garden.

In a corner of the garden near the back was a plot of dark purple spirit soil that resembled mud from a swamp. The Dao Warrior primary beans growing inside were coming along quite nicely, and the entire area was enshrouded within a cloud of purple mist, giving it a rather indistinct appearance.

However, Han Li could tell from their auras that the primary beans were growing just fine.

Beyond this point in the spirit garden was a more recently expanded area, and even though it had already been watered with spirit liquid, it was still looking rather barren as nothing had been planted there.

All of a sudden, a voice rang out nearby.

"Can I offer you a piece of advice, Fellow Daoist Han?"

Han Li turned to discover Mo Guang making his way toward him, and he nodded in response.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang."

"The world's origin qi is able to circulate within this domain treasure, but it's ultimately still limited and can't quite compare with the outside world. Hence, if you plant too many things in here and exceed the limits of what this space can tolerate, that could result in spiritual qi failure, leading to the demise of this space," Mo Guang said.

"I've already considered that, I came here on this occasion to bolster the restrictions within the domain," Han Li replied with a nod.

"In that case, it seems that my advice was unwarranted," Mo Guang said with a smile.

"Not at all, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang. I appreciate you looking out for me. I managed to expel some baleful qi from my body and collect it, and I was planning to go to the bamboo pavilion to give it to you, but you've saved me the trouble," Han Li said as he tossed a black storage pouch through the air.

Mo Guang caught the storage pouch, and a hint of surprise appeared on his face as he inspected its contents.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Han."

"Don't worry about it," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand. "Let's go to the bamboo pavilion."

The two of them made their way to the pond in front of the purple bamboo pavilion, and Mo Guang entered the pavilion to continue his cultivation.

Meanwhile, Han Li walked a couple of laps around the pond, tossing some round stones that were riddled with array patterns into the pond at strategic locations.

After all of the stones were deposited, he flipped a hand over to produce an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, then carefully began marking the ground around the pond, injecting immortal spiritual power and sword qi into the ground with every single stroke.

Before long, a massive and complex array had taken shape around the pond, and Han Li exhaled as he stowed his sword away upon seeing this.

Immediately thereafter, a mid-grade Immortal Origin Stone appeared in his hand.

He gripped the stone tightly in his hand with a pained look in his eyes, but ultimately, he made his decision and tossed the Immortal Origin Stone into the pond, where it vanished into the water beneath the purplish-golden lotus flower.

Immediately thereafter, the water in the pond was stirred up into a frenzy, and one huge bubble after another emerged from beneath the lotus flower before popping in succession.

Bursts of dense purple mist emerged from the popped bubbles, permeating over the entire pond and inundating the arched bamboo bridge sitting over the pond.

Han Li felt an invisible breeze rise up from the center of the pond before sweeping through the air in all directions, releasing abundant spiritual qi that instantly struck him with a sense of relaxation and comfort.

After standing beside the pond for a moment, Han Li suddenly vanished from the spot.

Almost in the exact same instant, he appeared elsewhere in the domain, then flipped a hand over to produce an array plate that he had refined earlier. After installing some normal Immortal Origin Stones into the array plate, he buried it deep in the ground.

After that, he continued to make his way throughout the domain before burying more array plates that were fitted with Immortal Origin Stones.

By the time all of the array plates were planted, it was as if the domain had become a giant go board, and a metallic clang rang out as all of the array plates were activated in unison, sending pillars of light erupting into the sky.

At the center of the pond near the purple bamboo pavilion, the lotus flower lit up, and a fist-sized flower bud suddenly emerged beside it before blooming as well.

"Very impressive, Fellow Daoist Han. You've sacrificed a mid-grade Immortal Origin Stone to produce another lotus flower, and now, you won't have to worry about this domain running out of spiritual qi for at least the next century," Mo Guang praised as he stood in front of a window on the second floor of the bamboo pavilion.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he was quite pleased with his work.

A few minutes later, all of the phenomena taking place within the domain subsided, and Han Li examined the entire space to ensure that nothing was amiss before returning to his secret chamber.

By the time he emerged from the Flower Branch domain, it was already very late at night, and a beam of moonlight was shining down upon the ground in front of him through the hole in the ceiling above.

Han Li pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial before setting it down under the moonlight.

......

Over thirty years flew by in a flash in the Leisure Valley, and nothing really changed throughout the years.

During this time, Han Li purchased various ingredients for the medicinal liquid from the Transient Guild, then planted them in his spirit medicine garden before maturing them with the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial.

At this point, the primary ingredients required to refine the medicinal fluid had already been matured to a far more advanced age than the minimum threshold stipulated in the secret technique, so the medicinal fluid that he was able to refine was far more efficacious than normal.

At this moment, he was meditating with his eyes closed in his secret chamber.

On the stroke of midnight, all of the lamps in his secret chamber were suddenly snuffed out, plunging the room into complete darkness with the exception of the beam of moonlight coming through the hole in the ceiling.

Placed under the moonlight in front of Han Li was a clay vase with a large mouth but a thin neck, inside of which was some translucent purple liquid that was shimmering incessantly.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open, and a burst of bright blue light flashed through them.

At the same time, a layer of purplish-golden scales emerged over his skin, and the immense immortal spiritual power was being converted into inky black devilish qi before surging out of the gaps between his scales.

He began chanting the Infernal Devilish Eyes mantra internally while making a string of hand seals, then swept a sleeve over the vase sitting on the ground, and a ball of purple liquid immediately flew out from within before being guided into his eyes.

As soon as the liquid made contact with his eyes, Han Li immediately felt a burning pain that struck him with the reflexive urge to close his eyes, but he was able to resist the urge to do so.

Cleansing one's eyes with the ready-made medicinal fluid was the first step to cultivating the Infernal Devilish Eyes, and it was also an extremely important step that set the foundation for all of the subsequent steps.

Tears began to flow out of Han Li's eyes, carrying with them some tiny impurities that were otherwise undetectable, leaving two faint white streaks on his cheeks.

Through the cleansing process, the blue light in his eyes had become a little dimmer, but it had also become clearer, while his eyes themselves were becoming rather bloodshot.

All of a sudden, he switched to a different hand seal, then flipped his hands upward, raising both index fingers before extending them toward his own eyes.

Chapter 634: Strange Happenings

Right at this moment, the black devilish qi within the secret chamber began to swirl, forming two small vortexes, which then transformed into a pair of black spirals that surged directly toward Han Li's eyes.

The blue light glowing in Han Li's eyes instantly began to glow brighter, but it also became more murky and indistinct with this injection of devilish qi.

His eyes were like a pair of bottomless holes that were greedily devouring the devilish qi, and it didn't take long before they had become as dark as a pair of abysses.

At the same time, he made a strange hand seal with both hands and maintained it as he sat in a completely still fashion.

A series of purplish-golden halos emerged beneath his body before spreading outward.

......

Several years flew by in a flash.

Han Li remained seated with his legs crossed in his silent secret chamber, making the exact same hand seal as before.

The purplish-golden scales over his body had already faded, as had the devilish qi around him, and all that remained were the purplish-golden halos that were still constantly expanding outward.

Right at this moment, his eyes suddenly sprang open, and two pillars of golden light erupted out of his pupils, illuminating the entire secret chamber.

All of the tiny dust particles inside the secret chamber instantly became clearly visible, as was the case for all of the restrictions that he had previously set up.

Han Li raised his head to peer through the hole on the ceiling of his secret chamber, and he was able to see everything, from the white clouds in the sky to every single feather on the birds flying up above, and even the minute air currents created by the flapping of their wings.

It was as if nothing could remain hidden in the face of his eyes.

With that, he had achieved elementary mastery of the Infernal Devilish Eyes. As for whether these spirit eyes had any other abilities, that was still yet to be seen.

In any case, his eyesight had improved significantly compared with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

Moments later, all of the light in Han Li's eyes faded, and they reverted back to their original color.

A faint smile appeared on his face, and he adopted a disguise using his Dragon 5 mask, transforming into an ordinary-looking young man with a pale complexion.

After that, he stood up before taking a moment to stretch out his body, then emerged from his secret chamber.

He had gone into seclusion for a rather long time, and during this time, both Daoist Master Jingyang and Immortal Lord Hot Flame had come to visit him, only to be informed by a puppet that Han Li was in seclusion, and they had departed without disturbing him.

Hence, after coming out of seclusion, Han Li planned to pay the two of them a visit each.

It was winter in the Leisure Valley, and the entire valley was covered in a blanket of snow that was around a half a foot thick.

After making his way out of his cave abode, Han Li chose to walk through the valley on foot instead of taking flight, and he made his way deeper into the valley while appreciating the surrounding scenery.

All of a sudden, he noticed some buildings deep in the forest that hadn't been there before, and they had clearly been constructed during his seclusion.

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and right at this moment, a figure emerged from behind a large rock on the mountain path.

It had already stopped snowing, but the figure was still holding a dark red oil paper umbrella as he made his way toward the exit of the valley.

As the two drew closer to each other, Han Li was able to see that the approaching figure was an extremely handsome young man with a very pale complexion that was made to appear even paler in contrast with the large red cloak that he was wearing.

As the two passed each other by, the man gave Han Li a smile and a nod, but didn't say anything, and Han Li also responded in kind.

After the two had passed each other, they continued to walk in opposite directions, getting further and further away from one another.

Is he a new resident of the valley?

Han Li was rather perplexed, but he didn't think much of it as he continued to make his way deeper into the valley.

After walking for several kilometers along the mountain path, he arrived on the cliff where Immortal Lord Hot Flame's cave abode was situated, and he just so happened to spot a figure flying up from the cliff, setting off into the valley.

"Where are you going, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li hurriedly called out.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame faltered slightly upon hearing this, then immediately descended back down onto the ground as he greeted with a smile, "Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Li."

"I just came out of seclusion today, and I heard you came to visit me during my seclusion, so I'm here to return the favor," Han Li explained with a smile.

"I heard you were in seclusion during my visit, so I didn't disturb you," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a nod.

"Was there something you needed to speak to me about?" Han Li asked.

"It's nothing overly important. I just wanted to tell you to try and avoid using the elder badge of the Fire Leaf Sect to enter Jade Gathering City in the immediate future," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said.

"Why is that?" Han Li asked.

"Jade Gathering City has not been very peaceful these past two hundred years. The Black Mountain Immortal Palace is conducting more stringent examinations on people entering the city, and I was worried that you could land yourself in trouble if you weren't careful," Immortal Lord Hot Flame explained.

"What's been happening in the city?" Han Li asked, thinking that the unrest must've resulted from a continuation of the events that had ensued following the auction.

"It's a bit of a long story. Everyone just so happens to be meeting up today, so why don't you come with me, and we'll discuss this with everyone else?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame proposed with a smile.

Han Li could only suppress his curiosity for now and depart with Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

Thus, the two of them rose up into the air together and quickly arrived on a spacious cliff deep in the valley.

The cliff was situated on a mountain face on the right side of the valley, and it protruded out of the mountain face by several hundred feet. There was an octagonal pavilion constructed on the cliff, and it was also covered in a thick layer of snow.

Inside the pavilion was a stone table with three figures already gathered around it, namely Yu Ziqi, Mo Wuxue, and Duan Yuzai.

After everyone had exchanged some greetings, Duan Yuzai turned to Han Li as he asked, "When did you come out of seclusion, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"I just came out of seclusion today, and it seems that I did so at just the right time," Han Li replied with a smile.

"I heard from Fellow Daoist Jingyang that..."

Before Yu Ziqi had a chance to finish, Mo Wuxue tugged on his sleeve to cut him off, and he immediately realized that he had brought up a rather sensitive subject, upon which a guilty look appeared on his face.

"It's fine, it's not like this is a taboo subject. The pills I refined did indeed fail to achieve the intended effect, I'll just have to search for another solution in the future," Han Li said with a carefree smile.

"My apologies, Fellow Daoist Li. It appears I overreacted," Mo Wuxue said with a faint smile.

"Not at all, Celestial Maiden Mo. I should thank you for looking out for me. Speaking of Fellow Daoist Jingyang, where is he right now?" Han Li asked.

"Fellow Daoist Jingyang said that he had some things to take care of, and he hasn't been back to the valley for over a hundred years," Yu Ziqi replied.

Han Li speculated that he most likely had some important duties to take care of in the Hundred Creations Mountain, so he didn't dwell on this subject.

"How unfortunate for him. I just so happened to bring some of my Red Mulberry Wine today. Would everyone care to have a taste?"

Everyone's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this.

Everyone returned to their seats, while Han Li brought out a jar of wine and filled some cups. As he did so, he noticed that Yu Ziqi wasn't playing his guqin as he normally did, nor had Duan Yuzai set up his go board, and his brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"By the way, what were you saying earlier, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame? What's been happening recently?" Han Li asked.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame had already raised his cups to his lips, but he set it down again as he replied, "I'm sure you've already noticed that many new residents have settled in our Leisure Valley of late."

"I did indeed encounter a young man in a large red cloak on the way here. He must be one of those new residents, right?" Han Li asked.

"That man's name is Feng Qingyuan, and he's only one of about fifty to sixty new residents who have moved into the valleys of Relaxation Mountain over the past two hundred years," Duan Yuzai replied.

"There were that many?" Han Li exclaimed.

While people were free to come and go as they pleased in Relaxation Mountain, the mountain range never had a large number of residents. After all, it was very rare for someone to be able to settle in one place and give up on aspirations of future cultivation progression, even if the endeavor were clearly futile.

Hence, this was a very abnormal turn of events.

"If that's the only change, then it wouldn't be all that noteworthy, as long as everyone abides by the rules and doesn't interfere with others. However, there have been many strange happenings in the mountain range, and many people have been disappearing from the valleys," Mo Wuxue explained.

"Just last month, the cave abode of a pair of Dao partners was destroyed overnight in the nearby Flower Moon Valley, and both of them disappeared," Yu Ziqi added.

Han Li had met the pair in question, and he knew that they were a pair of early-True Immortal cultivators.

"Has there been any shared trait among the people who've disappeared?"

"Not at all. From Golden Immortals to Deity Transformation cultivators, from beautiful female cultivators to elderly men... There doesn't seem to be any rhyme or reason to the disappearances," Yu Ziqi replied.

"Has no one investigated this matter?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"How? All of the people residing in the mountain range are here to live lives unburdened by responsibilities, and there are no factions or unified organizations here, so who's going to investigate this matter? There have only been some private investigations, and they haven't yielded any useful leads.

“On top of that, like Fellow Daoist Ziqi said, it seems like there's no rhyme or reason to the victims, so it's almost impossible to pinpoint anything," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a wry smile.

"Exactly. Who knows if those people simply left the valley? Having said that, in the past, people would generally inform their good friends in the mountain range prior to the departure, and there's never been such an unannounced mass exodus like this before," Yu Ziqi chimed in.

Chapter 635: Another Incident

"The only thing that we can be almost certain of is that these events have something to do with the new residents who've moved in over the past two centuries. After all, the valley has been a very peaceful place prior to their arrival," Duan Yuzai said.

"In that case, why hasn't anyone investigated these new residents?" Han Li asked.

"On the surface, these people all appear to be very normal, and due to the rules in the valley, everyone was initially reluctant to pry into these matters. However, with all these strange occurrences taking place of late, some people have begun investigating, but the results of their investigations are extremely bizarre, and many strange rumors have come out of these investigations," Yu Ziqi sighed.

"What are these rumors?" Han Li asked.

"Some say the mountain range has been infiltrated by man-eating devils, some say this is the work of bloodthirsty evil cultivators, some proclaim that the Immortal Palace sent spies here to disrupt the peace and eradicate the community here as it's outside of their control, and some have even speculated that all of this is related to the Silver Fox case that took place in Jade Gathering City.

“They say that Silver Fox wasn't able to flee the Black Mountain Immortal Region, so he's hiding in Relaxation Mountain. In any case, it's all a bunch of unsubstantiated nonsense," Duan Yuzai sighed.

"If you ask me, I think these rumors were intentionally spread by the perpetrators to serve as red herrings that throw people off their trail," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as he took a sip of wine.

Han Li's mind was racing upon hearing this.

If these strange happenings did indeed have something to do with the Silver Fox incident, then there really was a chance that the perpetrators had been sent into the mountain range by the Black Mountain Immortal Palace. If that were the case, then things would most likely only continue to grow more chaotic in the future.

"Relaxation Mountain has never fallen under the jurisdiction of the Immortal Palace or any sect, so it's essentially a lawless place. The peace here has only been maintained thanks to the rules established by that powerful senior, but at this point, there's no longer anyone around to enforce the rules, so I'm afraid things will only get worse from here," Mo Wuxue sighed, and everyone fell into a solemn silence upon hearing this.

All of a sudden, Immortal Lord Hot Flame slammed his wine cup heavily down onto the table as he declared, "Even if the sky comes falling down, there will be others above us to catch it before it falls on us, so what's there to worry about? It's not like this is the only place of its kind in the entire True Immortal Realm. If things become too dangerous here, we can just go somewhere else!"

"That may apply to all of us, but as the grand elder of the Fire Leaf Sect, I doubt that you can just leave this place anytime you please," Han Li jibed with an amused smile.

"Why do you have to be so direct, Fellow Daoist Li?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame complained with a displeased expression.

Everyone else was quite amused to see this, and the solemn atmosphere was slightly alleviated.

After having some more wine, everyone chatted for about half a day longer before parting ways.

No further mention was made of the disappearances that had taken place in the mountain range, but it was clear that it was still constantly in the back of everyone's minds.

Han Li departed with Immortal Lord Hot Flame, and as they parted ways, the latter once again cautioned him against using his identity as an outer sect elder of the Fire Leaf Sect in case he ran into any trouble as a result.

As for the exact reasons, he didn't go into further detail, and Han Li didn't ask any questions, either.

Upon returning to his cave abode, Han Li entered his Flower Branch abode to check on his spirit medicines and Dao Warriors, then went into seclusion in his secret chamber to continue working on his time-attribute cultivation arts.

However, only about half a year passed by before an incident took place in the Leisure Valley.

One morning, Han Li was planning to make a trip to his spirit medicine garden to water his Dao Warrior primary beans when he discovered that Duan Yuzai had come to visit.

Hence, he opened the entrance of his cave abode to see Duan Yuzai, and he was just about to extend a warm greeting, but it was clear from Duan Yuzai's urgent expression that he was in no mood for small talk.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Duan? Why do you look so distressed?"

"Yu Ziqi was attacked and is on the verge of death! Please save him, Fellow Daoist Li!" Duan Yuzai replied in an urgent voice.

"Where is he right now?" Han Li hurriedly asked.

"He's on Light Breeze Cliff," Duan Yuzai immediately replied, and Han Li instantly vanished from the spot.

Duan Yuzai faltered slightly upon seeing this, then also departed as a streak of light.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li appeared on Light Breeze Cliff, and he immediately noticed that a large patch of snow on the edge of the cliff had been soaked in blood and frozen into dark red ice crystals.

In the middle of the bloodstained ice crystals laid a young man with his white robe completely drenched in blood. His complexion was deathly pale, and his eyes were completely glazed over.

Mo Wuxue was kneeling in the snow beside him, looking just as pale, and she had conjured up a silver light barrier that encompassed his body while also injecting him with a steady supply of immortal spiritual power.

"Fellow Daoist Li!"

A glimmer of hope instantly appeared in Mo Wuxue's distraught eyes at the sight of Han Li.

Han Li gave her a nod, then quickly made his way over to Yu Ziqi before reaching into the silver light barrier to clasp a hand around his wrist. At the same time, purple light flashed within his eyes as he roamed his grave over Yu Ziqi's body.

As he inspected Yu Ziqi's physical conditions, his brows became tightly furrowed, while a grim look appeared on his face before slowly turning into anger.

Mo Wuxue could tell from his reaction that the situation was dire, and her complexion paled even further.

"It's alright, he can still be saved," Han Li said.

Mo Wuxue's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this, following which tears began to well up in her eyes, and she made no attempt to conceal her feelings any longer as she turned her gaze back to Yu Ziqi.

Meanwhile, Duan Yuzai was standing a bit further away, and only after hearing that Yu Ziqi could still be saved did he hurriedly approach Han Li's trio.

Han Li withdrew his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and his brows remained tightly furrowed as he flipped a hand over to produce a translucent, jade-like pill, then gently pried Yu Ziqi's mouth open by squeezing his cheeks before feeding him the pill.

However, Yu Ziqi displayed no reaction, nor was he able to swallow the pill, so Han Li had to manually guide the pill down his esophagus and into his stomach.

Immediately thereafter, a layer of faint white light emerged over his lower abdomen before flowing toward all of his limbs and meridians.

Mo Wuxue could hear a string of faint cracks ringing out across Yu Ziqi's entire body, and a perplexed look appeared on her face as she turned to Han Li.

"That's the sound of his bones reconnecting and mending. As I'm sure you could already see, all of his bones and meridians have been snapped, and his soul has also been completely ravaged as a result of a forced soul search. At the moment, his body is like a dilapidated house that's full of holes, and it's extremely fragile," Han Li explained.

"That's why we asked you to come here instead of carrying him to your cave abode," Duan Yuzai said with a nod.

"All I fed him just now was a True Immortal Stage pill to help mend his bone and meridians, and only after that will I be able to administer further treatment. In any case, it seems that he should be able to survive now," Han Li sighed.

Both Mo Wuxue and Duan Yuzai were very relieved to hear this, but they were still no less concerned.

After all of the cracking sounds faded, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a white jade vial, which was filled with a type of purple liquid.

This was a soul nourishment liquid that he had refined using the Soulbirth Flower. Back when he refined his Earthly Deity Avatar, he discovered that this liquid was very effective for treating spiritual damage, so he had refined some more.

However, thanks to his Spirit Refinement Technique, his soul had become more and more powerful, so there was never a need for him to use this liquid himself.

He removed the stopper of the vial, then poured all of its contents into Yu Ziqi's mouth, upon which a peculiar fragrance spread through the air.

After that, Han Li brushed a hand over Yu Qi's eyelids to close his eyes.

"Who could've possibly harbored such a vendetta against him that they would beat him into such terrible condition?" Mo Wuxue asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"Perhaps there's no personal vendetta at all. Perhaps the perpetrator only wanted to secure some information from him," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

"From the looks of it, they succeeded," Duan Yuzai sighed.

"Not necessarily. Judging from the damage sustained by Fellow Daoist Yu's soul, the perpetrator most likely triggered some type of restriction while using a soul search technique on him, thereby detonating his consciousness.

“However, it's also exactly because of this that the perpetrator seems to have flown into a rage and broke all of Fellow Daoist Yu's bones, then left him here to die," Han Li analyzed with a grim expression.

Mo Wuxue shuddered slightly upon hearing this, and her hands had already balled up into tight fists in her sleeves.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he hurriedly crouched down before pressing a palm down onto Yu Ziqi's glabella.

A burst of invisible fluctuations surged out of the palm of his hand, and after a thorough examination, he withdrew his hand as he murmured to himself, "I see..."

"What is it, Fellow Daoist Li?" Mo Wuxue hurriedly asked.

"The perpetrator even went as far as to plant a restriction on Fellow Daoist Yu's nascent soul, preventing it from being able to escape his body, so if his physical body were to perish, then his nascent soul would also meet its demise, eliminating any possibility for it to escape and possess someone else in the future.

“However, you managed to save him by sealing his consciousness in a timely fashion while also injecting him with immortal spiritual power, and only then was he able to survive long enough for me to get here," Han Li said.

A puzzled look appeared on Mo Wuxue's face upon hearing this.

"His consciousness has been sealed? I didn't do that at all, all I did was inject immortal spiritual power into his body."

Han Li turned to Duan Yuzai with an inquisitive gaze upon hearing this.

Chapter 636: Sword Integration

"It wasn't me, either. Celestial Maiden Mo was the first one to have discovered Fellow Daoist Yu, and she was worried that you could be in seclusion, so she sent me a message, asking me to go look for you," Duan Yuzai explained.

"With all of this recent unrest, I was planning to meditate for a while, but I was unable to enter a tranquil state, so I came here in the morning, and I discovered him laying in the snow. At the time, I thought he was already dead," Mo Wuxue sighed.

Han Li didn't say anything further upon hearing this.

He rested the palm of his hand down onto Yu Ziqi's glabella to conduct a further examination, then rose to his feet with a perplexed look in his eyes, wondering exactly who it was that had sealed his consciousness.

"How is he right now, Fellow Daoist Li?" Mo Wuxue asked.

"His body and soul have been stabilized for now, but he's still not out of the woods yet. Take him back to my cave abode. I'm going to need to administer extensive treatment to him before he can truly be saved," Han Li said.

"Thank you, Fellow Daost Li," Mo Wuxue said in an earnest manner.

Han Li's gaze roamed back and forth between Mo Wuxue and Yu Ziqi for a moment, and it occurred to him that this near-death experience may have just been a blessing for Yu Ziqi.

With that in mind, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light hat picked up Yu Ziqi before carrying him back to his cave abode.

......

Close to a month later.

Daoist Master Jingyang had only just returned to the valley when he received a message from Han Li, and by the time he arrived at Han Li's cave abode, Immortal Lord Hot Flame and the others were already gathered there.

Just like Mo Guang, Daoist Xie had also been deposited in the Flower Branch domain, so there were only some puppets and Dao Warriors left in the cave abode, and Yu Ziqi was staying in the room previously occupied by Mo Guang.

Following this period of recovery, his aura had stabilized a little, but he still wasn't showing any signs of waking up as the spiritual damage that he had sustained was extremely severe.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Daoist Master Jingyang were always bickering with each other, but in a rare display of camaraderie, both of them united to declare that they were going to find the perpetrator and give them a taste of their own medicine.

"I told all of you that there was going to be some unrest, but I didn't think that things would become so bad so quickly," Daoist Master Jingyang sighed.

"Do you know something that we don't, Fellow Daoist Jingyang?" Mo Wuxue asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"The information that I have access to aren't exactly secrets. As long as you're willing to spend some Immortal Origin Stones, you can purchase this information from Jade Gathering City," Daoist Master Jingyang replied.

"None of us have been to Jade Gathering City for some time now, so we'll be relying on you to relay this information to us, Fellow Daoist Jingyang," Han Li said.

"Hurry up and spit it out!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame urged.

"I'm sure all of you have heard about the Silver Fox incident. After the incident, some other things happened, and there's a chance that the palace master of the Black Mountain Immortal Palace used this as an excuse to join forces with the immortal envoy stationed in Jade Gathering City, exerting pressure upon the itinerant cultivator who established the rules of Relaxation Mountain so that he would allow Immortal Palace cultivators to access and search the mountain range as they please," Daoist Master Jingyang revealed.

"So you're saying that the perpetrator in this case could be someone from the Black Mountain Immortal Palace?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"I said no such thing. All I'm saying is that the Black Mountain Immortal Palace has sent people into Relaxation Mountain to ruin the peace here. In all honesty, there are even more people from the Robe Change Order in the mountain range, and neither of those organizations are to be messed with," Daoist Master Jingyang said.

"It's not like members of the Reincarnation Palace have only recently infiltrated the valley, but none of them have ever disturbed the peace. If you ask me, I still think the Immortal Palace cultivators are to blame," Duan Yuzai said.

Just like the Ubiquitous Pavilion and the Transient Guild, the Robe Change Order was also a far-reaching subsidiary power of the Reincarnation Palace.

"Could it be that Fellow Daoist Yu is a member of the Reincarnation Palace?" Han Li asked.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Duan Yuzai turned to Daoist Master Jingyang and Mo Wuxue upon hearing this. One of them was Yu Ziqi's closest friend in the valley, while the other was Yu Ziqi's romantic interest, but neither of them seemed to know the answer to that question.

"There's no point in making all this empty speculation. Let's ask Fellow Daoist Yu when he wakes up," Mo Wuxue said.

"In any case, all of us have to be more careful from now on," Daoist Master Jingyang said.

After everyone departed, Han Li began to feel more and more uneasy, and he no longer felt like this was a safe place to stay.

However, if he were to leave the Leisure Valley at a time like this, he would most likely only be attracting the attention of the Immortal Palace cultivators, so he would just have to stay put and wait for now.

On top of that, he also had to stay with Yu Ziqi for a long time to administer his treatment.

After some contemplation, he began working on removing the restriction on Yu Ziqi's nascent soul.

Over five years passed by in a flash.

One morning, Han Li was seated in his secret chamber, holding his Heaven Controlling Vial in one hand and the Profound Heavenly Gourd in the other.

He opened the Heaven Controlling Vial before tipping a drop of green spirit liquid onto the mouth of the gourd.

Over the years, the mouth of the gourd had been steadily nourished by the green liquid to the point that it was almost completely blending in with the rest of the gourd, but Han Li still felt like it wasn't fully mature yet.

A pleasant sound rang out from the gourd, and the drop of green spirit liquid was instantly absorbed by it.

Immediately thereafter, the gourd began to radiate incredibly bright green light, and all of the countless geren runes on its surface began to flash incessantly.

At the same time, an unfathomable burst of law power fluctuations surged through the surrounding area, and a faint pop rang out from the mouth of the gourd.

To Han Li's surprise, the gourd had opened on its own without any outside force.

Does this mean it's completely matured?

Before Han Li had a chance to draw any conclusions, a burst of green light shot out of the mouth of the gourd, transforming into a green flame that enveloped the entire gourd while keeping it suspended in mid-air.

Some time later, the flame began to shrink before finally vanishing altogether, and the gourd was left looking as if it had been reborn anew. It had become entirely as translucent as jade, and it had a warm and smooth tactile sensation to the touch.

A hint of elation welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he was just about to conduct a closer examination when a burst of burning pain suddenly arose in one of his arms.

He hurriedly pulled up his sleeve and looked down to discover that a faint green sword mark had appeared on his arm, and it was none other than the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword that had already been missing for many years.

Immediately thereafter, he felt all of the blood in his arm converging toward the sword mark, and as a result, the previously indistinct sword mark was gradually becoming clearer and clearer.

Is the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword about to return?

Han Li was ecstatic to see this.

Even though the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword was a treasure from a lower realm, it was still a Profound Heavenly Treasure that encompassed the law powers of an entire realm, making it equivalent to an Essential Immortal Treasure in the True Immortal Realm, so it had to be harboring many secrets that had remained hidden to him up to this point.

Right at this moment, the pain in his arm intensified even further, and the green sword mark suddenly tore through his skin as a streak of green light, then instantly flew into the gourd through its mouth.

Han Li was very startled by this turn of events, and he immediately grabbed onto the gourd before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

The green vortex within the internal space of the gourd was still slowly revolving as usual, and the seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were hovering peacefully within the vortex, giving off a faint azure glow.

After searching through this space, Han Li was unable to find the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword, so he extended his spiritual sense further into the second space within the gourd.

As soon as he did this, he was immediately struck by a sense of disorientation, and he felt as if there were bursts of green light flashing incessantly in front of his eyes.

He focused his gaze directly forward to find the green ball hovering within this space, and it was currently fluctuating in brightness while releasing a series of green halos that were giving off peculiar energy fluctuations.

A green sword-shaped mark had appeared on the ball, and it was none other than the mark of the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword.

As he attempted to extend his spiritual sense toward the sword mark, the latter instantly released a burst of green light that exploded to shatter the spiritual sense being extended toward it.

Han Li immediately gave a muffled groan as his eyes sprang open, and he was gasping for air.

His head was ringing incessantly while throbbing with agony, and he hurriedly closed his eyes to recuperate.

A long while later, his complexion had largely returned to normal, and he opened his eyes as he massaged his own throbbing glabella with a contemplative expression.

He didn't know how it had happened, but it appeared that the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword had fused as one with the gourd.

Instead of a resurrection for the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword, it seemed that the destructive law powers within it had been sucked into the gourd, and he couldn't help but wonder if this would somehow alter the gourd's properties and abilities.

Chapter 637: Laying Low

With that in mind, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a fire-attribute immortal sword that circled around within the secret chamber before hurtling directly toward him.

At the same time, Han Li patted the underside of the Profound Heavenly Gourd, and it immediately turned so that its mouth was facing the oncoming sword, then released a burst of green light toward it.

As soon as the fiery sword was bound by the green light, the former instantly drew to a complete halt, while the flames on its surface were quickly snuffed out.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, then made a hand seal to try and extricate the flying sword out of the green light, but as soon as a layer of flames re-emerged over its surface, a beam of dark green light instantly shot out of the gourd to completely pulverize the sword.

The shattered fragments of the sword were then disintegrated even further within the green light before being sucked into the gourd.

All of this had taken place so quickly that Han Li was left a little dumbstruck by what he had seen, and he hurriedly extended his spiritual sense into the gourd, where he discovered the remnants of the fire-attribute immortal sword within the second space inside the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

Those remnants were currently adhered to the energy fluctuations around the green ball, and they were slowly revolving while releasing specks of translucent light.

The spiritual power that they contained was slowly being stripped away to reciprocate the gourd, and to Han Li's surprise, he noticed a tiny crimson speck of light hovering in the air outside of the green ball with faint fire law power fluctuations emanating from it.

Clearly, the law powers of the fire-attribute immortal sword hadn't been absorbed by the gourd. Instead, it had simply been stored away.

Han Li was becoming more curious by the second, and he wanted to see just how the Profound Heavenly Gourd's abilities had changed, but right at this moment, he suddenly raised an eyebrow as he withdrew his spiritual sense from the gourd, then turned to the door of his secret chamber.

After that, he stowed the Profound Heavenly Gourd away, them emerged from his secret chamber before making his way into the secret chamber previously occupied by Mo Guang.

As soon as he entered the room, he saw Yu Ziqi struggling to try and sit up on the bed, but it seemed that he was still too feeble and weak to do so.

"Don't be in a hurry to get up, Fellow Daoist Yu. You sustained very severe spiritual damage, so you must be feeling very dizzy right now," Han Li said as he made his way over to Yu Ziqi before gently lowering him back down onto the bed.

"You were the one who saved me, right, Fellow Daoist Li? I could sense that it was you, but I just wasn't able to wake up and thank you."

Yu Ziqi's speech was very smooth and steady, but his eyes were still looking a little dull, and he also seemed to be having difficulty focusing his gaze on Han Li.

"There's no need to thank me. Do you recall who it was that attacked you?" Han Li asked with a grim expression.

"I've been pondering this question ever since I regained my consciousness, but I can't recall who my attacker was. I only have a vague recollection of them interrogating me about someone in the valley, but I can't remember who exactly that person was, either," Yu Ziqi replied with a shake of his head, and it seemed that he couldn't even recall the horrific torment that he had been subjected to.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he couldn't help but wonder if the perpetrator had been trying to interrogate Yu Ziqi about him.

After all, not only was he on the Heavenly Court's Immortal Slaying List, he was also a member of the Reincarnation Palace and had cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique, all of which were crimes punishable by death.

He had to go to great lengths to buy himself these past few centuries of peace and serenity, but he wasn't sure if he could continue to stay in the Leisure Valley at this rate.

"How long has it been since I was attacked?" Yu Ziqi asked.

"Not long, only just over five years," Han Li replied.

"So I slept for five whole years... I really must thank you, Fellow Daoist Li. Not only did you save my life, you've been looking after me for the past five years as well. I truly don't know how to repay you," Yu Ziqi sighed.

"I'm not the one that you should feel indebted to. The one who actually found you and saved your life is Celestial Maiden Mo. If it wasn't for her, you would've perished before I had a chance to save you, and she's also been paying you frequent visits over the past five years," Han Li said.

A hint of emotion appeared in Yu Ziqi's eyes for the first time upon hearing this, and he hurriedly asked, "Is that true?"

"Are you saying I would lie to you about something like this?" Han Li countered.

"Of course not, but..."

Han Li was starting to grow a little disgruntled, and he asked, "You were even able to let go of your attachment to pursuing the Great Dao, why can't you get over something minor like this? Are you waiting for Celestial Maiden Mo to confess to you instead?"

"Of course not," Yu Ziqi hurriedly replied.

"Think about it: if we weren't able to save you this time, would you not have regretted not confessing your feelings to Celestial Maiden Mo?" Han Li asked.

Han Li didn't have much experience when it came to romance and relationships, but he knew that the man had to take more of the initiative in such matters, and that was precisely the case between him and Nangong Wan.

Yu Ziqi was silent for a long while upon hearing this, then finally sighed in an earnest voice, "Thank you, Fellow Daoist Li. I know what I need to do now."

Han Li could see that Yu Ziqi had been truly convinced, so he didn't dwell on this subject any longer.

He fed Yu Ziqi a soul nurturing pill, then instructed him to rest and refrain from strenuous activity before sending him away.

Following Yu Ziqi's departure, Han Li's brows furrowed tightly with concern.

A month after Yu Ziqi's departure, Han Li also began to prepare for his departure from the Leisure Valley and even the entire Black Mountain Immortal Region as a whole.

Several more years passed by in a flash, and the disappearances and attacks taking place in the Floating Cloud Mountain Range were only becoming more and more frequent.

As a result, many of the cultivators residing here had begun to leave, and at this point, Han Li had also already packed up all of his belongings.

He wanted to leave a long time ago, but he refrained from doing so in order to avoid drawing attention to himself.

However, now that many people had already begun to leave the mountain range, he now had an excuse to leave himself.

Of course, if he were to detect someone following him, then he certainly wouldn't mind luring them into a secluded place before permanently silencing them.

After meditating in his secret chamber for some time, Han Li left his cave abode, then made his way over to the pavilion where he often met up with Immortal Lord Hot Flame and the others.

To his surprise, Immortal Lord Hot Flame and the others were already gathered in the pavilion at this moment, and they were all discussing something with rather grim expressions.

Yu Ziqi was also among them, and he was looking a little pale. Mo Wuxue was standing beside him, and the two of them were speaking to each other in hushed voices.

Everyone stopped talking upon seeing Han Li, and Daoist Master Jingyang beckoned to him as he said, "You came at just the right time, Fellow Daoist Li. We were just about to go and look for you."

"What are all of you doing here?" Han Li asked as he made his way into the pavilion.

"The valley is becoming more and more dangerous. Three fellow daoists were attacked just last month alone, and one of them was even killed," Duan Yuzai said with a grim expression.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

In order to avoid drawing attention to himself, Han Li had been in seclusion in his cave abode all these past years, and he had made no attempt to unearth the root cause behind the unrest in the Floating Cloud Mountain Range.

It seemed that the situation was even more chaotic than before.

"Indeed. The Floating Cloud Mountain Range is no longer the place it once was, and we're all gathered here to discuss what we should do from here," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed.

"What are you planning to do, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li asked.

"What else can I do but return to the sect for now? At the very least, it should be a bit safer over there," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a wry smile.

"I'm also planning to leave for a while and go to Auspicious Cloud City. I have some acquaintances there that I can live with for now," Duan Yuzai sighed.

"How about you, Fellow Daoist Li?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked.

"I really don't want to leave the Leisure Valley, but it is indeed no longer the place it once was, so I'm also planning to leave just like all of you," Han Li replied.

"Do you have a place to go, Fellow Daoist Li? If not, why don't you come to our Hundred Creations Mountain for now? Your safety will definitely be ensured there, and if you have any other requests, feel free to state them, and I'll do my best to satisfy you," Daoist Master Jingyang proposed.

At this point, Daoist Master Jingyang had already revealed his identity to Immortal Lord Hot Flame and the others, so they weren't perplexed to hear this offer.

"Thank you for the invitation, Fellow Daoist Jingyang, but I've already decided on where I want to go next," Han Li replied, turning down the offer in a tactful manner.

"I see. If you ever change your mind, feel free to come and find me at the Hundred Creations Mountain at any time," Daoist Master Jingyang said with a hint of disappointment in his eyes.

"What are your plans, Fellow Daoist Yu?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

Yu Ziqi turned to look at Mo Wuxue with a hesitant expression, while the latter remained silent as she stared out into the distance.

"Fellow Daoist Yu, if you and Celestial Maiden Mo don't have anywhere to go for now, then you can also come to our Hundred Creations Mountain," Daoist Master Jingyang said as he turned to Mo Wuxue and Yu Ziqi with a smile.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Jingyang, but I have no plans of leaving this place for now," Mo Wuxue replied with a shake of her head.

Everyone was quite surprised to hear this with the exception of Yu Ziqi, who seemed to have already been aware of her decision.

Chapter 638: Nine Grades of Immortal Treasures

"Celestial Maiden Mo, the Floating Cloud Mountain Range is fraught with peril right now. Even for a Golden Immortal like yourself, it's far too dangerous to remain here," Duan Yuzai urged.

Daoist Master Jingyang and the others also chimed in in agreement, trying to dissuade her from her decision, but Mo Wuxue shook her head with a determined expression as she said, "Thank you for your concern, everyone, but I've already sworn a vow to remain in the Leisure Valley and wait for the return of a certain person."

Yu Ziqi's complexion paled slightly as he lowered his head upon hearing this.

Han Li naturally noticed this reaction from Yu Ziqi, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly, but he didn't say anything.

It seemed that Yu Ziqi had already confessed his feelings to Mo Wuxue, but there appeared to be some obstacle standing between them.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame and the others exchanged a glance with one another, and all of them chose to remain silent as well.

It was simply not in their place to be commenting on the relationships of others.

"Having said that, please take Fellow Daoist Yu with you to the Hundred Creations Mountain, Fellow Daoist Jingyang. He still hasn't fully recovered from his injuries, so he needs some more time to rest and recuperate," Mo Wuxue said.

Daoist Master Jingyang was just about to reply when Yu Ziqi sprang to his feet and declared, "If you're not leaving, then I'm staying here with you."

A complex look appeared in Mo Wuxue's eyes upon hearing this, and she lowered her head as she heaved a forlorn sigh, but didn't turn him down.

A slightly awkward silence descended upon the pavilion.

"Seeing as both of you have already made up your minds, we won't say anything further. I'll set up some Hundred Creations Mountain restrictions around the valley later, and I'm sure that'll at least be somewhat effective in intimidating whoever it is that's been wreaking havoc in the valley," Daoist Master Jingyang said.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Jingyang," Mo Wuxue said with a grateful expression.

Just because she had chosen to stay here didn't mean that she didn't fear death. The Hundred Creations Mountain was vastly renowned near Jade Gathering City and throughout the entire Black Mountain Immortal Region, so with this restriction in place, they would be much safer in the valley.

Yu Ziqi also hurriedly rose to his feet to express his gratitude.

Everyone chatted for a while longer before parting ways, and Daoist Master Jingyang flew out of the valley to begin setting up the restriction.

Mo Wuxue also returned to her cave abode, and before long, Han Li and Yu Ziqi were the only ones left in the pavilion.

Meanwhile, Yu Ziqi stared after Mo Wuxue with a dazed expression, only withdrawing his gaze after she had already entered her cave abode.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this, but there was no further part that he could play in their relationship.

Even though he had only been with these people for a few centuries, he had found some warmth and friendship here, both of which were extremely rare and precious things in the harsh world of cultivation, and that was why he was willing to help them.

Perhaps only by casting aside the fulfillment of certain desires could one hope to regain some precious things that they had lost in the past, but ultimately, such a lifestyle was destined to be nothing more than a fleeting affair.

"Fellow Daoist Yu, these pills are for you, and they should be helpful for your recovery," Han Li said as he summoned a storage ring before handing it to Yu Ziqi.

"I already owe you a great deal for saving my life, I can't accept any more of your pills. I'll be fully recovered in a few more years at most, so I won't waste your precious pills," Yu Ziqi hurriedly refused.

"These pills are no longer very useful to me, so don't turn them down, Fellow Daoist Yu. The sooner you recover from your injuries, the less that Celestial Maiden Mo has to worry about you," Han Li said as he set the storage ring down beside Yu Ziqi.

Yu Ziqi was silent for a moment upon hearing this, and a dejected look appeared on his face as he sighed, "I have only myself to blame for being so weak..."

"Don't be disheartened, Fellow Daoist Yu. You possess decent cultivation aptitude, so it's not entirely impossible for you to reach the Golden Immortal Stage someday," Han Li said.

"Perhaps," Yu Ziqi replied with a wry smile.

"I'll be leaving the valley now. Farewell and take care, Fellow Daoist Yu," Han Li declared as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

"You're leaving so soon?" Yu Ziqi asked with a surprised expression.

Han Li nodded silently in response, then promptly departed.

Yu Ziqi stared after Han Li for some time, then picked up the storage ring, and as soon as he injected his spiritual sense into it, he was instantly rooted to the spot.

Not only did the storage ring contain some recovery pills, it also contained a Bell Valley Pill that could stabilize one's dantian, as well as several types of pills that could assist one in reaching the Golden Immortal Stage.

These pills should be more than sufficient to help him break through his Golden Immortal Stage bottleneck.

I'll never forget what you've done for me, Fellow Daoist Li, Yu Ziqi thought to himself, gripping the storage ring tightly in his hand as he vowed to repay Han Li in the future if the opportunity ever arose.

......

As Han Li flew out of the Leisure Valley, he was greeted by Daoist Master Jingyang, who seemed to have been waiting for him.

"You're leaving so soon, Fellow Daoist Li?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked.

"I have to leave sooner or later, and I've never been one to procrastinate," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Are you really not going to consider joining our Hundred Creations Mountain, Fellow Daoist Li? If you have any requests, please do state them," Daoist Master Jingyang said, making one final effort to recruit Han Li.

"Thank you for thinking so highly of me, Fellow Daoist Jingyang, but as opposed to joining any power, I much prefer to be free," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"I knew from the very beginning that you were a free spirit. In that case, I suppose this is where we'll part ways for now," Daoist Master Jingyang sighed as he shook his head with a wry smile.

Han Li offered no response.

"Having said that, you and I are good friends, and competition between the deputy mountain masters of the Hundred Creations Mountain has always been extremely fierce, so if I need your help with something in the future, you'd better not refuse!" Daoist Master Jingyang said.

"Of course," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Before you leave, I'm afraid I have a piece of disappointing news for you. I've done my best to search for baleful qi expulsion methods, but to no avail," Daoist Master Jingyang revealed.

Han Li was a little disappointed to hear this, and he said, "That's fine. That was always going to be a difficult task. Thank you for your efforts so far, and please continue your search. Also, there's something that I'd like you to source for me."

"What is it, Fellow Daoist Li?" Daoist Master Jingyang asked.

"Items that contain time law powers, whether that be materials, immortal treasures, anything is fine," Han Li replied.

Having gained eight time law threads last time, the rate of recovery of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had increased significantly, and at this point, all of the runes had recovered.

Of course, while Han Li was very pleased to see this, his main objective for trying to secure more time law threads was to see whether accruing a sufficient number of them will actually allow him to physically transmigrate using the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Daoist Master Jingyang raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he flipped a hand over to summon a small golden lock.

The golden lock was giving off incredibly formidable time law power fluctuations, far superior to that of the Time Severing Flagon and the azure wooden ruler that Han Li had previously acquired, and his eyes immediately lit up at the sight of it.

"This is a time-attribute immortal treasure. It's only a ninth-grade one, but given that it contains one of the three paramount laws, its value is equivalent to that of a normal seventh-grade immortal origin stones.

“I still owe you eighty thousand Immortal Origin Stones from last time, and now that you're leaving, I have to repay my debt, so I'll be doing so in the form of this lock," Daoist Master Jingyang said, and it was clear that he was very reluctant to part with the lock, but he still handed it to Han Li.

"A ninth-grade immortal treasure? There are grades among immortal treasures? Why have I never heard of this before?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression.

"You're not aware of this? I suppose that makes sense. Generally speaking, only High Zenith cultivators are privy to this information," Daoist Master Jingyang replied with a smile. "All treasures of a sufficient caliber that contain law powers can be referred to as immortal treasures, but there are huge discrepancies between immortal treasures.

“Our Hundred Creations Mountain invented a grading system depending on how much law powers an immortal treasure contains, with the ninth grade being the lowest, and the first grade being the highest. As I just said, this golden lock is a ninth-grade immortal treasure."

"If this lock contains such immense law powers, yet is only a ninth-grade immortal treasure, then doesn't that mean that most immortal treasures wouldn't be graded at all?" Han Li asked with a stunned expression.

"That is indeed the case. Graded immortal treasures are extremely precious, and generally speaking, they're only in the possession of High Zenith cultivators. As for cultivators below the High Zenith Stage, the vast majority of the immortal treasures that they own are ungraded.

“For someone at or below the Golden Immortal Stage, obtaining an immortal treasure is already a very difficult task in itself," Daoist Master Jingyang explained with a smile.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod, then looked down at the golden lock in his hand.

The lock contained such immense law powers that it outshone almost all of the immortal treasures in his possession, and it was definitely worth more than eighty thousand Immortal Origin Stones, so this was clearly a gesture of goodwill from Daoist Master Jingyang.

"This is too precious a treasure to be worth a measly eighty thousand Immortal Origin Stones, but it is indeed something that I require, so I won't refuse. I owe you a favor for this," Han Li said with a serious expression as he stowed the lock away.

"There's no need to be so serious about it, Fellow Daoist Li. I'm glad that it's to your liking," Daoist Master Jingyang replied with a faint smile.

He had a good grasp on Han Li's personality, and he knew that Han Li wasn't the type of person who would accept kindness without reciprocation. As a Heavenly Pill Master, Daoist Master Jingyang knew that Han Li would definitely be able to assist him greatly in the future.

After that, the two of them chatted for a while longer before parting ways.

Right as Han Li was about to depart, a voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Fellow Daoist Li, no matter where you go from here, make sure you do not use that Fire Leaf Sect elder badge ever again."

Han Li stopped in his tracks as he turned back to the Leisure Valley with a surprised look in his eyes.

That voice belonged to none other than Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

At this moment, Immortal Lord Hot Flame's cave abode was completely empty, and only a faint burst of spatial fluctuations remained within its walls, but that also quickly faded.

Despite the restrictions present in Immortal Lord Hot Flame's cave abode, they were unable to keep out Han Li's Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Chapter 639: Trouble for Immortal Lord Hot Flame

Han Li withdrew his gaze from Immortal Lord Hot Flame's cave abode, and his brows furrowed slightly as he flew out of the valley as a streak of azure light.

While hovering in mid-air, he took a glance in the direction of Jade Gathering City, but instead of flying in that direction, he chose to fly southward instead.

While there were teleportation arrays in Jade Gathering City that led to other cities, the circumstances in the city were very complicated, and he would have to use his Fire Leaf Sect elder badge to access those teleportation arrays, something that Immortal Lord Hot Flame had just explicitly told him not to do.

He actually didn't have any concrete plans from here onward. He was just going to go somewhere secluded to avoid the unrest in the Floating Cloud Mountain Range, then create a temporary cave abode and continue to try and find ways to expel the baleful qi in his body.

At the moment, there was unrest across the entire True Immortal Realm, and Han Li had no idea how long the conflict between the Heavenly Court and the Reincarnation Palace had been raging for, but it was clearly only becoming more and more intense.

He was nothing more but a mere Golden Immortal, and while he could dominate his fellow Golden Immortals in battle and even ensure self-preservation against normal High Zenith cultivators, he was still far too powerless to play any significant role in this conflict.

The only plausible plan from here onward was to try and make a breakthrough to the High Zenith Stage as soon as possible so that he could stand a better chance of surviving in this chaotic world.

Only by ensuring his own survival first could he even begin to think about anything else.

According to the map, the nearest major city southward of the Floating Cloud Mountain Range was Auspicious Cloud City, and it would take around two to three months to get there.

Han Li was constantly keeping tabs on his surroundings while flying onward, and it didn't take long before he emerged from the Floating Cloud Mountain Range.

Up to this point, he hadn't encountered any trouble, and he heaved an internal sigh of relief as he summoned his green jade flying carriage before continuing his journey.

......

Close to a month flew by in the blink of an eye.

At this moment, Han Li was seated on the flying carriage with a small golden lock hovering in mid-air before him, and it was giving off radiant golden light alongside bursts of time law power fluctuations.

He was making a series of hand seals to cast a string of incantation seals into the lock, refining it while also carefully assessing the time law powers imbued within it.

Some time later, a hint of enlightenment flashed through his eyes, and the lock fell into his grasp at his behest.

He hadn't completed the refinement process yet, but he had gotten a good grasp of the time law powers that it contained. It was a type of restrictive law powers similar to that of the Mantra Treasured Axis. Furthermore, the lock contained far more law powers than even the previous three immortal treasures combined.

The lock would most likely be able to yield quite a large number of time law threads, but given how powerful it was, Han Li was rather reluctant to part with it.

Let's just wait and see for now. It's not like I'm in any hurry anyway.

With that in mind, Han Li opened his mouth to release a burst of golden light, which enveloped the lock before drawing it into his body to continue the refinement process.

After that, he flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip, which contained a map of the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

Up to this point, he hadn't detected anyone following him, and that was why he felt like it was safe to bring out the golden lock.

Below the flying carriage was an undulating mountain range that was entirely pitch black in color, and the mountain range was also enshrouded in a cloud of black mist, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

Most of the mountain ranges that Han Li had passed by on the way here were of the same color, and that was probably why this place was called the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

Han Li withdrew his gaze from the strange black mountain range, then pressed the jade slip against his own forehead.

The Floating Cloud Mountain Range and Jade Gathering City were both situated in the northernmost region of the Black Mountain Immortal Region close to the primordial land, and it was said that Jade Gathering City had been constructed on a massive plot of land that the Heavenly Court had managed to secure tens of millions of years ago, following a huge battle against the fierce beasts of the primordial land.

It was a similar story for most other immortal regions. Whenever human cultivators managed to expand their territory into the primordial land, a major city like Jade Gathering City would be constructed, and that would act as a foundation for further expansion, eventually resulting in the formation of an entire immortal region.

Sightings of primordial beasts were quite infrequent near Jade Gathering City, but that didn't mean that it was a safe place. To the south of Jade Gathering City was a rather barren area that was filled with mountain ranges and forests, but this area was actually far safer than the city, and many mortal cities and nations were constructed there.

The flying carriage quickly flew over the black mountain range down below, and a massive river appeared up ahead.

The river was close to five hundred kilometers wide, and there were massive waves churning over its surface, as if there were an enormous wyrm wreaking havoc within the depths, presenting a spectacular sight to behold.

According to the map, this river was called the Black Pine River, and further up ahead was a mortal nation by the name of the Prosperous Origin Nation.

Right at this moment, something suddenly caught his attention, and he turned to the side with purple light flashing in his eyes, upon which a hint of surprise quickly appeared on his face.

He could sense violent spiritual power fluctuations in the distance in that direction, interspersed with hints of law power fluctuations, indicating that a battle between cultivators of at least the Golden Immortal Stage was taking place there.

This area had very sparse spiritual qi, and there were only several Body Integration Stage sects in a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers, so why were there Golden Immortals locked in battle here?

Han Li made a hand seal to conceal the flying carriage while carefully releasing his spiritual sense in that direction, and all of a sudden, a hesitant look appeared on his face.

After some contemplation, he stowed the flying carriage away, then began to fly in that direction as a faint shadow.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li descended in front of an enormous col in another black mountain range.

Lights of different colors were rising up into the sky from the col that was several hundred kilometers up ahead, and sure enough, a fierce battle was taking place there, with three golden-robed cultivators, two male and one female, attacking a white-haired elderly man.

Judging from their attire, the three golden-robed cultivators were all Heavenly Court cultivators, and they were led by an imposing man with a head of yellow hair. Judging from the aura that he was exuding, he was an early-High Zenith Stage immortal envoy, while his companions were both at the late-Golden Immortal Stage.

As for the white-haired elderly man, he was none other than Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

Why is Fellow Daoist Hot Flame here? And why is he fighting Heavenly Court cultivators?

There was a dense cloud of yellow mist around the yellow-haired man, encompassing the entire surrounding area in a radius of dozens of kilometers while giving off formidable earth law power fluctuations.

The cloud of yellow mist was crashing down in waves upon Immortal Lord Hot Flame at the man's behest, while the other two Heavenly Court cultivators were attacking with a pair of giant purple swords that appeared to be a set of extremely formidable twin immortal swords.

Their assault was as relentless as it was formidable, and even though Immortal Lord Hot Flame was clearly on the back foot against his three assailants, his situation wasn't all that dire.

There was a large crimson flag hovering above his head, upon which was embroidered a majestic silver peacock.

Thick pillars of fire were erupting out of the flag incessantly, forming a churning sea of flames to ward off the oncoming attacks.

However, that flag wasn't the reason why Immortal Lord Hot Flame was able to withstand the attacks from his three opponents. Instead, what was truly keeping him in this battle was a ball of radiant golden light that was glowing from his waist.

It was an ovular golden mirror that was around a foot in size and quite antiquated in appearance.

Bursts of golden ripples were surging out of the mirror, encompassing an area with a radius of several thousand feet around Immortal Lord Hot Flame, and as soon as the attacks from his three assailants entered the area encompassed within the golden ripples, they were instantly slowed down by tenfold, allowing Immortal Lord Hot Flame to evade or block them with ease.

These golden ripples were giving off formidable time law power fluctuations, and Han Li's pupils instantly contracted slightly upon seeing this.

That golden mirror was clearly also a time-attribute immortal treasure, and it didn't seem to be inferior to Han Li's golden lock.

The yellow-haired man was unable to break through Immortal Lord Hot Flame's defenses, but he remained unfazed as he yelled, "Huo Zhuozi, surrender and hand yourself over to us right now! Our Heavenly Court could use a man of your talents!"

Waves of yellow mist were surging out of his sleeves before converging toward Immortal Lord Hot Flame from all directions to prevent him from getting away.

Meanwhile, the other two Heavenly Court cultivators were also racing through the air around Immortal Lord Hot Flame while raining down bolts of lightning upon him.

"Who the hell is Huo Zhuozi? I am Immortal Lord Hot Flame, an elder of the Fire Leaf Sect! Stop trying to frame me!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame yelled in a furious voice as he opened his mouth to release a burst of crimson energy into the large flag above his head, then began to chant an incantation.

The crimson flag instantly swelled to around twice its original size, and the pillars of flames erupting out of it became several times thicker than before.

These fiery pillars fused as one in a flash to form a mountainous crimson sword, which struck the cloud of yellow mist with tremendous power amid the sound of a volcanic eruption.

A huge opening was instantly torn into the cloud of mist, and much of it was evaporated by the flames around the giant sword.

However, the fiery sword was also slowed down significantly, but the flames around it were still erupting outward with immense power.

The yellow-haired man remained completely unfazed, and he sneered, "You think a mere Golden Immortal like yourself can break my Yellow Sand Tent?"

He made a hand seal as he spoke, and all of the nearby yellow mist instantly began to churn violently, then formed an enormous yellow mountain directly in front of the fiery sword.

The giant sword struck the mountain with a resounding boom, and it was instantly stopped cold in its tracks.

On top of that, tendrils of yellow were shooting out of the surrounding yellow mist before wrapping themselves around the fiery sword, binding it tightly into place.

Chapter 640: Looks Like I Found the Right Targets

"Now!" the yellow-haired man yelled, and his two companions instantly pounced on this opportunity, sending bolts of purple lightning raining down upon the giant sword.

Purple and red light intertwined incessantly on the surface of the giant sword, and a series of cracks began to appear on its blade before rapidly expanding, looking as if it could explode at any moment.

However, right at this moment, a peculiar look flashed through Immortal Lord Hot Flame's eyes, and he opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence, which exploded to form a ball of radiant crimson light that vanished into the crimson flag above his head in a flash.

A resounding boom rang out as the purple peacock shot out of the crimson flag, then flew away in the opposite direction of the fiery sword, plunging headfirst into the cloud of yellow mist in that direction.

After the silver peacock emerged, the crimson flag erupted into flame and was incinerated into ashes in an instant.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame paid no heed to the flag as he made a rapid string of hand seals, and a vast expanse of silver flames erupted out of the silver peacock's body to strike the cloud of yellow mist.

A violent explosion rang out as the two clashed, and it was like a coming together between cold water and hot oil.

The silver peacock was clearly far more formidable than the fiery sword, and it was immediately able to eradicate the yellow mist directly in front of it before easily tearing a massive gash into the cloud of yellow mist up ahead.

In the blink of an eye, the silver peacock was on the verge of completely tearing through the cloud of yellow mist, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame was flying along in hot pursuit behind it.

The yellow-haired man's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release a yellow feather fan that was riddled with spirit patterns and giving off radiant spiritual light.

He grabbed onto the handle of the fan before sweeping it viciously through the air, and a burst of dense yellow light instantly erupted out of the fan before rapidly expanding to form an all-encompassing yellow storm that swept up both Immortal Lord Hot Flame and the silver peacock.

The storm was extremely powerful, and the entire col was instantly encompassed within an enormous pillar of yellow wind, along with a large area around it.

The pillar of wind erupted into the heavens, and the clouds up above were also torn apart.

As soon as the silver peacock was swept up by the storm, it was instantly unable to advance any further, and it was beginning to move involuntarily in the direction of the ferocious wind.

Even though Immortal Lord Hot Flame was also caught in the storm, the fierce winds were slowed down significantly by golden ripples around him, so the storm wasn't able to affect him very much, but he was also forced to stop in his tracks.

Meanwhile, the yellow-haired man vanished from the spot, then instantly appeared directly in front of Immortal Lord Hot Flame before releasing an enormous yellow spirit domain that encompassed the entire col.

Everything within the col instantly became extremely heavy, and the yellow-haired man thrust a fist forward with tremendous force, conjuring up a gargantuan yellow fist projection that struck Immortal Lord Hot Flame with incredible power.

The fist projection was too massive for the golden ripples around Immortal Lord Hot Flame to ward off, and he was sent flying back through the air, forced back into the encirclement once again.

In the distance, Han Li remained still on the spot. The yellow storm conjured up by the yellow-haired man was extremely powerful, but Han Li was sufficiently far away from it that he remained unaffected.

However, at this moment, his brows were tightly furrowed, and there was a hesitant look in his eyes, but it didn't take long before he seemed to have made up his mind, and he abruptly vanished from the spot.

After forcing back Immortal Lord Hot Flame, the yellow-haired man turned to the silver peacock, then pointed a finger at it, and a burst of radiant yellow light emerged on his fingertip, then transformed into a shimmering yellow needle that shot forth through the air, leaving a trail of afterimages in its wake.

The silver peacock was still trapped within the yellow storm, and it was desperately flapping its wings in an attempt to stabilize itself, but right at this moment, a thin streak of yellow light shot past, and the peacock's struggles instantly ceased as a fist-sized hole appeared on its glabella, running through the entirety of its head.

It immediately let loose an anguished cry before exploding into countless specks of silver flames that were instantly devoured by the surrounding yellow storm.

Meanwhile, the fiery sword had also been destroyed under the combined effort of the other two Heavenly Court cultivators, and it exploded into crimson flames that were also swept up by the surrounding storm.

With the silver peacock and the fiery sword destroyed in quick succession, Immortal Lord Hot Flame's complexion instantly paled slightly, while the protective spiritual light around him also dimmed significantly.

The golden ripples around him also shuddered before shrinking down to encompass a far smaller area.

The yellow-haired man was ecstatic to see this, and he tossed the yellow feather fan in his hand forward before opening his mouth to release a burst of yellow energy into it.

The fan immediately began to glow with radiant yellow light while rapidly expanding, reaching in excess of a thousand feet in size in the blink of an eye. At the same time, all of its feathers had spread apart, while the spirit patterns inscribed upon them flashed erratically, and the law power fluctuations that it was giving off had become several times more powerful than before.

The other two Heavenly Court cultivators hurriedly flew back in retreat for fear of being caught in the attack.

Right at this moment, a streak of green light shot forth from afar, then drew to a halt in front of the giant yellow fan, revealing itself to be a green gourd.

A thick beam of green light shot out of the gourd before wrapping itself around the yellow fan, and the radiant yellow light around it instantly faded, while the fan itself rapidly shrank back down in size.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was just about to make a final stand, and a surprised look appeared on his face upon seeing this.

"Who's there?" the yellow-haired man roared in a furious voice as he cast an incantation seal into the yellow fan.

The dim yellow light on its surface instantly brightened ever so slightly, and it began struggling violently to try and free itself from the binding green light, but right at this moment, a beam of dark green light shot out of the gourd before also wrapping itself around the yellow fan.

A loud crack rang out as the beam of dark green light destroyed the yellow fan with ease, following which the remnants of the fan were sucked back into the gourd.

Immediately thereafter, an azure figure appeared behind the gourd, and it was none other than Han Li.

However, at this moment, his entire body was enshrouded in a layer of blurry azure light, making it impossible to make out his appearance.

A hint of surprise flashed through Immortal Lord Hot Flame's eyes at the sight of Han Li.

"Who are you? You must have a death wish to be opposing our Immortal Prison!" the yellow-haired man said in a cold voice as he turned his gaze to Han Li.

"Looks like I found the right targets," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

"Insolence! I don't know where you got this Profound Heavenly Treasure from, but you're still nothing more than a mere Golden Immortal! Let's see if you can still be so cocky once I've torn your nascent soul out of your body!" the yellow-haired man said in a cold voice as he reached for the storage pouch strapped to his waist, but Han Li beat him to the punch, thrusting a palm into the underside of the gourd like lightning.

The mouth of the gourd turned slightly to face the yellow-haired man, and a burst of dazzling golden light emerged from its opening amid the sound of thunderous rumbling.

At this moment, the green vortex within the gourd was revolving rapidly in the direction that was opposite from its normal direction, and an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword was hovering at the center of the vortex, trembling violently while on the verge of being blasted out of the gourd.

However, right at this moment, a ball of yellow light shot out from deep within the gourd. There were countless yellow runes flashing within the ball of light, and it was giving off astonishing law power fluctuations that came from the destroyed yellow fan.

The ball of yellow light appeared in the green vortex in a flash, and as soon as it entered the vortex, the two seemed to resonate with each other, causing both to light up.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword within the vortex was instantly sent flying out of the vortex by a burst of tremendous force, and a hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

This was a completely unexpected turn of events.

A beam of yellow light shot out of the gourd at an astonishing speed, and the yellow-haired man's expression changed drastically as he hurriedly flew back in retreat.

At the same time, countless yellow spirit patterns emerged over his body, then flew out to form an antiquated yellow shield in front of him.

In the next instant, a resounding boom rang out, and the yellow shield shuddered violently as a burst of blinding yellow light erupted from its surface, only to then instantly vanish.

A large hole had appeared on the shield, and the yellow-haired man behind it had a dazed and incredulous look on his face.

A large hole had been punched through his lower abdomen as well, piercing straight through his dantian. The hole was smooth and charred black, and not a single drop of blood was flowing out.

The hole extended all the way into the ground beneath him, where the beam of yellow light had burrowed an unfathomable distance into the earth.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the other two Heavenly Court cultivators were looking on with their mouths agape in incredulity, as was Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

Chapter 641: Sought Out

A hint of surprise and elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he pointed a finger at the yellow-haired man.

In the next instant, a small azure sword appeared above the yellow-haired man's head, then swooped down with incredible speed and power.

The man's body was instantly sliced into two, and his soul was also completely torn to shreds.

Only now did the other two Heavenly Court cultivators return to their senses, and they immediately turned and fled in two different directions while summoning a string of immortal treasures to defend themselves.

All of a sudden, Immortal Lord Hot Flame appeared in front of the female cultivator, blocking her path as he swept both sleeves through the air, sending a wave of golden ripples surging toward the woman.

As soon as she flew into the golden ripples, she was instantly slowed down significantly.

"It's my turn now!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame chortled as he made a hand seal to send several fiery red flying swords hurtling directly toward the woman.

Han Li took a glance in Immortal Lord Hot Flame's direction, then turned to the final Heavenly Court cultivator, but didn't immediately strike.

Instead, he turned his gaze to the green gourd before thrusting a palm into its underside once again.

The third Heavenly Court cultivator, a portly young man, was flying extremely quickly, and he was just about to disappear into the distance when a streak of crimson light shot out of the gourd at an incredible speed, appearing behind the portly young man in a flash.

The layers of protective spiritual light around his body were torn apart by the streak of crimson light with ease, and a large hole was punched through his lower abdomen, destroying the nascent soul inside.

Immediately thereafter, a small azure sword appeared above his head, then swooped down to slice his body into two as well.

After that, a burst of azure swordlight surged out of the sword, picking up the portly young man's storage tool before carrying it back to Han Li, who remained still on the spot, observing the green gourd with a contemplative expression.

That streak of crimson light was the burst of law powers that had been sucked into the gourd in the wake of the destruction of that fiery immortal sword.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he stowed the green gourd away, following which two small azure swords appeared beside him, both of which were carrying storage tools belonging to the yellow-haired man and the portly young man.

Han Li stowed the two swords and storage tools away, then flicked a finger through the air, releasing two balls of fire that quickly incinerated the remains of the two slain Heavenly Court cultivators into ashes.

Right at this moment, an agonized wail rang out, and Han Li turned to discover that the female Heavenly Court cultivator had already been set alight with silver flames.

She was frantically trying to douse the flames, but her efforts were completely futile, and she was also incinerated into ashes in the blink of an eye.

In the next instant, Han Li appeared beside Immortal Lord Hot Flame, and the latter asked, "It's you, right, Fellow Daoist Li? Thank you for your help."

"Now's not the time for small talk, let's get out of here first," Han Li said as he made a hand seal to release two thick bolts of golden lightning, conjuring up a lightning array.

A loud thunderclap rang out, and the two instantly vanished into thin air.

Shortly thereafter, an arc of five-colored lightning arrived on the scene, drawing to a halt in the sky above the col.

The lightning then faded to reveal Su Liu and a scholarly-robed man, both of whom had grim looks on their faces.

"It looks like Yi Lian and his two companions were all killed," Su Liu remarked in a grim voice.

"Huo Zhuozi is only at the late-Golden Immortal Stage, so there's no way that Yi Lian and his two late-Golden Immortal Stage subordinates should've been killed by him, especially not this quickly," the scholarly-robed man said with tightly furrowed brows.

Su Liu swept his gaze over the battlefield, and all of a sudden, something caught his attention as he descended beside the bottomless hole that had been pierced into the earth by the beam of yellow light that had come out of Han Li's gourd.

He crouched down to examine the hole a little closer, and the grim look on his face became even more pronounced.

The scholarly-robed man flew down beside him, and after briefly inspecting the hole, he declared, "This is definitely not something that the likes of Huo Zhuozi and Yi Lian could've done. Someone must've killed Yi Lian and his subordinates and rescued Huo Zhuozi."

The scholarly-robed man then began to chant an incantation, and a wave of rippling white light surged out of his glabella before instantly spreading over the entire surrounding area in a radius of several dozen kilometers.

Shortly thereafter, he continued, "I can sense the aura of a fifth cultivator here outside of Yi Lian and the others, and that person was most likely the culprit. However, the aura that they've left behind is very faint, so they must've anticipated that someone would come to search the battlefield. In the end, they appear to have used some type of lightning spatial array to flee the scene with Huo Zhuozi."

"Can you find out the destination of the lightning array?" Su Liu asked.

"I'm afraid not. The lightning array has already teleported them outside of my sensory range," the scholarly-robed man replied.

Su Liu fell silent upon hearing this.

"What do we do now?" the scholarly-robed man asked after a brief silence.

"We can't find any leads, so let's go back for now," Su Liu replied.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of five-colored lightning, which swept up both of them before sending them flying back the same way that they had come from.

......

In the sky above a lush forest in the Black Mountain Immortal Region, a vast expanse of silver lightning cascaded down like a waterfall, forming a lightning teleportation array that contained Han Li's duo.

After the lightning faded, the two of them traveled southward for several days before descending into a small town concealed within a col.

Upon landing, neither of them said anything as they busied themselves with concealing their own auras, and only after that did they make their way into the town along the bumpy stone path.

At the entrance of the town was a wooden archway that was in a state of severe disrepair. The black tiles on top of the archway were covered in moss, and the words "Green Forest Town" were engraved onto lintel below.

The archway was tilting slightly to the side, and upon catching sight of the town's name, Han Li suddenly recalled the first town that he had stayed in after leaving his village countless years ago as a child. That town's name had been Green Ox Town, and there was only a difference of one word, but the two were worlds apart.

"What is it, Fellow Daoist Li?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked at the sight of Han Li's distracted expression.

"It's nothing, I was just reminiscing about some past events," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"You're still in the mood to be reminiscing about the past in a situation like this? You certainly seem much more composed and relaxed than I am," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a wry smile.

"We've been traveling southward this entire time, but along the way, we've changed directions eastward and westward several times, and it doesn't seem like we're being tailed by anyone at the moment, so there's no need to be overly anxious," Han Li said with a smile.

The two of them passed through the archway to discover that the town wasn't very large, but it had everything that one could hope to find in a town like this, including restaurants, shops, and inns.

Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame entered a teahouse, then requested a booth on the second floor before sitting down next to the window.

The waiter brought to their table a pot of premium tea and some well-made snacks before departing, leaving Han Li's duo on their own.

Han Li lifted the teacup before taking a whiff, and he couldn't help but raise an eyebrow in surprise at the refreshing fragrance of its contents.

"I didn't think there would be such fine tea in such a secluded place."

Immortal Lord Hot Flame took a sip of tea upon hearing this, then immediately set his cup down again, clearly not as impressed with the tea as Han Li was.

"I'm even more indebted to you now, Fellow Daoist Li," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as he turned to Han Li with a serious expression.

"Before we discuss that, why don't you tell me why you were being attacked by Heavenly Court cultivators?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid I can't answer that question, Fellow Daoist Li," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a slightly awkward expression.

"It's fine, I can roughly guess the reason. Something must've happened in your sect, right? I'm assuming this is also why you told me not to use my identity as an outer sect elder of the Fire Leaf Sect any longer. You helped me in the valley, so I'm only repaying the favor here," Han Li said.

"That was part of my consideration, but mostly, I just didn't want any more trouble," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed.

Han Li picked up his cup to take a sip of tea, btu right as he was about to speak again, his expression suddenly changed drastically as he stood up from his chair, and an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword appeared in his grasp in a flash.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame immediately sprang out of his chair as well upon seeing this, and he followed Han Li's gaze, turning his attention to the entrance of the booth.

At the same time, a burst of silver light appeared there without any warning, giving off formidable spatial fluctuations.

A burst of azure light immediately emerged over Han Li's body as he prepared for battle, and the aura that had erupted out of his body in that instant was so immense that Immortal Lord Hot Flame couldn't help but be momentarily dumbstruck.

Right at this moment, a slightly familiar voice rang out.

"Settle down now, fellow daoists. We are not from the Immortal Palace, and we don't mean you any harm."

Two figures emerged from within the silver light, one of whom was a handsome purple-robed young man, while the other was a thin black-robed young man.

Chapter 642: Refusal

Han Li was immediately able to identify the two as Shi Chuankong and Silver Fox of the Reincarnation Palace, but he didn't lower his guard in the slightest.

Instead of saying anything, he turned his gaze to Immortal Lord Hot Flame as he noticed that both Shi Chuankong and Silver Fox were also looking at him.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame swept his gaze over Silver Fox, then turned to Shi Chuankong as he asked, "Who are you?"

"My name is Shi Chuankong. You probably haven't heard of me, but that's not an issue. All you need to know is our objective for coming here to see you," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

As he was speaking, he took a quick glance at Han Li, and a hint of befuddlement appeared deep within his eyes.

"You were at the Jade Kun Pagoda auction, right? Considering all the bidding wars we were involved in, you must be a very wealthy man," Silver Fox remarked as he turned to Han Li.

"Surely the vastly renowned Silver Fox hasn't come all the way here to seek retribution over such a trivial matter," Han Li said with a composed smile.

"Rest assured, I'm not that petty. We're here today for Fellow Daoist Hot Flame," Silver Fox replied with a smile of his own.

"What do you want from me?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a wary look in his eyes as he unconsciously shuffled a little closer to Han Li.

"Let's not waste time here, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame. I'm sure you know why we've come here to see you," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame with an inquisitive expression upon hearing this.

"I don't know what you're talking about. There's no vendetta between us, so let's all go our separate ways. Come on, Fellow Daoist Li, we're leaving," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said.

"Do you not want to go back to visit our sect?" Silver Fox suddenly asked as he raised his voice a little.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then asked, "What's the point? It's nothing more than a set of ruins anyway. I don't understand why you can't just let the past go."

Han Li was rather perplexed by this conversation, but he could see that Silver Fox and Shi Chuankong didn't harbor any animosity, so he stowed his longsword away.

"It's not that we're unwilling to let go of the past, Fellow Daoist Huo, it's the Heavenly Court that refuses to let bygones be bygones. Why is the Fire Leaf Sect under the Immortal Palace's surveillance? And why is there so much unrest in the Floating Cloud Mountain Range? I'm sure you're fully aware of the underlying reasons," Silver Fox sighed.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

It was no wonder that Immortal Lord Hot Flame had warned him not to use his identity as an elder of the Fire Leaf Sect. It seemed that there were some mysterious circumstances involved.

Even though Han Li had already guessed that this was the case, it was all but confirmed now that Yu Ziqi had been attacked because of Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was silent for a moment, then asked once again, "Who are you?"

"I am a member of the Reincarnation Palace, while Fellow Daoist Shi here comes from the Devil Realm," Silver Fox replied.

"What? Even the Devil Race has chosen to join forces with your Reincarnation Palace?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a surprised expression.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame, I don't possess anywhere near the level of status or power required to represent the entire Devil Race. I'm here today as I was invited by Fellow Daoist Silver Fox, and I'm also curious about what happened to the True Mantra Sect. Would you be able to enlighten me, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Shi Chuankong asked with a smile.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, he was reeling upon hearing mention of the True Mantra Sect.

This was not a sect that he was unfamiliar with. Not only did the Mantra Axis Scripture come from this sect, one of his spiritual transmigrations had taken him to the sect.

On top of that, it was clear to him that Shi Chuankong was downplaying his own importance. He had mastery over the laws of space, which was one of the three paramount laws, so how could he possibly just be some insignificant no-name as he proclaimed?

"During the fall of the True Mantra Sect, I just so happened to be trapped in a set of ruins while out on a mission for my master. By the time I finally managed to free myself, close to a thousand years had already passed. All of the surviving members of our sect had become wanted fugitives of the Heavenly Court, so I had no choice but to alter my own appearance and leave.

“I also really want to find out what happened to our sect. Otherwise, I wouldn't have taken the risk to come to the Black Mountain Immortal Region and establish this Fire Leaf Sect," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed.

"So you've been residing in the Floating Cloud Mountain Range this entire time to evade the Heavenly Court?" Han Li asked.

"Not entirely. I spent most of my time in the Leisure Valley as I got along very well with Fellow Daoist Duan and the others, but ultimately, my troubled past followed me to the valley and brought disaster upon everyone," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a guilty expression.

"There's no need to blame yourself, Fellow Daoist. The Immortal Palace has been aiming to target the Floating Cloud Mountain Range for quite some time now, and their primary objective is to eradicate the members of our Reincarnation Palace residing in the mountain range," Silver Fox consoled.

"I have a question. Some time ago, one of the fellow daoists living in our valley was attacked. Was the perpetrator someone from your Reincarnation Palace or from the Immortal Palace?" Han Li asked.

"Are you talking about the one that was left on that cliff to die? He was attacked by some guy who dressed up like a woman and had a red umbrella. He looked more like the subordinate of an immortal envoy than someone from the Black Mountain Immortal Palace to me," Silver Fox replied.

"Does that mean you were the one who saved him?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"He detonated his own consciousness rather than allow his own soul to be searched, and I was impressed with his courage, so I decided to help him out. Having said that, I didn't think you would actually be able to save his life. That was also very impressive," Silver Fox praised.

"We're going off on too much of a tangent, Silver Fox. Let's finish discussing the matter at hand first," Shi Chuankong interjected.

"Sorry, I do tend to get distracted. So how about it, Fellow Daoist Huo? The Heavenly Court has already tracked you down, so you'll have to go back on the run anyway. Why don't you become our ally and we'll search for the ruins of the True Mantra Sect together? After that, I can submit a recommendation for you to join our Reincarnation Palace, and you'll receive protection in exchange," Silver Fox said.

A hesitant look appeared on Immortal Lord Hot Flame's face upon hearing this, and he didn't immediately reply.

"The ruins of the True Mantra Sect will be hard to find, but you don't necessarily have to join us to find it. If you don't wish to join us, then we won't force you to do so, but in that case, you'll have to face the Heavenly Court on your own," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"Fellow Daoist Shi is right. The Heavenly Court won't let you off the hook, and you may not be able to get away next time. Are you not interested in uncovering the mysteries behind the True Mantra Sect's demise? Working with us will be a win-win situation for everyone," Silver Fox chimed in.

Han Li watched in silence as the two took turns trying to convince Immortal Lord Hot Flame, and he didn't interject as this had nothing to do with him anyway.

"Besides, surely you don't want the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra left behind by Patriarch Miro to be taken by the Heavenly Court," Silver Fox, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame immediately shuddered slightly upon hearing this.

"There's no need to be so surprised, our Reincarnation Palace has some very good sources. One of the main reasons why the Heavenly Court has always wanted to enter the ruins of the True Mantra Sect is precisely for the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"Does the same not apply to you?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a cold sneer.

"As opposed to saying that our objective is to obtain this cultivation art, it's better to say that we want to avoid having the cultivation art fall into the hands of the Heavenly Court. In that regard, we have a common objective," Silver Fox replied with a smile.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was silent for a long time upon hearing this, following which he finally arrived at a decision.

"Alright, I agree to your proposal."

"You won't regret the decision, Fellow Daoist Huo! This is why I love working with smart people," Silver Fox said with a gleeful expression.

"Hold on a second! If you want me to join you, then you have to agree to a condition of mine," Immortal Lord Hot Flame suddenly said.

"Go ahead," Silver Fox prompted.

"In order to save me, Fellow Daoist Li has killed cultivators of the Immortal Palace, so he needs to go on the run as well. Hence, you have to bring him along as well," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as he took a glance at Han Li.

A slightly hesitant look appeared on Silver Fox's face upon hearing this.

"I think that's fine. We've been observing Fellow Daoist Li for a few days now, and I can tell that he's not a member of the Heavenly Court, so why don't we have him come along?" Shi Chuankong said.

"In that case, I'll extend the invitation to Fellow Daoist Li as well," Silver Fox replied with a nod.

"I appreciate the kind offer, but I only saved Fellow Daoist Hot Flame as he's a friend of mine, and I wanted to repay some favors that he had done for me in the past. I don't have much interest in these True Mantra Sect ruins that you speak of, so I think we should go our separate ways," Han Li said.

Everyone was quite surprised to hear this.

"Fellow Daoist Li, perhaps you're unaware of just how powerful the Reincarnation Palace is. If you go with them, you'll be able to use their power and resources, and that'll save you a lot of trouble. Even if you don't want to go to the True Mantra Sect ruins, at least accompany us until we get to a safe place before going off on your own," Immortal Lord Hot Flame hurriedly said to Han Li through voice transmission.

"As you're aware, I'm currently dealing with my baleful decay, and that's already taking up all of my time and energy, so I really don't have the spare capacity to pursue anything else. No one from the Immortal Palace was there to bear witness to the part that I played in that battle, so as long as I proceed with caution, I should be alright," Han Li replied, doing so openly instead of through voice transmission.

He was well aware of just how powerful the Reincarnation Palace was, and he could tell that Immortal Lord Hot Flame was genuinely thinking for his benefit, but at the moment, his sole focus was to overcome his baleful decay, so he had no interest in exploring any ruins.

Chapter 643: Reunion

Shi Chuankong and Silver Fox exchanged a glance with each other upon hearing this, but neither of them said anything.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame could see that Han Li's mind was already made up, and he said, "In that case, it appears that this is where we'll part ways. I'll repay you for everything that you've done for me when we meet again."

"May we meet again someday," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame returned his salute, and Han Li gave Shi Chuankong and Silver Fox a nod before flying out of the window as a streak of azure light, instantly vanishing into the distance.

"I'm sure the two of you are already aware that the ruins are in the Black Soil Immortal Region. When do we set off?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

"There's no hurry, we're still missing one person," Silver Fox replied with a smile.

"In any case, let's leave this place right away. The confounding arrays that we set up earlier may not be enough to fool those immortal envoys, and perhaps they could even be on their way here as we speak," Shi Chuankong said.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he made a hand seal, and a burst of silver light appeared in front of him, giving off powerful spatial fluctuations. The silver light quickly inundated all three of them, and they vanished from the teahouse.

......

Over three years flew by in a flash.

In an undulating black mountain range in the Black Mountain Immortal Region was a short and unremarkable mountain between a pair of taller mountains.

There was a completely overgrown stone path in a mountain in the forest, and it led to a rundown Daoist temple with two ancient locust trees planted in front of the entrance.

The temple had already completely collapsed with the exception of a single side hall, which was covered in moss and vines and just barely hanging on for dear life.

Late at night, a faint white light could be seen through the dilapidated windows of the side hall, casting elongated shadows onto the stone steps outside.

An azure-robed man was seated on an old cushion with his legs crossed, and there was a small green vial sitting on the ground in front of him.

The man was none other than Han Li, and after parting ways with Immortal Lord Hot Flame, he had left Green Forest Town before teleporting several times in succession using his lightning array, following which he embarked on a southbound journey on his green jade flying carriage.

He would travel by day, then find some places in the wilderness near cities and towns to rest at night, allowing him to avoid other cultivators and demon beasts so that he could focus on his time-attribute cultivation arts.

The Baleful Quelling Pills that he had taken had expelled much of the baleful qi in his body, so the journey thus far had been a safe and smooth one, but he couldn't visit any major cities where powerful cultivators were present.

After a few minutes, a drop of spirit liquid took shape within the Heaven Controlling Vial from the moonlight that it had absorbed.

Han Li flicked a finger toward a nearby pile of lumber to ignite it and start a fire, then picked up the Heaven Controlling Vial before raising it up to his own eyes.

Thanks to the light of the fire, he was able to see through the wall of the vial that there was a drop of liquid slowly rolling around inside.

Right as he was contemplating entering the Flower Branch domain to water his Dao Warrior primary beans, the Dragon 5 mask on his face abruptly emerged on its own.

Han Li was rather taken aback by this, and he made a hand seal, upon which a beam of red light shot out of the glabella of his mask, producing a projection of a humanoid figure.

The figure was over twenty feet tall, almost as tall as the side hall that Han Li was staying in. They were wearing a loose-fitting black robe, and there was a menacing dark red mask on his face.

A hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face as he discovered that this figured looked exactly like the reincarnation envoy that he had seen in Lu Renjia's memories.

"You're Dragon 5, right? It's already been close to a thousand years since you became a Reincarnation Disciple, so you'll need to complete a mission for the next thousand-year period," the reincarnation envoy declared in an indifferent voice.

"Has it already been a thousand years? Time really does fly," Han Li sighed.

"Are you going to accept this mission or issue Immortal Origin Stones for exemption?" the reincarnation envoy asked.

"Please tell me the contents of the mission first," Han Li said.

"For this mission, you'll have to meet up with Fox 3 on Magpie Coop Mountain to assist him in exploring a set of ruins. He'll inform you of the specific details once you meet up with him. As for the reward for the mission, you'll be receiving twenty thousand Immortal Origin Stones and an ungraded immortal treasure from Fox 3 in addition to the spoils that you reap from the ruins," the reincarnation envoy explained.

A thought occurred to Han Li upon hearing this, and he asked, "Is this Fox 3 the renowned Silver Fox?"

"You can ask him that yourself when you meet him," the reincarnation envoy replied in an indifferent voice.

Even though this wasn't direct confirmation, Han Li already knew the answer to his question.

"If I choose to pay Immortal Origin Stones instead, how much will it cost?" Han Li asked.

"Fifty thousand," the reincarnation envoy replied.

Han Li fell into deep thought upon hearing this.

Fifty thousand was not an insignificant sum, but it wasn't outside of his means, either. However, who would be willing to forfeit fifty thousand Immortal Origin Stones for nothing? With that in mind, he couldn't help but begin to reconsider the True Mantra Sect ruins.

He was quite interested in the True Mantra Sect, and the main reason why he had turned down the offer to explore the ruins was because he didn't trust Silver Fox and Shi Chuankong.

However, now that this had become a Reincarnation Palace mission, things were different.

As for his baleful decay, the missions that he had released in the Reincarnation Palace hadn't received any responses up to this point, so it didn't really matter whether he was in the True Mantra Sect ruins or out on the run.

"Make up your mind," the reincarnation envoy suddenly urged.

"I'll take on the mission," Han Li finally decided.

"Alright, once you complete the mission, you'll be free for the next one thousand years, and you can access all of the Reincarnation Palace's resources as long as you issue the corresponding sum of Immortal Origin Stones," the reincarnation envoy replied with a nod.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of silver light, which formed a large map, at the center of which was a glowing red dot, above which were the words "Magpie Coop Mountain."

"Memorize this map. You will have to meet Fox 3 on Magpie Coop Mountain within half a year, and if you're not there by then, you'll be punished on the basis of refusing to complete your mission," the reincarnation envoy said, following which his body began to dissipate.

Han Li carefully inspected the map before him, and after identifying several landmarks on the map, he quickly tracked down the mountain range that he was currently in, discovering that its name was "Old Indent Mountain."

The mountain range wasn't far away from Magpie Coop Mountain, and it would only take around three months for him to get there on his flying carriage.

Shortly after Han Li memorized the map, it vanished into thin air, and he took a moment to recollect the map in his mind once more, then opened his Flower Branch domain and stepped into it.

......

Over three months later.

Three figures were seated around an intricately crafted white jade table on a lone mountain that was several thousand feet tall.

Each of them was holding a silver cup, and they were exchanging toasts with one another.

The cups were filled with dark red wine that was giving off a slightly astringent aroma, and one of the three figures was a black-robed young man who was holding a cup in one hand and a silver wine flagon in the other, occasionally drinking straight out of the flagon whenever the mood struck him.

The flagon seemed to become some type of treasure with a limitless capacity, and it seemed as if its contents were never going to run out.

Sitting across from the black-robed young man was a white-haired elderly man, and he said, "Fellow Daoist Li was also an avid wine enthusiast. If he hadn't left, I'm sure you two would've bonded over your shared love for wine."

These three were none other than Immortal Lord Hot Flame's trio.

"Is that right? What a pity. Having said that, he had already made up his mind, so we weren't going to convince him to stay," Fox 3 replied with a smile.

Shi Chuankong was looking at the distant scenery in an absentminded manner, taking no interest in the wine as he asked, "When is the final member of our party going to arrive, Fox 3?"

"He should be here in a month or two. The higher-ups are taking this mission quite seriously, so I'm sure the one that they've chosen to complete our party was carefully selected," Fox 3 replied.

As soon as his voice trailed off, his eyes suddenly lit up slightly as he chuckled, "Looks like he's a little earlier than I expected."

Right at this moment, a streak of green light shot forth from afar, then drew to a halt up above, following which an azure figure descended in front of the trio.

Fox 3 and the others were astonished to see this azure figure.

"What are you doing here, Fellow Daoist Li?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame exclaimed with a surprised and elated expression.

"Long time no see, fellow daoists," Han Li said with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong exchanged an uncertain glance with one another.

"Are you the one sent by our Reincarnation Palace to assist us on this mission?" Fox 3 asked.

"That's right. As it turns out, my current thousand-year mission is to assist you in exploring the True Mantra Sect ruins," Han Li sighed.

He wiped a hand over his own face as he spoke, and his Dragon 5 mask was revealed.

Fox 3 carefully inspected the mask for a moment, following which he suddenly exclaimed, "So you're Dragon 5!"

"Oh? You've heard of me?" Han Li asked as he reverted back to his original appearance.

"I heard from Wyrm 3 that you're an exceptional prodigy in both pill refinement and cultivation. I've always wanted to meet you, but I didn't think my wish would be granted so soon," Fox 3 replied with a smile.

It was Immortal Lord Hot Flame's turn to be in disbelief now, and he turned to Han Li as he asked, "Fellow Daoist Li, you're also a member of the Reincarnation Palace?"

Chapter 644: Departure

"My apologies for keeping this identity from you," Han Li said as he cupped his fist toward Immortal Lord Hot Flame in an apologetic salute.

He had considered altering his appearance before coming here, but that didn't seem like a good idea.

He had resided in the Leisure Valley alongside Immortal Lord Hot Flame for quite some time, and if he were to come here under an alternate identity, there was a very good chance that Immortal Lord Hot Flame would eventually catch on, and that would likely attract him much suspicion from Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong.

Hence, it was better for him to come clean right away to avoid potential misunderstandings.

"There's no need to apologize, Fellow Daoist Li. After all, I hadn't been entirely forthcoming with you, either," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a wry smile.

"The fact that we all know each other certainly makes things easier," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"Fellow Daoist Huo was just telling me about how you and I are both avid wine enthusiasts. Come, let's have a drink before we discuss anything else," Fox 3 said with a wide smile.

Han Li didn't turn down the offer, and he sat down across from Shi Chuankong, where he was handed a silver cup.

Back in the Leisure Valley, Immortal Lord Hot Flame was second only to Daoist Master Jingyang when it came to his penchant for drinking, and it seemed like Fox 3 shared this interest.

Fox 3 was a little loose and lackadaisical in his personality and demeanor, but that didn't bother Han Li.

......

Black Mountain Immortal Region, Origin Turtle Continent, Flowing Cloud City.

The Origin Turtle Continent was situated on the southeastern border of the Black Mountain Immortal Region, while Flowing Cloud City was on the southernmost tip of the Origin Turtle Continent. However, despite its secluded location, it was one of the most prosperous mega cities in the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

The city walls were so tall that they were almost concealed in the clouds, and the city was filled with wide streets and countless tall and majestic buildings stretching as far as the eyes could see.

There were people everywhere, as well as streaks of light whizzing through the sky, presenting an incredibly bustling and prosperous sight to behold.

This was a coastal city, so outside the city was the boundless black sea. The surface of the sea was churning violently, and there were enormous waves passing through one after another.

This sea was referred to as the Violent Sea, and the conditions here were terrible all year round, making for an extremely hostile environment.

Despite the terrible conditions in the Violent Sea, it harbored a vast abundance of the world's origin qi, so it was home to countless demon beasts and precious spirit materials. Hence, countless cultivators flocked to Flowing Cloud City to venture into the Violent Sea in search of treasures, and that was how the city had become so prosperous over time.

The other important reason for the city's prosperity was that it was home to a teleportation array that led to the Black Soil Immortal Region.

The four allied immortal regions weren't separated by primordial lands, but they weren't directly connected to one another, either, and there were some perilous terrains to be traversed between them.

The Violent Sea was the obstacle that stood between the Black Mountain Immortal Region and the Black Soil Immortal Region.

At the center of Flowing Cloud City was a giant white mountain that extended all the way up into the clouds, and there were countless buildings constructed on the mountain.

From afar, the entire mountain resembled a giant beehive, presenting a spectacular sight to behold.

Halfway up the mountain was a three-story white pagoda, hanging above the entrance of which was a plaque that was several dozen feet in size, bearing the words "Flying Immortal Hall."

This was the teleportation hall of Flowing Cloud City, and it was entirely constructed from white jade blocks.

After stepping into the hall and passing through a white corridor, one would arrive in a giant white hall that was several thousand feet in size.

To the left of the hall was a rectangular white jade table, behind which stood several golden-robed Heavenly Court cultivators who were processing documents for the cultivators lined up in front of the table.

To the right of the hall were dozens of teleportation arrays of different sizes, beside each of which stood a jade plaque that denoted the destination of the array.

These teleportation arrays were all buzzing incessantly while occasionally flashing with white light, teleportation cultivators in and out of the city.

Right at this moment, a burst of blinding wind light erupted within one of the teleportation arrays, and around a dozen figures emerged within it.

Among them was a group of four figures, three young men and a white-haired elderly man, and they were none other than Han Li's group.

All four of them had altered their appearances somewhat in order to avoid trouble.

They had traveled here mostly through teleportation arrays, only occasionally traveling by flight instead whenever some trouble arose, and it had taken them over thirty years to finally arrive at Flowing Cloud City.

"We're finally here. Let's go," Fox 3 said as he made his way out of the teleportation array.

"Are we not going to take a teleportation array from here? The Violent Sea is not going to be easy to traverse," Immortal Lord Hot Flame hurriedly asked.

"Taking interregion teleportation arrays is different from traveling on normal teleportation arrays. The checks are very stringent, so we have to make some preparations first," Fox 3 explained through voice transmission.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame gave a slight nod upon hearing this and followed along, as did Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

Fox 3 had spent countless years traveling from one immortal region to another, accruing a tremendous amount of experience as a result, so he was responsible for organizing the itinerary for this trip.

In fact, it was no exaggeration to say that he had played a vital role in getting everyone to Flowing Cloud City safely.

He seemed lackadaisical and unreliable on the surface, but in reality, he possessed impeccable attention to detail and often considered things in a more in-depth fashion than his companions.

The four of them quickly made their way out of the white pagoda, which was situated at quite a high altitude, so the city down below and the Violent Sea outside were all clearly visible from this vantage point.

"So this is the Violent Sea. It really is a spectacular sight," Han Li praised as he looked out at the turbulent sea in the distance.

Bursts of thunderous rumbling were ringing out incessantly from afar, and even teh white mountain was trembling slightly.

"This is nothing. The waves deep in the Violent Sea are far more massive, and that's where the real fun is," Fox 3 said with a smile.

"Oh? Have you ventured deep into the Violent Sea before, Fellow Daoist Fox 3?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"That was a very long time ago. On that occasion, I was also traveling to the Black Soil Immortal Region from Flowing Cloud City. At the time, I decided on the spur of the moment that I would cross the Violent Sea, and it took me several decades to complete the journey," Fox 3 replid with a smile.

"I've heard that not only is the Violent Sea home to all types of demon beasts, there's also a very special race of beings residing there. Not only are they extremely powerful themselves, they can control the marine demon beasts in battle, and with all of the natural hazards present in the Violent Sea to boot, very few people are able to make that journey," Han Li said.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Shi Chuankong turned to Fox 3 with intrigued expressions upon hearing this.

"You're a very knowledgeable man, Brother Li. The Violent Sea is indeed a very dangerous place. In particular, that race of sea-dwelling beings that you spoke of are extremely resentful of human cultivators, and very few people can survive an encounter with them.

“I was unfortunate enough to have been pursued by those beings during my journey, and they hunted me for over a decade. In the end, I was only able to escape using a spatial immortal talisman, but I still sustained some injuries in the process," Fox 3 said with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

"May I ask what your cultivation base was back then?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked in a hesitant manner.

"That was many years ago. At the time, I had just progressed to the High Zenith Stage, so my ego was severely inflated, and that was what led me to do something so foolish," Fox 3 chuckled.

Han Li was astonished to hear this.

He had witnessed Fox 3 in battle, and the fact that he was unable to cross the Violent Sea at the early-High Zenith Stage was sufficient testament to just how dangerous a place it was.

"I've heard that there are Great Encompassment Stage beings among the race of sea-dwelling beings. Even the Heavenly Court couldn't eradicate them, and that was why it had gone to such great lengths to construct this interregion teleportation array," Fox 3 continued.

"I see," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a nod.

"Let's go and find an inn in the city to stay in for now," Fox 3 said, then took flight and departed from the pagoda.

Han Li's trio followed along, and the four of them quickly arrived in a clean and quiet inn, where they booked four rooms.

After setting down some belongings in his room, Han Li made his way to Fox 3's room and asked him what measures they had to take in order to access the interregion teleportation array.

"There's no hurry. It's not every day that we get to come to Flowing Cloud City, so it would be a great pity if we left so quickly. I know of a restaurant in the city that serves exceptional dishes and wine. Let's go have a meal there before discuss anything else."

Instead of answering Han Li's question, Fox 3 began to enthusiastically introduce all of the fine restaurants in the city, much to Han Li's exasperation.

On the way here, whenever they passed through a city, Fox 3 would be sure to explore all of the delicacies that the city had to offer, and at times, they would even stay in a city for half a month at a time, thereby severely delaying their itinerary.

"Did I hear fine wine?"

At this moment, Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Shi Chuankong also entered the room, and the former was immediately enthused upon hearing mention of delectable wine.

"It's been hard work traveling all this way, so it would be good to take a rest," Shi Chuankong said with a faint smile.

"I couldn't have said it better myself, Brother Shi. Let's go right away," Fox 3 said in an eager voice as he patted Shi Chuankong on the shoulder, then made his way out of the room.

Han Li could only heave an internal sigh before following along.

He wasn't all that interested in the delicacies that the city had to offer, but it would be rather unbecoming of him to refuse to go along.

Chapter 645: The Finer Things in Life

Fox 3 led Han Li's trio through a series of twists and turns in the city, and they soon arrived at an opulent five-story restaurant.

The bottom two levels of the restaurant were normal dining areas consisting of open halls filled with large tables, while the third, fourth, and fifth floors were dedicated solely to VIP booths.

Even though it wasn't mealtime yet, the first two floors were already laden with people, and all of the patrons were cultivators of decent cultivation bases.

Furthermore, there were also many cultivators lined up outside the restaurant, just like one would see in a mortal restaurant, and Han Li's trio was quite surprised to see this.

Fox 3 didn't seem to be surprised at all to see this, and he made his way into the restaurant, then pulled out a badge before waving it at an approaching waiter.

"Welcome, esteemed guests. Please come with me."

As soon as the waiter caught a glimpse of the badge, he immediately let the group to a booth on the fifth floor.

All of the furniture in the booth was very tasteful and refined, striking a good balance between luxury and practicality, and as soon as Fox 3 sat down, he immediately rattled off a long order, capped off by a large flagon of wine that was around a foot in height.

Wisps of white mist were rising up out of the mouth of the flagon before slowly dissipating in the air, releasing a peculiar aroma that immediately drew the interest of Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Shi Chuankong.

"This is some exceptional wine!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame praised with an excited gleam in his eyes.

"Of course. Most of the people who come to this restaurant are here for this wine," Fox 3 said as he poured everyone a cup of wine each, then downed his own cup of wine in one go, following which a blissful look appeared on his face.

Han Li took a sip from his own cup of wine, and his eyes also lit up.

The wine was a transparent amber color, and it coated his entire tongue in an indescribable rich fragrance that slowly seeped through his entire body.

The flavor of the wine consisted of a combination of over a hundred different exquisite flavors, some of which he was familiar with, some of which he had never tasted, and some of which he had never even thought of.

Despite the vast abundance of flavors, all of them were able to shine through without any particular stealing too much of the spotlight, and it was more exquisite than any wine that Han Li had ever tasted.

"How truly exquisite! What is the name of this wine?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked after taking a sip out of his cup.

"This wine is called Amber Immortal, and it's the main reason why this restaurant is so famous. Whenever the Heavenly Court holds its Gathering of Immortals, this Amber Immortal is always the drink of choice," Fox 3 introduced.

"What's this Gathering of Immortals?" Han Li asked as he set down his cup.

"It's an event held by the Heavenly Court. Every once in a while, the Heavenly Court will gather all of the palace masters of the Immortal Palaces to the Heavenly Court to discuss certain important matters, and it could be said that this is the most important event on the Heavenly Court calendar," Fox 3 explained.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this, but Fox 3 paid no heed to this as he began digging into the meal.

Shi Chuankong also seemed to be quite an avid foodie, while Immortal Lord Hot Flame was much more interested in the Amber Immortal and was having one cup after another.

Before long, the entire table of dishes and wine had been devoured, and Fox 3 patted his own slightly bulging belly as he sighed, "Nothing compares with the feeling of a good meal. What's the point in working so hard in cultivation if you can't even enjoy the finer things in life?"

"I agree!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame concurred loudly, while Shi Chuankong remained silent.

"Now that we're all fed, let's discuss how we're going to get to the Black Soil Immortal Region," Han Li said as he set down his cup.

At the same time, he made a hand seal to conjure up an azure light barrier around the entire booth.

"Do you ever relax, Brother Li?" Fox 3 complained in a lazy voice.

"Brother Li is right. Flowing Cloud City is a major city in the Black Mountain Immortal Region, so it's constantly under strict surveillance from the Heavenly Court. Hence, it's best for us to leave this place as soon as possible," Shi Chuankong said with a serious expression, while Immortal Lord Hot Flame also nodded in agreement.

"Fine, fine, let's get serious then," Fox 3 sighed as he put away his joking expression.

"Just as Brother Shi said, Flowing Cloud City is constantly under heavy surveillance from the Heavenly Court. In particular, that interregion teleportation array is very closely monitored, and anyone who wishes to use it must undergo stringent examinations," Fox 3 said.

"What does that entail?" Han Li asked.

"There are two areas of scrutiny, the first of which pertains to one's identity. In order to access the interregion teleportation array, one requires an official identity that's recognized by the Black Mountain Immortal Region. That's not difficult to arrange as long as we're willing to spend the Immortal Origin Stones. The problem is the examination by Heavenly Mirror," Fox 3 explained.

"What's this Heavenly Mirror?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

"It's a sensory array developed by the Heavenly Court, and it's extremely sensitive to auras. It has a memory function, and it's said to be holding information pertaining to all fugitives currently wanted by the Heavenly Court, including their appearance, the cultivation arts and immortal treasures that they use, etc.

“For wanted fugitives like ourselves, we could easily fall prey to this Heavenly Mirror Array, and I'm sure I don't need to explain what'll transpire if that happens," Fox 3 replied.

"A sensory array that can record all of the information of the Heavenly Court's wanted fugitives? That's very impressive!" Han Li praised.

"I'm not a fan of the Heavenly Court, but it's undeniably a vastly powerful and resourceful organization that is unmatched in many areas. However, setting up a Heavenly Mirror Array is extremely costly and complicated, so they're only present in a handful of important locations," Fox 3 said.

Everyone else nodded in response.

"Brother Shi, after what happened back in Jade Gathering City, you're most likely on the Immortal Slaying List as well, and the same applies to Brother Huo, so the two of you need to find ways to completely conceal your auras to avoid detection," Fox 3 said as he turned to Shi Chuankong and Immortal Lord Hot Flame, both of whom nodded in response once again with contemplative expressions.

"As for Brother Li, I don't know if you're wanted by the Heavenly Court, but the Heavenly Mirror Array's primary function is to catch members of the Reincarnation Palace, so you have to be careful as well. I can sense that there's an abnormally high abundance of baleful qi in your body. I can also see that you're somehow concealing it, but the concealment isn't perfect, and you'll definitely be caught by the Heavenly Mirror Array," Fox 3 said.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this. He had constantly been taking Origin Void Pills to conceal the baleful qi in his body, but Fox 3 was somehow able to see through it right away.

"I'm currently facing a baleful decay, so there's naturally going to be more baleful qi in my body than normal. Surely everyone at this stage in their cultivation will have the same problem. Is that alone enough for the Heavenly Court to accuse me of being a member of the Reincarnation Palace?" Han Li asked.

"Now matter who it is, as long as they're determined to possess an abnormally high amount of baleful qi in their body, they'll immediately be captured by the Heavenly Court. As for why that is, I'm not sure myself," Fox 3 said.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a thought occurred to him.

It was clear that the Heavenly Court wasn't doing this for no reason. There seemed to be some type of connection between the Reincarnation Palace and Gray Immortals, and the most prominent trait of Gray Immortals is baleful qi.

"In terms of baleful qi concealment, I have something that could work," Fox 3 said after a brief hesitation.

"Oh? Please enlighten me, Brother Fox," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Fox 3 flipped a hand over to produce a silver jade vial, then tossed it at Han Li.

Han Li caught the vial before removing the stopper, and a small silver pill rolled out from inside.

To his surprise, the pill was different in color from the Origin Void Pill, but it possessed a very similar aura, except this pill's aura was far more pronounced.

"What is this?" Han Li asked as he turned to Fox 3.

"This is an Origin Baleful Pill that's very effective for concealing the aura of baleful qi," Fox 3 replied.

"This must be a very precious pill, I can't just take it from you," Han Li said with a hesitant expression.

"It's fine, I don't have any use for it anyway, so why not give it to someone who can actually make use of it?" Fox 3 replied, brushing off Han Li's concerns.

Han Li turned his gaze back to the pill, and after carefully inspecting it momentarily with his spiritual sense, he didn't hesitate any longer before taking the pill.

As soon as he swallowed the pill, it immediately melted into a burst of cool energy that flowed through his entire body, suppressing all of the baleful qi that it encountered.

Even the baleful qi vortexes in his immortal acupoints had virtually completely stopped revolving, and it didn't take long before most of the baleful qi in his body had been suppressed, much to his elation.

Furthermore, the Origin Baleful Pill still hadn't been completely refined yet, so its baleful qi concealment effect still hadn't been fully realized.

By Han Li's estimates, the pill's effect could last for around a decade.

Chapter 646: Preparations

"Do you have any more of these Origin Baleful Pills, or perhaps the pill recipe, Fellow Daoist Fox 3? I'm willing to purchase them from you or exchange other items for them," Han Li said.

"I'm afraid not. I only secured this pill by chance, so I don't have any more pills or the recipe," Fox 3 replied with a shake of his head.

"In that case, would you be able to tell me where you got this pill from?" Han Li asked.

"Prior to reaching the High Zenith Stage, I saw someone purchase a vial of Origin Baleful Pills for a thousand Immortal Origin Stones at an underground exchange convention, so I decided to steal it. There were two pills in the vial, and I used one of them. As for where these pills came from, I have no clue," Fox 3 replied.

Han Li fell silent upon hearing this.

Shortly thereafter, he raised his head and summoned a storage tool as he said, "In any case, I have to thank you, Brother Fox. Here are five hundred Immortal Origin Stones for the pill."

"Don't bring money into this, I'm giving this pill to you as a friend," Fox 3 said as he rose to his feet, refusing the storage tool being handed to him.

"Just accept the pill. Fox 3 isn't going to hold a grudge against you for it," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Fox 3," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

"I've been to this city quite a few times, so just leave the matter of official identities to me. Give me a few days, and I'll have that sorted out, but you'll have to find your own ways to deal with the Heavenly Mirror Array.

“Let me warn you that this is not to be taken lightly, so don't think you can just get by with some half-arsed scheme," Fox 3 said with a serious expression, then vanished from the spot as a burst of silver light, leaving Han Li's trio behind with grim looks on their faces.

Shortly thereafter, the three of them also departed from the restaurant and returned to the inn.

......

Close to half a month later.

Han Li's trio were gathered in Fox 3's room, and Fox 3 himself had just returned, looking a little weary, but also rather excited.

"It looks like all of you are well prepared," Fox 3 remarked with a nod and a smile.

At this moment, the only thing that remained unchanged about Han Li's trio was their appearances, while everything else had undergone a complete transformation.

Shi Chuankong had changed into a white robe, and his devilish aura had completely faded, replaced by a burst of pure yang-attribute aura fluctuations.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was holding a purple cane with arcs of purple lightning occasionally flashing over its surface, and the fiery power in his body had transformed into an aura of lightning that resonated perfectly with his purple cane.

Han Li had also changed into some different clothes, and there were bursts of water-attribute energy fluctuations emanating out of his body.

During the past few days, he hadn't set foot outside of the inn at all, focusing all of his efforts on refining the Origin Baleful Pill to suppress the baleful qi in his body. At the same time, he had stowed everything that could expose him, including his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, the Profound Heavenly Gourd, Daoist Xie, the Flame of Essence, and even the storage tools that he normally used into the Flower Branch domain.

As an additional safety precaution, Han Li had even set up an array inside the Flower Branch domain that encompassed everything and masked their auras, including even Mo Guang.

"You issued us a very serious warning last time, so we had to take you seriously," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a smile.

Fox 3 nodded in response, then pulled out three identification tokens before handing them to Han Li's trio.

The tokens were yellow badges that seemed to have been crafted out of some type of wooden material.

Han Li glanced at his own badge to find his name etched on it, but only his Li surname had been preserved, while the rest of his name had been altered.

On the other side was a hexagonal floral design, and it seemed to be the emblem of some clan or sect.

"Right now, we are outer sect elders of the Flowing Sand Continent's Heavenly Sand Sect. We are currently traveling to the Black Soil Immortal Region to purchase some cultivation resources under orders from our sect master," Fox 3 said.

As he was speaking, his body began to slowly transform within a layer of warped white light, and he quickly transformed into a white-haired young man with a completely different aura from before.

Han Li's trio collectively nodded in response, and the four of them emerged from the room before flying toward the giant white mountain in the city, arriving at the entrance of the Flying Immortal Hall once again.

Just like last time, the Flying Immortal Hall was very busy, with many cultivators entering and exiting the building.

Instead of entering through the main entrance, Fox 3 led Han Li's trio to a side entrance, at the foot of which was a staircase.

The four of them had only just stepped onto the staircase when Fox 3 suddenly turned around and instructed, "Each of you, give me two hundred Immortal Origin Stones."

Han Li's trio faltered slightly upon hearing this.

"What for?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"To avoid some trouble, of course," Fox 3 replied with a mysterious grin.

This was not a very satisfactory answer, but Han Li's trio had no reason to doubt him, so they did as they were told, giving him two hundred Immortal Origin Stones each.

After that, the four of them quickly scaled the staircase and arrived in a white hall.

There were several Heavenly Court cultivators standing inside, and as soon as Han Li's group entered the room, the cultivator closest to them, a silver-haired young man, immediately approached them with a warm smile as he asked, "Are you planning to use the interregion teleportation array, seniors?"

The other people in the hall were a little vexed upon seeing this, but none of them said anything.

"That's right," Fox 3 replied with a nod.

The silver-haired young man was ecstatic to hear this, and he immediately said, "Please come with me, seniors."

The young man led Han Li's group into another hall, within which was a stone table with an imposing man seated behind it and an elderly man standing beside him.

The imposing man was a Golden Immortal, and the golden robe that he wore was far more luxurious than the ones worn by the silver-haired young man and the elderly man.

The imposing man immediately turned to Han Li's group upon hearing their footsteps, and the silver-haired young man reported, "Administrator Fang, these seniors wish to use the interregion teleportation array."

The imposing man nodded in response, then turned to Han Li's group as he declared, "The teleportation fee is one thousand Immortal Origin Stones per person. Before that, I have to verify your identification information and conduct a screening process by having all of you pass through an inspection array."

Han L's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Fox 3 hadn't informed them of the teleportation fee prior to this, and Han Li was quite surprised by how expensive it was. A thousand Immortal Origin Stones was enough to purchase a graded immortal treasure, albeit only one of the lowest grade.

"Here are our identity tokens," Fox 3 said with a smile as he summoned his wooden badge before handing it to the imposing man, and Han Li's trio quickly followed suit.

The man fished a gold-covered book out of his robe pocket, then waved it at the wooden badges, and the book released a beam of golden light that enveloped the four badges.

Immediately thereafter, a layer of golden light emerged over the book, and some lines of text and accompanying images appeared on its pages.

"So the four of you are elders of the Heavenly Sand Sect. Why are you traveling to the Black Soil Immortal Region?" the man asked.

"We are under instructions from our sect master to purchase a batch of pill refinement ingredients from the Black Soil Immortal Region," Fox 3 replied as he took a step forward, then covertly stuffed a storage ring into the man's hand.

The man briefly inspected the contents of the storage ring with his spiritual sense, and his demeanor instantly softened significantly.

"I see. That certainly is a long way to travel just to purchase some pill refinement ingredients. There are no issues with your identification tokens. Come with me," the burly man said as he rose to his feet, then returned the four wooden badges to Han Li's group while leading the way deeper into the hall, followed by the silver-haired young man and the elderly man.

Han Li's group was led into another hall that was completely constructed from a type of silver stone material that was emitting a fluorescent glow.

At the center of the hall was a circular golden array that was several hundred feet in size. There were countless complex and intertwining array patterns within the array, and there were also eight golden pillars around it, each of which stood at several dozen feet tall.

The stone pillars and the walls of the hall were also riddled with array patterns that were connected to the array down below, and atop each pillar sat a golden-robed cultivator, all of whom were currently meditating with their eyes closed.

Hovering directly above the golden array was a massive golden mirror, and the air within the array was buzzing incessantly.

An intrigued look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

So this is the Heavenly Mirror Array...

"Activate the array and conduct a close examination. Make sure not to miss even the smallest of details," the imposing man instructed with a serious expression.

The eight golden-robed cultivators opened their eyes before chanting an incantation while releasing a string of golden incantation seals.

A burst of radiant golden light interspersed with countless golden runes immediately erupted out of array, forming a pillar of golden light that surged into the mirror up above.

A series of golden patterns instantly appeared on the mirror before rapidly spreading outward, quickly filling the entire mirror.

These golden patterns formed a series of strange designs that resembled blinking golden eyes, and waves of golden ripples surged out of these eyes to encompass the array down below.

"Please take turns walking through the array, fellow daoists," the imposing man said as he turned to Han Li's group.

The four of them exchanged a glance with one another, following which Fox 3 led the way, stepping into the golden array first.

The array rippled slightly, and countless threads of golden light emerged from the array patterns on the surrounding pillars, gently roaming over Fox 3's entire body like feelers.

The ripples surging out of the eyes on the golden mirror also brightened slightly while fusing as one, forming a series of golden halos that encompassed Fox 3's body.

Fox 3 remained calm and collected as he made his way forward, and he quickly made his way to the other side of the array without any incident.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this.

"Next," the imposing man said as he beckoned to Han Li's trio.

Shi Chuankong was the second one to make his way into the golden array, and the same inspection process was carried out.

Just like Fox 3, Shi Chuankong was also able to make it out of the array without any incident.

Before the imposing man had a chance to speak again, Han Li stepped into the golden array in a calm manner.

Chapter 647: Underground City

As soon as Han Li stepped into the array, he immediately felt a burst of indescribable pressure weighing down upon his body.

He felt as if he were standing on a seabed with a boundless volume of water above him, and in that instant, he was completely immobilized.

The threads of golden light converged from all directions, surrounding him before revolving around his body, while a series of golden ripples descended upon him from above.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he felt two bursts of power surge into his body from the array, one gentle and inquisitive, while the other was vast and insistent.

The two bursts of power surged through his entire body, inspecting everything that they passed through.

Han Li made no attempt to resist these two bursts of power as they only lingered in his body for a brief moment before his mobility was restored, and he continued to make his way out of the array with a calm expression.

Ever since he left the inn, he had been circulating his immortal spiritual power in accordance with the method stipulated in the Water Divination Time Arts.

On top of that, he had also used a secret technique to seal away the majority of the tremendous energy in his body, concealing most of the aura of his true spirit bloodlines and the Great Universe Origin Arts.

He had done everything that he could to conceal any information that could expose him, and if the Heavenly Mirror Array could still identify him, then he would just have to accept such an outcome.

The golden array continued buzzing as the two bursts of power flowed through Han Li's body, lingering momentarily at the seals in his body and in the fingers of his right hand, but ultimately raising no alarm.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief, then made it the rest of the way through the array to arrive by Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong's side.

The two of them gave Han Li a nod, then turned their attention to Immortal Lord Hot Flame, who had also stepped into the array at this point, and was able to make it through without incident as well.

"You can come through to the interregion teleportation array now, fellow daoists. The teleportation fee will be one thousand Immortal Origin Stones per person," the imposing man said.

Han Li and the others each handed over a thousand Immortal Origin Stones to the man, and while handing over his teleportation fee, Fox 3 snuck yet another storage ring into the man's hand.

A faint smile appeared on his face, and he instructed Han Li's group to come with him, then led the way into another hall.

There was a teleportation array that was over a hundred feet in size on the ground in the hall, and there were countless silver patterns in the array, not inferior in number to that of the Heavenly Mirror Array.

Bursts of silver light were flashing incessantly within the array, giving off formidable spatial fluctuations.

Han Li's group made their way into the teleportation array under instructions from the imposing man, who then swept a sleeve through the air to release four streaks of white light, each of which adhered itself to one of Han Li and his companions, revealing themselves to be four white triangular talismans.

After that, the imposing man summoned a silver badge and began chanting an incantation, and the silver-haired young man and the elderly man also made their way over to the other side of the array before summoning a jade badge each.

The silver light within the teleportation array instantly brightened significantly, and Han Li's group vanished shortly thereafter.

Following the successful teleportation, the flashing light and spatial fluctuations in the array quickly subsided, and the silver-haired young man and the elderly man made their way over to the imposing man's side.

"You two can have these Immortal Origin Stones," the imposing man said as he summoned a storage tool before tossing them at the two men.

The two of them were ecstatic, and they immediately extended a collective curtsey.

"Thank you, Administrator Fang!"

Only after the imposing man had departed did the two of them open the storage ring to find a hundred Immortal Origin Stones inside, with each of them claiming half.

"I'd always heard that working on the second floor of the Flying Immortal Hall was a very lucrative job, but I didn't think it was this good! At this rate, it won't take long before I can afford a graded immortal treasure!" the silver-haired young man said in an excited manner.

"Of course! Why else do you think so many people want to come here?" the elderly man chuckled.

The two of them chatted for a while longer, then departed from the hall.

......

In the northern region of the Black Soil Immortal Region was a long and thin continent by the name of the Black Dragon Continent.

The northern part of the continent was filled with mountains and rivers with extreme topographic variance and very complex terrains.

Due to the special terrain in the region, there were very many cities there, but very few large ones, and the largest of all of the continent's northern cities was Black Glaze City, which was situated in the Drawer Beam Mountain Range.

Even though the northern region of the Black Soil Immortal Region was very sparsely populated, it wasn't a very perilous place. Instead, it was rife with all types of precious spirit soils, and as a result, it was home to many spirit medicines and mountain spirits.

Many of the trading houses in the nearby immortal regions that were in the spirit medicine business saw this place as a blessing from the heavens, and there were many branches of these trading houses established nearby, harvesting and planting spirit medicines while also mining for mineral and spirit soil resources.

Black Glaze City derived its name from a special type of black spirit soil found in the Drawer Beam Mountain Range.

Black Glaze Soil contained abundant spiritual qi, but it couldn't be used for planting spirit medicines. Instead, it was far better suited to being fired into puppets.

Due to its unique cohesiveness and spiritual qi retention properties, introducing certain ratios of Black Glaze Soil during the puppet refinement process could significantly increase the chances of successful refinement, as well as the caliber of the final puppet.

It was exactly because of this that Black Glaze Soil was extremely sought after, and following the past close to one million years of excavation, almost all of the Black Glaze Soil in the entire mountain range had been exhausted.

With all of the underground Black Glaze Soil reserves emptied out, the entire Drawer Beam Mountain Range had sunk downward. As a result, it had become a flatter and smoother area than nearby places, thereby making it an ideal site for constructing large ferry stations for ships to dock at.

Hence, starting from over a hundred thousand years ago, all mining activities had ceased in the Drawer Beam Mountain Range. Several large ferry stations had been constructed in some areas of the mountain range, while the rest of it had been covered in spirit soil and converted into spirit medicine fields.

As for the central area of the mountain range, a giant underground city had been constructed there, and that was Black Glaze City.

The city bore several hundred kilometers deep into the earth and was split up into seven levels, thereby giving it its alternative name of "Sevenfold City."

On the deepest seventh level of the city was a large teleportation hall that received cultivators who had come from the nearby Black Mountain Immortal Region.

At this moment, there were four figures making their way out of the teleportation hall, and they were none other than Han Li's group.

Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong were leading the way, while Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame trailed along behind them, and the latter was looking rather tense.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame? Are you feeling a little uneasy now that we've returned to the Black Soil Immortal Region?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"The Black Mountain Immortal Region isn't far away from the Black Soil Immortal Region, but I've never dared to come back here. Hence, I don't know what this immortal region is like now, and I can't help but feel a little apprehensive," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a wry smile.

"This Black Soil Immortal Region really does seem to be a unique place. I've never seen a teleportation hall constructed so deep underground."

Han Li inspected his surroundings to discover that the ceiling of the hall was extremely tall, and there was a series of giant glowing jewels embedded into it, giving off dazzling radiance that illuminated the entire space.

The hall behind him was embedded into the rock face, while up ahead was a spacious hall, and there were two wide passageways branching off from the hall, leading to the left and the right.

"Right now, we are inside an underground city constructed out of a mine. In addition to this teleportation hall, there are also many inns and shops down here. I'll take you on a tour of the nearby area so you get to see what this place is all about," Fox 3 said to Han Li, seemingly quite familiar with the area.

"I'm looking forward to it," Han Li replied with a smile.

The four of them made their way down the passageway on the left, and sure enough, there was a series of buildings embedded into the mountain faces on either side of the passageway, and there were many signs outside the buildings, just like one would expect to see in inns and shops in normal cities.

"You won't find many merchants or travelers on the seventh level of the city, but the branches of all of the major trading houses have been set up here, and the two largest inns in the city are also on this level," Fox 3 introduced as the group made its way down the boardwalk.

They passed through an arched opening, then walked a few hundred meters before arriving in a spacious hall. There was a two-story stone archway situated in the hall near the mountain face, and there were all types of intricate designs engraved upon it, presenting a mesmerizing sight to behold.

At the top of the archway was a huge plaque that bore the words "Hundred Creations Pavilion" in large, golden characters.

Han Li had stopped in front of the archway and was looking up at the plaque, and upon noticing this, Shi Chuankong asked, "Do you want to take a look inside, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"Does this place have anything to do with the Hundred Creations Mountain?" Han Li asked.

"Have you not heard of Hundred Creations Pavilions, Fellow Daoist Li? The Hundred Creations Mountain is renowned across the entire True Immortal Realm for its tool refinement prowess, and it has shops set up across many immortal regions in the form of these Hundred Creations Pavilions," Shi Chuankong explained.

"I see. It seems like I really do need to get out more," Han Li replied with a smile.

Even though he had spent a lot of time with Daoist Master Jingyang in the past, most of the conversations between them pertaining to the Hundred Creations Mountain were related to the art of tool refinement, so he wasn't aware of these other facets.

"I suppose that's not too surprising. I've heard from Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3 that you've been living in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region prior to coming to the Black Mountain Immortal Region. The Northern Glacial Immortal Region is a very secluded place, and I don't think there are any Hundred Creations Pavilions there," Fox 3 said.

Shi Chuankong's brows furrowed ever so slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to take a subtle glance at Han Li.

Han Li noticed his gaze and gave him a smile, and Shi Chuankong nodded in response before looking away.

Chapter 648: Ferry Station

After walking a few more kilometers, Han Li's group drew to a halt in front of another arched opening.

Han Li's trio turned to Fox 3, and the latter said, "In here is one of the teleportation arrays leading to the sixth level that I was telling all of you about. There are quite a few more of these littered throughout the city."

With that, Fox 3 stepped through the opening, followed by Han Li and the others.

As soon as they made their way through the opening, Han Li caught sight of a teleportation array that was over a hundred feet in size on the ground not far away.

Beside the array was a table, behind which sat a green-skinned being that resembled a lizard. At the moment, the foreign being seemed to be sleeping, and it displayed no reaction to the arrival of Han Li's group.

Fox 3 made his way over to the table, then tossed a pouch of top-grade spirit stones onto it, then led Han Li and the others into the array.

The green-skinned being took a moment to inspect the contents of the pouch, upon which he discovered that there was an additional tip enclosed on top of the teleportation fee. An elated look appeared on his face as he hurriedly sprang up from behind the table, working to activate the array while extending a bow toward Fox 3, who nodded in response.

Following a flash of light within the array, Han Li's group vanished from the spot.

The green-skinned being turned back to the top-grade spirit stones sitting on the table with an excited expression, yet right as he was about to inspect the contents of the storage pouch again, his expression suddenly stiffened.

He looked down at his own bare fingers, and his elation was instantly replaced by fury.

On the sixth level of the city, Fox 3 was playing with a green storage ring as he made his way out of the teleportation hall.

"You're going to land yourself in trouble sooner or later if you keep dabbling in petty theft like this," Shi Chuankong sighed with a resigned expression.

"That was very impressive, Fellow Daoist Fox 3. You were able to instantly sever that man's connection with his storage ring without being detected at all," Han Li praised with a smile.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame remained silently as he reflexively checked his own storage bracelet, and he was quite relieved to see that it was still there.

"I've been sticking to the straight and narrow for too long recently, so I was getting a little antsy," Fox 3 chuckled.

Upon reaching the sixth level, there was a noticeable increase in the number of people making their way along the boardwalk, and most of them appeared to be human, but there was also a clear increase in the number of foreign beings around.

There were also far more shops that lined the mountain faces, and all manners of flags and banners had been hung up outside the shops, most of which were selling spirit soils and spirit plants, but of course, there were also some shops that sold treasures and pills.

After that, Han Li's group made their way up a few more levels, and the things were much the same, but the higher they went, the more densely populated the levels became, and as a result, their surroundings also became progressively more bustling and chaotic.

However, Fox 3 seemed to be quite fond of this type of chaotic environment, and the higher he went, the more leisurely his pace became. Along the way, he even stopped by a restaurant and treated everyone to a meal.

The restaurant was quite renowned for the spirit wine that it served, and Fox 3 had heard that Han Li was an avid wine enthusiast as well, so he offered to gift a few flagons to Han Li. However, having spent so much time with Daoist Hu Yan, Han Li had developed a taste only for the finest spirit wines, and the spirit wine in question wasn't quite up to his standards, so he tactfully turned down the offer.

By the time Han Li and the others made their way up to the surface, half a day had already passed by.

It was close to nighttime, and the light of the dying sun was spilling down from the west, basking the city in a warm, red glow.

Han Li could see a series of giant docks situated around the outskirts of the city, hovering beside which was a collection of mountainous immortal ships.

"The True Mantra Sect ruins are located somewhere in the Illusory Smoke Swamp of the Floating Mountain Continent, which is, in turn, situated in the central region of the Black Soil Immortal Region. There won't be many teleportation arrays along the way, so we'll mostly be traveling by ship, and it'll take us around thirty years to get there," Fox 3 said.

"Why are we traveling by ship? Surely it'll be faster for us to travel using our flying immortal treasures," Han Li said in a perplexed manner.

"That's correct, but there are some special rules in the Black Soil Immortal Region, so flight is prohibited in certain areas. There are even some restrictions set up in some places, and if you try to force your way through them, there's a very good chance you'll catch the attention of the Immortal Palace," Fox 3 explained.

"I didn't know there were so many annoying rules in the Black Soil Immortal Region," Immortal Lord Hot Flame scoffed.

"There are many spirit fields and mines in the south, most of which are privately owned by the major trading houses, so trespassing is strictly prohibited. On top of that, there are also massive swamps between the continents of the Black Soil Immortal Region, some of which are home to many fearsome demon beasts.

“In fact, even Great Encompassment Stage demon beasts have been known to prowl those areas, so it would be very dangerous to try and fly through them," Fox 3 explained.

"These are all rules put in place by the Black Soil Immortal Palace in order to strengthen their control. The rules aren't enforced all that tightly in some more rural places, but things get a little troublesome near the larger cities," Shi Chuankong added.

"All of the ships of the trading houses have set routes that have been registered with the Immortal Palace, so they're able to make the journey without drawing any ire," Fox 3 said.

"Back when our True Mantra Sect was still standing, the Black Soil Immortal Region didn't have any of these bullshit rules!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed in an indignant and melancholic fashion.

"In that case, it does sound like traveling by ship is our best option," Han Li said with a nod.

"Not necessarily. Even though all of the trading houses have registered routes and have issued enormous sums of Immortal Origin Stones to the Immortal Palace, their ships are still subject to checks at some ferry stations for all manners of arbitrary reasons. In those situations, the ships will either have to accept the checks and be delayed for several months, or issue another sum of Immortal Origin Stones as a toll of sorts," Fox 3 said.

"That does sound like a real pain in the backside," Han Li said with an amused smile.

"Thankfully, we won't have to worry about any of that with Brother Shi here with us. Out of all of the ships, only those owned by the Hundred Creations Pavilion and the Vast Origin House are granted certain privileges, and during most trips, those ships won't be subject to these impromptu checks," Fox 3 said with a smile.

"The Vast Origin House's ferry station is a bit further away from here. Please come with me," Shi Chuankong said with a smile, then flew away into the distance.

Han Li and the others followed along, and the group began to travel southward.

After rising up into the sky, Han Li looked down to discover that there were far more ferry stations on the ground below than he had seen earlier. All of them were spread out in an orderly fashion in an area with a radius of several hundred kilometers.

There were also some markets and streets interspersed throughout these ferry stations, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

Moments later, the group arrived at a large ferry station before making their way into an administrative hall.

There was an elderly administrator inside, who immediately approached Han Li's group at the sight of them.

The administrator seemed to be familiar with Shi Chuankong, and a wide smile appeared on his face, but right as he was about to speak, Shi Chuankong beat him to the punch.

"Long time no see, Shopkeeper Zhu. I'll have to trouble you again."

"Not at all! It's always an honor whenever you come to our ferry station, Fellow Daoist Shi. These must be your friends, right? Come in and take a seat, everyone," the elderly man said.

He led Han Li's group into a booth as he spoke, then poured cups of tea for everyone before asking, "What brings you here today, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"When is our Vast Origin House's ship to the Floating Mountain Continent scheduled to set off?" Shi Chuankong asked with a smile.

The administrator considered the question for a moment, then replied, "We recently collected a batch of spirit soil, and some of the spirit plants in our fields have also matured. We'll be ready to set off once everything is loaded, and that should only take about half a month."

"It sounds like we came at just the right time then," Fox 3 said.

"Indeed, you have," Shopkeeper Zhu replied with a smile. "There's an arena in Black Glaze City that's opening in a few days. Why don't you go and check it out to kill some time?"

Shi Chuankong was very intrigued to hear this, and he immediately sat up straighter as he asked, "Is it the Black Fence Arena? What are the draws like?"

"That's right. I've heard that there are going to ten fights, and all of the combatants are high-grade demon beasts captured from the primordial land north of the Black Mountain Immortal Region, two of which even possess true spirit bloodlines, so it's certainly a stacked draw," Shopkeeper Zhu replied.

"How about it? If you're interested, we can all go and take a look together, fellow daoists," Shi Chuankong proposed as he turned to Han Li and the others.

Han Li was rather amused by Shi Chuankong's enthusiasm. Fox 3 was a thief and an avid drinker, while Shi Chuankong was a gambler, so they certainly made for a good pair. Having said that, he wasn't interested in watching the arena battles, so he turned down the offer.

"I'll pass as well," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a smile.

"How about you? Surely you're coming along," Shi Chuankong asked as he turned to Fox 3.

"Of course I'm going! Why not? You lose in every single bet that you make, so I just have to bet against you, and I'm guaranteed to win!" Fox 3 declared.

"Nonsense! When have I ever lost?" Shi Chuankong protested.

After chatting here for a while, everyone was arranged places to stay by Shopkeeper Zhu.

That night.

Han Li was meditating in his room when he suddenly received a visit from Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

Han Li invited him into the room, then poured him a cup of tea and sat down across from him in silence.

Right as the atmosphere in the room was beginning to grow a little awkward, Immortal Lord Hot Flame finally broke the silence.

"Fellow Daoist Li, I have something to say, but I'm not sure if I should say it..."

Before he had a chance to finish, Han Li raised a hand to conjure up an invisible light barrier that encompassed the entire room.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame," Han Li prompted with a smile.

"You've been waiting for me, haven't you, Fellow Daoist Li?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a wry smile.

Chapter 649: The Lost Sect

"If I were in your shoes, I would also definitely want to find an ally," Han Li said with a smile.

"That's exactly why I'm here, and it's also why I wanted you to come with us, but you turned down the offer last time before I could bring up this topic," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a resigned shake of his head.

"If I didn't have so much on my plate already, perhaps I would've agreed at the time. In any case, we're both still traveling together anyway, it's just that both of us are members of the Reincarnation Palace now," Han Li said.

A hesitant look flashed through Immortal Lord Hot Flame's eyes upon hearing this, and he was silent for a moment, then said, "Fellow Daoist Li, I consider you to be a friend from the time that we spent together in the Leisure Valley, so can I ask you to be candid with me and tell me exact what mission the Reincarnation Palace assigned to you? Does it have anything to do with the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra?"

"Truth be told, I'm not a true core member of the Reincarnation Palace, and the mission that I received only requires me to assist Fox 3 in exploring the True Mantra Sect's ruins. As for exactly what his plans are, that's completely unknown to me," Han Li replied in a truthful fashion.

"I see. I don't trust Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong. Ours is only a partnership of convenience, and I don't know what their objectives are, so I want a definitive response from you in regard to whether you'd like to form an alliance with me," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a serious expression.

"I'm carrying out a mission for the Reincarnation Palace, so there are some things that I must do, but if your life comes under threat, I can't guarantee that I'll do everything in my power to save you, but I definitely won't just stand by and watch," Han Li declared.

"That's all I need, Fellow Daoist Li. I'll be sure to repay you handsomely once all of this is over," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Han Li returned his salute, and the two of them chatted for a while longer before Immortal Lord Hot Flame departed.

......

One morning, around two weeks later.

Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame arrived at a dock, upon which they discovered that Fox 3 was the only one waiting for them there.

"Where's Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked after greeting Fox 3.

"Brother Shi has some things that he needs to do, so he'll be a little late. Where did the time go? I still haven't had anywhere near enough fun yet!" Fox 3 yawned in a lazy manner.

"It sounds like you went to the arena again yesterday," Han Li remarked with a faint smile.

"Sure did," Fox 3 replied.

Around 15 minutes passed before Shi Chuankong and Shopkeeper Zhu arrived, and the two of them apologized for their tardiness before everyone boarded the ship together.

There was a late-Golden Immortal Stage elder of the Vast Origin House and an early-True Immortal Stage administrator coming on the trip, and the former only appeared for a brief chat with Han Li's group before returning to his living quarters, while the latter arranged places to stay for everyone.

The ship was enormous, tens of thousands of feet in size, and aside from cargo warehouses, there were also over three hundred guest rooms, but they were generally reserved solely for members of the trading house.

Han Li chose a room that was situated close to the bottom level, and the conditions were a little lackluster compared with the rooms on the higher levels, but it was quieter and more inconspicuous.

The True Immortal Stage administrator accompanied Han Li through the cargo warehouse to his room, and as they passed through the warehouse, Han Li caught sight of a collection of large black crates with some special restrictions engraved upon them stacked in an orderly fashion.

A hint of intrigue emerged in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

"Administrator Hu, why does it feel to me like the spiritual power fluctuations on these black crates are similar to those of storage pouches?" Han Li asked.

"That's a very astute observation, Senior, these black crates are indeed storage tools, and they're actually a little easier to craft than storage pouches. They can contain a hundred times their volume's worth of cargo, but things can't be stored in them for as long as they can in storage pouches. However, they're more than sufficient for transporting things like spirit soils," the administrator explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

As he looked deeper into the warehouse, Han Li spotted some special cages that ranged from only around three feet in size to over a thousand feet tall. There were arcs of lightning flashing over them, and all of them had restrictive talismans adhered to them.

Inside the cages were a series of wounded or completely defeated demon beasts, and before Han Li even had a chance to ask about them, the administrator pointed at the cages and explained, "There are always people willing to pay exorbitant prices for exotic beasts. Take that Primordial Sand Lion, for example: it was specifically requested by the arena in Spirit Swamp City, and we had to go to great lengths to capture one from the primordial land."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he didn't say anything further.

The administrator could see that Han Li didn't want to speak on this matter, so he also fell silent.

Upon accompanying Han Li to the entrance of his room, he couldn't help but ask, "Are you really not going to switch to a premium room, Senior?"

"There's no need for that. I appreciate the thought, but I prefer a more peaceful room," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Alright, I won't disturb you any further then, Senior. Feel free to call upon me if you need anything," the administrator said, then promptly departed.

Following the administrator's departure, Han Li entered his room, and only then did he discover that it was very spacious, consisting of a bedroom, a meditation chamber, and a guest room.

There was a small window in each of the meditation chamber and the guest room, and he could see the sky outside through the windows.

After briefly inspecting the room, Han Li began to set up a series of array tools, and only after the setup was completed did he make his way into the meditation chamber, where he sat down with his legs crossed.

As night fell, the light of the moon spilled into the room through the window, illuminating a patch of ground that was around a foot in size.

Han Li removed the Heaven Controlling Vial from around his neck, then placed it onto the illuminated patch of ground. After that, he flipped a hand over to summon the jade slip that contained the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique before pressing it against his own glabella.

......

Over thirty years passed by in a flash.

By alternating between ships and teleportation arrays, Han Li and the others were able to cross the Black Dragon Continent without any incident and enter the Floating Mountain Continent.

On this day, Han Li was cultivating in seclusion when he received a knock on his door from Fox 3.

"Don't get too absorbed in your cultivation and forget the task at hand, Fellow Daoist Li. We're almost at Smoke Wave City, which is where we need to disembark," Fox 3 said with a smile.

"Even if I wanted to forget about all of this, I'm sure you wouldn't let me. Go on ahead, Fellow Daoist. I'll pack up my belongings, then come meet up with everyone on the deck," Han Li jibed.

Fox 3 nodded in response before departing.

Han Li closed the door of his room, then packed up all of the array treasures and his other belongings. After that, he erased all residual aura of himself in the room before setting off for the deck.

A few minutes later, Han Li and the others disembarked from the ship, landing on the official road outside Smoke Wave City before making their way into the city.

"Why didn't we disembark at Illusory Smoke City like we planned? I've already had everything arranged there in advance, why do you insist on disembarking here instead?" Shi Chuankong asked with a displeased expression.

"You mustn't be so inflexible, Brother Shi. Everyone knows that the emergence of the illusory smoke is a precursor to the emergence of the True Mantra Sect ruins, but not everyone knows where the illusory smoke arises," Fox 3 said with a disdainful expression.

"So you're saying the illusory smoke has arisen near Smoke Wave City?" Shi Chuankong asked in a skeptical manner.

"Smoke Wave City, Illusory Smoke City, and Flowing Smoke City are all spread out across the bank of the Illusory Smoke Swamp, but during the past few instances in which the illusory smoke has arisen, it's almost always been sighted first in Smoke Wave City, so that city must be the nearest one to its origins. My guess is that it could be somewhere near Serene Floating Island," Fox 3 explained.

"What is this illusory smoke that you speak of, Fellow Daoist Fox 3?" Han Li asked.

"I'll explain that. For some reason, after the True Mantra Sect was destroyed, almost the entire sect vanished aside from a few fragments. Roughly every 3,600 years after that, a type of purple smoke would arise from the Illusory Smoke Swamp, and parts of the True Mantra Sect's ruins would emerge, but in most cases, they only appear for a moment before vanishing again like mirages," Immortal Lord Hot Flame explained.

"It sounds like you've been looking extensively into the True Mantra Sect ruins as well, Fellow Daoist Hot Flames," Shi Chuankong remarked.

"I've only heard some passing rumors," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied in a nonchalant fashion.

"The True Mantra Sect ruins actually didn't exist in the past, and the Illusory Smoke Swamp also had a different name," Fox 3 revealed.

"There were no ruins?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"That's right. The illusory smoke only appeared in this area for the first time tens of thousands of years ago. That was when the ruins of the True Mantra Sect began to emerge, and it was also from that time that this place became known as the Illusory Smoke Swamp," Fox 3 replied with a nod.

"So the True Mantra Sect ruins just suddenly popped up out of the blue? How is that possible?" Han Li asked with furrowed brows.

"Up to this point, there has been no conclusive answer to that question. However, Brother Shi speculates that the battle that led to the fall of the True Mantra Sect was so earth-shattering that it cast the entire sect into a spatial rift, thereby causing it to disappear, and it's only re-emerged tens of thousands of years ago due to some unknown reasons," Fox 3 explained.

"That's just a completely baseless guess from me, so do take it with a huge grain of salt," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"You're being far too modest, Fellow Daoist Shi. I think there's a very good chance that this was exactly what happened," Han Li said.

As the group was chatting with one another, they arrived at the gate of Smoke Wave City, where there was a group of cultivators conducting checks on those wishing to enter the city. However, they were only led by an early-True Immortal cultivator, and the tests weren't very stringent, either.

Hence, Han Li's group was able to quickly make its way into the city after submitting an entrance fee.

Chapter 650: Emergence

"This is a city inhabited by both mortals and cultivators, and only cultivators will be screened, while mortals are left alone. Even the tests administered on cultivators are nothing more than a formality. After all, the city lord is only a mid-Golden Immortal cultivator, so he'd do well to stay out of trouble," Fox 3 said.

"That makes things much more convenient. It sounds like you considered the options carefully before choosing this place," Han Li said.

With that, the group passed through the northern part of the city, which was inhabited by mortals, and arrived in the southern part of the city.

The southern section took up a third of the city, and the city lord's manor was situated there.

In the city not far away from the manor was a small mountain by the name of Smoke Watch Mountain, and it was only around five thousand feet tall. The largest immortal inn in the entire city was perched on the mountain summit, and that was where Han Li's group chose to stay.

According to information from the Reincarnation Palace, the last time that the illusory smoke appeared on the Illusory Smoke Swamp was around 3,500 years ago, so it should only be about a century before the illusory smoke was set to appear again.

For cultivators of Han Li's caliber, a century was nothing more than the blink of an eye.

Han Li and the others had thought that it wouldn't be long before they entered the Illusory Smoke Swamp, but even after over 130 years had passed, there was still no sign of the illusory smoke that they were searching for.

Fox 3 was naturally the one who was feeling most agitated by the unexpectedly long wait, and Shi Chuankong and Immortal Lord Hot Flame were also feeling rather apprehensive, while Han Li remained unbothered. He was much more interested in getting his hands on a baleful qi eradication method, but unfortunately, there had been no responses to the missions that he had released in the Reincarnation Palace.

On the bright side, through his extensive seclusion, he had begun to make some very encouraging progress in the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and all of the spirit plants in the Flower Branch domain were also coming along nicely.

On this day, Han Li had just finished watering his Dao Warrior primary beans, and he emerged from the domain, then cast his gaze out of the window of the room that he was staying in to observe the Illusory Smoke Swamp in the distance.

At the moment, it was around noon, and it was also a bright and sunny day, so most of the mist above the swamp had cleared up. As a result, he was able to see Serene Floating Island in the distance even without using his spirit eye abilities.

Strictly speaking, Serene Floating Island wasn't really an island. It was nothing more than a conglomeration of waterweeds and mud with a layer of soil on top. It was less than ten kilometers in size, and there were some shrubs with shallow root systems growing on it.

Han Li's plan was to look at the island for a short while before resuming his cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique, but right at this moment, an intrigued look appeared on his face as he activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

He had spotted a gray stone pillar jutting out of the shrubs on the island in a rather jarring fashion. It was as if it had grown out of the island, and it was only around six feet tall, just barely taller than the shrubs, so it would've been almost impossible to spot had it not been for Han Li's exceptional eyesight.

Immediately thereafter, wisps of pink mist suddenly began to emerge from around the stone pillar, and it was becoming thicker and thicker while quickly spreading over the surrounding area to inundate the entire island.

Finally...

Almost at the exact same moment, a voice rang out from outside his room.

"Fellow Daoist Li, the illusory smoke has already emerged, we must set off right away."

Han Li could tell that it was Fox 3's voice, and he immediately replied, "I'll be with you in a moment, Fellow Daoist Fox 3."

Shortly thereafter, Han Li's group appeared on the summit of Smoke Watch Mountain, preparing to set off for Serene Floating Island.

"Please pardon my urgency, fellow daoists. This bout of illusory smoke has emerged quite a bit later than anticipated, and many other cultivators have already arrived in Smoke Wave City to try their luck.There's no way they'll be able to find the entrance to the ruins, but it still won't be a good thing for too many people to see us," Fox 3 explained.

"It's fine. Time is of the essence, so let's set off right away," Shi Chuankong said.

Han Li exchanged a glance with Immortal Lord Hot Flame, and both of them nodded in unison.

With that, the four of them rose up into the air, completely disregarding the rule that prohibited flying over the city wall.

Upon emerging from Smoke Wave City, Han Li suddenly heard a chorus of chaotic sounds ring out from down below, and he looked down to discover a group of several hundred people making their way toward the Illusory Smoke Swamp while playing a series of percussion instruments.

The group was led by several dozen figures who were wearing extremely large and strange masks, holding onto burning tobacco stalks as they led the way forward while dancing with peculiar and exaggerated motions.

"Those are all mortals, aren't they, Fellow Daoist Fox 3? What are they doing?" Han Li asked.

Fox 3 took a nonchalant glance down below, then explained, "These people used to be indigenous inhabitants of the Illusory Smoke Swamp, and they're no different from normal humans, but all of them have remarkably long lifespans, able to live for over two hundred years. They only moved out of the swamp just over ten thousand years ago.

“Their ancestors don't know what the illusory smoke is, but every time it appears, some of their brethren would die or go missing. Over time, they came to regard the illusory smoke as some type of divine punishment from the gods, so they'll perform this ceremonial dance whenever it arises."

"At this point, they're already learned about what the illusory smoke is from the cultivators passing through this area, but they'll still abide by their traditions whenever it appears, performing their ceremonial dance at the edge of the swamp," Shi Chuankong added.

"I see," Han Li replied as he turned his gaze away from those people.

A few minutes later, the group arrived at the edge of the Illusory Smoke Swamp before descending onto it.

There was smoke swirling all over the surface of the swamp, resembling a vast river, and upon approaching the swamp, one would discover dark green waterweeds gently swaying beneath the water. Some white bubbles would also occasionally emerge on the surface of the water, producing a faint popping sound whenever they burst.

The illusory smoke was spreading quite quickly, and at this point, it had already encompassed the entire surrounding area within a radius of several dozen kilometers of Serene Floating Island. At this point, even mortals could clearly see the pink mist spreading over the landscape.

"I've already said this many times, but I still want to remind all of you once again that this illusory smoke can be very dangerous. Once we enter it, make sure to protect your mind so that you aren't fooled by the illusions presented to you," Fox 3 warned with a serious expression.

"I've prepared some Divine Spirit Pills that can stabilize the soul and cleanse the consciousness. They should be somewhat effective against the effects of the illusory smoke, so I suggest all of us take one each," Shi Chuankong said a he flipped a hand over to produce a dark green jade box.

"Where did you get these pills from? I haven't even been able to purchase them from the Reincarnation Palace!" Fox 3 asked with a surprised expression.

"Just because the Reincarnation Palace can't acquire these pills doesn't mean that the Vast Origin House is in the same boat," Shi Chuankong replied, then opened the jade box and plucked out one of the pills before swallowing it.

"This will certainly make things a lot safer," Fox 3 said as he also took one of the pills.

Meanwhile, Immortal Lord Hot Flame turned to Han Li with a slightly hesitant look in his eyes.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li said with a smile, then plucked out a pill for himself.

He briefly inspected the pill to ensure that there was nothing amiss about it, then promptly swallowed it.

However, as soon as he closed his mouth, a burst of silver flames emerged from his throat to envelop the pill, sealing it within his stomach.

He was quite confident in his own spiritual sense, so he wasn't planning to actually take the Divine Spirit Pill unless it was absolutely necessary to do so.

With the example set by Han Li, Immortal Lord Hot Flame also followed suit, taking a pill as well.

"Fellow daoists, all of us have to make sure to maintain our spiritual connections with one another so we don't get split up in the illusory smoke," Fox 3 said, then swept a sleeve through the air to produce an intricate silver flying boat that landed on the surface of the swamp.

Everyone stepped onto the boat, and Fox 3 made a hand seal, upon which a burst of silver light emerged from all of the runes on the boat, and it was lifted up by about half a foot before shooting over the water.

Only then did Han Li notice that the water in the swamp was a lot heavier than normal water. The momentum of the flying boat should've been enough to send waves churning in all directions, but there were only slight ripples surging over the swamp's surface.

He leaned down and extended two of his fingers, the ones with the Flower Branch refined into them, into the water, and he immediately realized why this was the case.

As it turned out, the water here was interspersed with some type of black sandy substance that possessed certain corrosive properties, but of course, it was unable to harm his Golden Immortal body.

Even though the boat still hadn't entered the illusory smoke yet, the sun was already beginning to set, making the smoke on the swamp appear darker and denser than before.

As they passed by a giant mass of green duckweed, the surface of the water suddenly exploded, and a massive wave erupted upward as a huge black shadow sprang out of the swamp before crashing down upon Han Li's group.

Han Li turned to discover that it was a giant fish that was covered in black scales. The mass of duckweed was actually a plume of disheveled hair on its head, and its cavernous mouth was filled with sharp teeth.

Han Li and the others had already detected the approaching fish even before it attacked, and none of them had paid it any heed, with Fox 3 even jokingly mocking its hideous appearance.

Shi Chuankong casually swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of silver light that sliced the fish into two with ease.

However, no blood seeped out of the fish's body as its wounds were sealed by a burst of spatial power, and only after it had fallen back into the swamp did its blood begin to spread through the water.

Chapter 651: Return to a Place of Old

"Don't get complacent, everyone. There's no telling what other manners of strange creatures we could encounter in this place."

As soon as Shi Chuankong's voice trailed off, a giant twin-headed crocodile rushed out of the swamp with mud all over its body, opening one of its mouths in an attempt to swallow the entire flying boat whole.

"You spoke it into existence, Brother Shi," Fox 3 said with an amused smile.

Shi Chuankong paid no heed to him as he made a hand seal, conjuring up a seemingly extremely thin silver light barrier around the flying boat.

The twin-headed crocodile crashed into the silver light barrier, both of its heads were instantly pulverized upon impact, as if a gargantuan mountain had fallen upon them.

"This thing's not very smart, but it certainly has strength to spare," Immortal Lord Hot Flame remarked.

"There's something else up ahead," Han Li suddenly said, an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword appeared in his grasp, following which he sprang up into the air before slashing his sword forward.

A streak of azure swordlight was released, vanishing into the swamp up ahead in a flash before exploding violently.

An agonized roar rang out as a huge volume of blood gushed into the water, and immediately thereafter, a creature that was identical in appearance to the strange fish from earlier, except enlarged by tenfold, rose up to the surface with its body already sliced into two.

The silver flying boat was able to fly straight down the middle between two halves of its body, and Fox 3 chuckled, "With the two of you standing on guard duty, I don't have to worry about anything aside from piloting the boat!"

As the flying boat rushed into the illusory smoke, the latter was also surging toward the former, and it didn't take long before the two made contact hundreds of kilometers away from Serene Floating Island.

As soon as the flying boat entered the pink smoke, it immediately slowed , and everyone released their spiritual sense to scour the surrounding area.

"As expected, spiritual sense is severely restricted within the illusory mist, so we won't even be able to discern our location," Fox 3 said.

"In that case, let's be a bit more careful, and we'll each focus on one direction," Shi Chuankong suggested with a cautious expression.

As for Han Li, his brows were slightly furrowed, and there was a hint of surprise in his heart. Even with his immense spiritual sense, his sensory range within the illusory mist was only around a dozen kilometers.

"It's fine, I'll be able to sense it if the sect ruins emerge," Immortal Lord Hot Flame assured.

He flipped a hand over as he spoke to produce a longan-sized pink bead, which appeared to be no different from a normal clam pearl, except it was riddled with tiny golden runes that were flashing incessantly.

"What's that?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"This is a True Mantra Bead that was given to me by my master. Originally, it was only meant as something to facilitate convenient travel for me within the sect, allowing me to use the teleportation arrays in the sect as I please, but in the wake of the sect's destruction, this is perhaps the only bead of its kind left in the outside world," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a reminiscent expression.

"So you're saying this True Mantra Bead can help us find the ruins?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"This bead can establish a connection with all of the teleportation arrays in the sect, of which there are over three hundred. However, due to the presence of this illusory mist, I'm guessing that its sensory range will be severely limited to no more than a few dozen kilometers," Immortal Lord Hot Flame explained.

"That's better than nothing. If we can find an intact teleportation array, perhaps we'll be able to teleport straight into the True Mantra Sect," Fox 3 said.

Han Li cast his gaze into the distance as he listened to the ongoing conversation, and he spotted a corner of a building's roof jutting out of the mist up ahead.

Immediately thereafter, a three-story archway that was around a thousand feet tall came into view. It was extremely dilapidated, and it looked as if it wasn't all that far away from toppling over entirely.

"This is the Black Beam Archway, one of the ten archways on the merchant street in the sect!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame exclaimed upon catching sight of the archway.

"Looks like we're in luck," Fox 3 said with an elated expression, and the flying boat began traveling in that direction at his behest.

"Hold on, Fellow Daoist Fox 3, you're running into an illusion!" Han Li suddenly declared.

The flying boat drew to a sharp halt over a thousand feet away from the archway, and everyone turned to discover a peculiar purple light glowing in Han Li's eyes.

"Those are Infernal Devilish Eyes! Fellow Daoist Li, how did you master this spirit eye ability of our Devil Race?" Shi Chuankong asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I came across the secret technique by chance, and I just so happened to have dabbled in a devilish cultivation art in the past, so things worked out quite well for me," Han Li explained in an ambiguous fashion.

A hint of befuddlement flashed through Shi Chuankong's eyes upon hearing this, but he didn't pry any further. As for Immortal Lord Hot Flame, he couldn't help but turn to Han Li with an intrigued look on his face. They were both late-Golden Immortal cultivators, but Han Li struck him as someone completely unfathomable.

"Looks like Fellow Daoist Li was the perfect final member to round out our group!" Fox 3 praised, then swept a sleeve through the air, sending a streak of light hurtling toward the archway.

In the instant that the streak of light struck the archway, a vast expanse of silver radiance erupted forth, forming a giant silver vortex with a radius of over a thousand feet. The vortex was releasing a burst of terrifying spatial power that twisted the entire archway into a ball before devouring it, and in the end, all that remained was a fist-sized black hole that also slowly disappeared.

Fox 3's smile instantly stiffened slightly upon seeing this.

"Thank heavens Fellow Daoist Li was able to see through the illusion. Otherwise, we would've most likely already been sucked into a spatial rift by now," Shi Chuankong said with a hint of lingering fear in his voice.

Right as his voice trailed off, an intoxicating aroma began to spread through the area, and everyone looked around to discover that a large area of palatial structures had appeared within the mist.

Their silver flying boat was no longer traveling over the swamp. Instead, it was traversing through a lush sea of flowers, sending countless flower petals drifting down in all directions.

Around the sea of flowers was a series of intricate pavilions and pagodas that connected to the palatial structures in the distance, and there was a group of gorgeous celestial maidens in palace dresses standing on a covered bridge.

Some were holding delectable spirit fruits, some were holding flagons of fine wine, and some were carrying palace lanterns as they made their way gracefully toward the nearby pavilions.

There were many immortals seated in these pavilions, sharing wine, reciting poetry, or playing go, and it seemed that Han Li's group had unwittingly stumbled its way into a banquet.

The flying boat immediately drew to a halt at Fox 3's behest, and he turned to Shi Chuankong as he said, "Your Divine Spirit Pills don't seem to be working, Brother Shi. Why are these illusions only becoming more and more potent?"

"The Divine Spirit Pills are working as intended, it's just that this illusion is too powerful. If we hadn't taken those pills, we would've most likely already become completely immersed in the illusion and be unable to discern it from real life," Han Li explained in Shi Chuankong's stead.

He hadn't taken his Divine Spirit Pill, so he was aware of just how powerful this illusion was. If he hadn't already channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to protect his own consciousness, even he would've most likely already fallen prey to it.

"Fellow Daoist Li, can you dispel this illusion with your spirit eye ability?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

"My spirit eyes can only help us avoid danger, but it can't dispel illusions. However, I think Fellow Daoist Shi can perhaps dispel part of the illusion by using his spatial law powers to force back some of the nearby illusory mist," Han Li replied.

"Theoretically, that's possible, but it would be far too taxing, and I won't be able to dispel any illusions that encompass large areas, so I'm afraid that's not a very feasible solution," Shi Chuankong said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"How about this? We'll have Fellow Daoist Li use his spirit eyes to help us avoid danger, while Fellow Daoist Hot Flame uses his True Mantra Bead to detect for teleportation arrays. Once we discover something, we'll get Brother Shi to dispel the illusion in that area. As for myself, I'll continue to pilot the boat," Fox 3 proposed.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance upon hearing this, and both of them nodded in approval of this proposal.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame naturally had no reason to object, and with that, the flying boat slowly continued onward.

"Turn left once we emerge from this field of flowers," Han Li instructed as he scoured his surroundings with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

"You want me to crash straight into that bridge?" Fox 3 asked in a hesitant manner.

"Trust me," Han Li insisted, and Fox duly obliged, guiding the boat in that direction.

After emerging from the field of flowers, the boat turned left and crashed straight into the covered bridge, only for it to completely disintegrate upon contact, and Han Li's group passed straight through the bodies of the celestial maidens on the bridge.

"From here, go straight for about seven hundred feet, then turn right..."

Under Han Li's guidance, the flying boat was able to traverse through one illusion after another, and around an hour later, the boat was passing through an illusory pond when Immortal Lord Hot Flame suddenly exclaimed, "I've found it!"

Chapter 652: Repair

Han Li and the others immediately turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame upon hearing this, and at this moment, the True Mantra Bead in his hand was glowing brightly, as were all of the golden runes on its surface.

"Is there a teleportation array here?" Fox 3 asked with an elated expression as he brought the flying boat to a halt.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame nodded in response.

"Alright, looks like it's up to you now, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li said as he turned to Shi Chuankong.

Shi Chuankong offered no response as he closed his eyes and joined his palms in front of himself, then chanted a silent incantation, and a burst of radiant silver light and spatial fluctuations immediately emerged from between the palms of his hands.

All of a sudden, his eyes sprang open as he brought his hands apart, then thrust both palms upward, and the burst of silver light between the palms of his hands instantly began to expand rapidly, forming a silver light barrier.

As the light barrier continued to expand, the surrounding pond began to disintegrate, and the nearby illusory mist was also pushed further and further away.

The silver light barrier expanded to encompass an area with a radius of over ten thousand feet before drawing to a halt, and the swamp was revealed in that area.

Han Li's eyes were glowing with radiant purple light as he swept his gaze across his surroundings, and he immediately spotted a pile of loose white rocks up ahead, looking completely out of place.

"Over there!"

Under Han Li's guidance, Fox 3 immediately piloted the spirit boat in that direction until it arrived at the pile of rocks.

The pile of rocks was only several dozen feet wide, and it looked like the remnants of a destroyed stone pillar.

"This is a stone pillar that would've once belonged to a teleportation array, but at this point, the entire array is already completely destroyed," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed in a disappointed manner.

"It's alright, the ruins aren't supposed to be easy to track down," Fox 3 said, not disheartened in the slightest.

With that, the search continued.

......

Over a month passed by in a flash.

During this time, Han Li's group was able to find some sets of ruins, but most of them were just toppled buildings. As for the few teleportation arrays that they encountered, all of them had been destroyed beyond repair.

"We're already quite far away from Serene Floating Island at this point. Should we consider going in another direction, Fellow Daoist Li?" Fox 3 proposed.

"We can try heading toward Illusory Smoke City," Han Li replied after a brief moment of contemplation.

Right at this moment, Immortal Lord Hot Flame suddenly interjected, "Hold on a second, there's another teleportation array nearby."

"Alright, let's go check it out first," Fox 3 said in an expressionless manner.

At this point, everyone had already been drained of the initial joy that they had experienced whenever a teleportation array was discovered.

However, as Shi Chuankong cleared away the surrounding illusory mist, everyone was stunned by the sight that was revealed.

On a white sand dune around ten thousand feet away stood seven or eight giant white stone pillars that were riddled with complex array patterns, but they weren't giving off any spiritual power fluctuations.

As the spirit boat flew over to the sand dune, the entire teleportation array came into view.

The array was surrounded by eleven stone pillars, but only seven of them were still fully intact, while another one was still half-standing, and the rest had completely collapsed.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame inspected the array momentarily, following which his brows furrowed slightly as he said, "This is one of the eight teleportation arrays outside the sect, but it's also damaged beyond repair."

Han Li paid no heed to him as he walked a lap around the entire teleportation array, then cast his gaze toward the center of the array with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Moments later, he turned to Shi Chuankong as he asked, "Fellow Daoist Shi, do you have anything that contains spatial law powers in your possession?"

"Do you intend to use such items to substitute these stone pillars and repair the array? Forgive me for being blunt, but that's not going to work," Shi Chuankong replied after a brief hesitation.

"We won't know for sure unless we give it a try," Han Li countered with a smile.

"You have that pair of stone lions, don't you, Brother Shi? Don't be so stingy! I'll compensate you if they somehow get damaged," Fox 3 said as he slung an arm across his shoulder.

Shi Chuankong paid no heed to Fox 3 as he continued to look at Han Li with a skeptical expression.

"Can you really repair this array?"

"I'd say there's a 30% chance of success. How about it? Do you want to take a gamble?" Han Li asked.

"My luck hasn't been great of late, so I'm probably going to lose again," Shi Chuankong sighed in a resigned manner as he flipped a hand over to produce a pair of gray stone lions, each of which was around three feet tall.

Han Li smiled as he made a beckoning motion, and the two stone lions were lifted up by a burst of azure light before descending onto the teleportation array.

After that, he flipped a hand over to produce a stack of array tools and commenced the repair process.

Several hours later.

"All done," Han Li declared as he slotted the final array plate into place.

"It's... fixed now?" Fox 3 asked with a skeptical expression.

"The spatial power within the stone lions should be sufficient to support the entire array's operation, but these array flags and array plates aren't so sturdy, so they'll only be able to last a very short time before they're destroyed," Han Li explained.

"Will that be enough time to complete the teleportation?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

"It should be. This array was designed to be able to teleport several hundred people at once, so it should be able to teleport us in an instant. There's only one more thing that I need now," Han Li said as he turned to Fox 3.

"What is it?" Fox 3 asked.

"Immortal Origin Stones, and it looks like the array will require at least mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones," Han Li said with a smile as he pointed at the indentations on the ground.

"Surely you could've filled those slots yourself, Fellow Daoist Li," Fox 3 said in a resigned manner.

"I'm but an itinerant cultivator, so I don't have many Immortal Origin Stones on me, particularly when it comes to mid-grade ones," Han Li replied with a smile.

Fox 3 exchanged a glance with Shi Chuankong upon hearing this, and they couldn't help but smile in amusement.

Prior to this, they didn't believe that Han Li was truly just an itinerant cultivator, particularly given all of the abilities that he had displayed up to this point, but in the wake of this stingy display, they were starting to believe him.

The group filed into the center of the array, following which Fox 3 fitted several mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones into the indentations on the ground.

After that, Han Li made a hand seal, and the entire array began to glow brightly.

Shortly thereafter, the entire group disappeared, and the light radiating from the array began to fade. Sure enough, the two stone lions remained completely unscathed, and most of the array tools that Han Li had set up were also preserved.

......

Moments later, Han Li and the others arrived in front of a giant mountain.

There was a majestic entrance standing in front of the mountain, beyond which was a giant hovering white stone plaza that was enshrouded in a cloud of mist. There seemed to be a spatial barrier within the mist that kept out all spiritual sense, and in front of the entrance stood several enormous stone pillars that extended all the way up into the clouds.

On top of that, the entrance was enshrouded under a white light barrier, which was clearly some type of powerful restriction.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame looked up at the majestic entrance, and tears began to well up in his eyes, while a reminiscent look appeared on his face.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom snapped him out of his train of thought, and he turned to discover Shi Chuankong attacking the white light barrier.

However, no matter what he tried, the light barrier remained firm, displaying no sign of breaking.

"Let me have a go!" Fox 3 said as his entire body abruptly swelled to over a hundred times its original size, and he raised a hand, curling his fingers into claws before swiping them viciously through the air.

Five massive claw projections appeared before tearing into the white light barrier.

A burst of radiant five-colored lightning instantly erupted out of the light barrier, causing the surrounding space to rumble incessantly.

However, after the lightning subsided, the white light barrier remained completely unscathed.

"Save your energy. This restriction is imbued with both spatial law powers and time law powers, so it's impossible to break it through conventional means," Shi Chuankong said.

Even though Han Li hadn't made an attempt at attacking the light barrier, he had arrived at the same conclusion through his observation.

Fox 3 immediately reverted back to his original form upon hearing this, and he asked, "Is it that troublesome to deal with? Can you see any way to break the restriction?"

"I can set up an array to weaken the spatial power within the restriction, and that might make it possible for us to break the restriction if we all attack it together," Shi Chuankong said.

"Alright, time is of the essence, so let's begin," Fox 3 said in an eager manner.

......

Meanwhile, on the edge of the Illusory Smoke Swamp stood a man who was built like a steel pagoda. His hands were clasped behind his back as he stood facing the swamp, and his fiery red hair was swaying gently in the wind.

His facial features were extremely chiseled and well-defined, and his appearance was quite similar to that of a human, except he had a rhinoceros horn for a nose, and his ears were also very long and tapered, with a large golden ring hanging from each of them.

At this moment, the man was peering into the illusory smoke in the swamp with an angry look on his face.

Right at this moment, a streak of green light shot forth from afar, and when it was still several hundred kilometers away, it was enveloped within a fiery red spirit domain, following which it was instantly teleported to the brawny man's side.

A resounding boom rang out as a green jade flying carriage abruptly appeared before slamming heavily down onto the ground.

On the carriage was a red-haired man, another man who was thin as a bamboo pole, and a third handsome red-robed man. All three of them jumped off the flying carriage at once, then extended a collective salute toward the brawny man in a slightly awkward fashion as they greeted in unison, "We pay our respects to Senior Chi Rong."

These three men were Gongshu Tian, his senior martial brother, Wang Xiaosen, and his most prized disciple, Feng Qingyuan.

"You're late, and by two whole weeks, at that," the brawny man accused in a cold voice.

Chapter 653: Multiple Factions

"My sincerest apologies, Senior Chi Rong. Silver Fox made an appearance in the Black Mountain Immortal Region, and we were delayed in our attempt to capture him," Gongshu Tian informed.

"Did you catch him?" the man by the name of Chi Rong asked.

"Unfortunately, Silver Fox was able to escape with the help of a man from the Devil Race..."

"Useless trash!" Chi Rong denounced before Gongshu Tian had a chance to finish.

The expressions of Gongshu Tian's trio changed slightly upon hearing this, and a hint of fury flashed through their eyes, but then quickly faded.

"Forget it. We're already way behind schedule, and the True Mantra Sect ruins will only be around for a short time, so we have to make haste. I'll deal with this matter at some later date, but for now, we need to set off right away," Chi Rong said in a cold voice.

Gongshu Tian's trio was quite relieved to hear this, and the three of them gave a collective affirmative response.

Chi Rong swept a sleeve through the air to release a wave of fire, which swept through the air in front of him before transforming into an enormous spirit boat in the visage of a fiery dragon.

The spirit boat sped forward as a streak of red light with the four men onboard, plunging straight into the illusory smoke.

Mere minutes following their departure, several streaks of light flew onto the scene from Illusory Smoke City, then descended onto the edge of the swamp.

The streaks of light then faded to reveal four figures, three male and one female.

They were led by a middle-aged man who was close to one and a half times the height of an average grown man, and his skin was bronze in color. His facial features were very angular, and he was wearing a suit of golden armor, outside of which was a purple and golden cloak. The man was none other than Su Liu of Jade Gathering City.

"It seems these insolent fools have no respect for me, even when they're on my territory," Su Liu harrumphed in disdain.

Standing behind him was a man in a scholarly white robe, and he said in a casual manner, "They're also part of the Heavenly Court like we are, but we've never interfered with each other's work, and I'll agree that they've overstepped their boundaries by coming here without even notifying us first. Having said that, why are you so angry about this? With our four allied immortal regions joining forces, there's no way that treasure could fall into anyone else's hands."

"Fellow Daoist Zhao Zhen is right. The Illusory Smoke Swamp is our territory, and they're just a bunch of outsiders stumbling into it completely blind. There's no way they'll actually be able to accomplish anything in there," a seductive woman in a purple palace dress chimed in.

She was the current city lord of Illusory Smoke City and also the dao partner of the Black Soil Immortal Palace's palace master. She was only at the late-Golden Immortal Stage, but she had quite a lofty status in the four allied immortal regions.

Zhao Zhen was the name of the scholarly-robed man, and he was the immortal envoy stationed in Abyssal Lake City of the Concealed Lake Immortal Region.

The final person to round out their group was a short and slightly hunched over elderly man, and he was peering into the swamp with his hands clasped behind his back, taking no part in the ongoing conversation.

"Senior Lu, we've all tried to enter the True Mantra Sect ruins on our own at some point, but none of us have found success. Now that we've chosen to join forces, I think you have an obligation to be open and candid with us. Are you really confident in your ability to find a spatial node?" Zhao Zhen asked as he turned to the short elderly man.

He was none other than Wu Liang, the current palace master of the Origin Contention Immortal Palace.

"Rest assured, I wouldn't have said anything if I didn't have absolute confidence. All of you are aware of how to open the spatial node, just make sure you don't hold back too much," the elderly man replied in a coarse voice.

"I'm certainly feeling much more reassured now," the seductive woman said with a faint smile.

"Alright, that's enough chit-chat, let's set off as well," Su Liu declared, and with that, he sped into the Illusory Smoke Swamp as an arc of five-colored lightning, while the other three quickly followed along.

......

Meanwhile.

Hovering in mid-air above a section of the swamp countless kilometers away was a giant stone staircase with several hundred steps.

At this moment, there were several men and women dressed in blue cloaks making their way up the staircase.

They were led by a tall and gorgeous woman with light blue skin and curly green hair, wearing a suit of light scale armor. She walked in an elegant and seductive fashion, moving like a beautiful snake that one couldn't look away from.

Trailing along behind her was an imposing man who was built like a stone wall with a giant sword on his back, and a thin and wizened elderly man who looked as if he were suffering from tuberculosis.

The imposing man was looking straight ahead with a solemn and slightly anxious look on his face, while the elderly man was looking much more relaxed, with his gaze blatantly roaming over the blue-skinned woman's body in a lustful fashion.

All of a sudden, the blue-skinned woman drew to a halt before turning around.

Her gorgeous features had completely frozen over, and she turned to the elderly man with a pair of piercing golden eyes that were brimming with killing intent.

"Take your filthy eyes off me, or I'll kill you right here and now!" the blue-skinned woman spat through gritted teeth.

The elderly man was instantly rooted to the spot, feeling as if a bucket of ice water had just been dumped over his head. The fear that he was feeling wasn't in response to the threat being directed at him. Instead, it stemmed from the peculiar light within the woman's golden pupils.

"Y-yes, Celestial Maiden Bi She, I'll k-keep my eyes to myself," the elderly man stuttered in response.

"Celestial Maiden Bi She, hasn't it always been customary for members of our Robe Change Order to carry out missions in pairs? Why are we traveling as a group of three this time?" the imposing man asked.

The blue-skinned woman's expression immediately warmed up upon hearing this, and a seductive smile appeared on her face as she replied, "If it isn't because that old pervert can set up spatial arrays, you'd have me all to yourself for this mission again."

The imposing man's expression became even more anxious upon hearing this, and he hurriedly said, "Please don't make such jokes, Celestial Maiden Bi She."

The blue-skinned woman seemed to be quite amused by this, and her smile became even more seductive, while the elderly man could only look on with a dejected expression.

......

At the entrance of the True Mantra Sect ruins, Han Li's group was busy at work, setting up a collection of array tools and a small pile of silver crystals.

At this moment, Shi Chuankong was engraving a silver array into the ground, and as he did so, he was instructing Han Li and the others to install all of the array tools and silver crystals into the array.

With all four of them working at once, progress was rapid, and it didn't take long before a complex and resplendent silver array was completed.

"Step back a little," Shi Chuankong said to Han Li's trio as he made his way into the silver array.

The three of them did as they were told, and Shi Chuankong made a hand seal before pointing a finger at the silver array, upon which all of the spirit patterns on its surface instantly lit up.

The entire array began to radiate dazzling silver light, and boundless world's origin qi surged toward it in a frenzy from all directions, making the array glow brighter and brighter.

All of the silver light then converged to form a silver cloud that was several hundred feet in size, and there were countless silver runes surging within it, giving off formidable spatial fluctuations.

Shi Chuankong rose up into the air, standing above the silver cloud, and his entire body was enshrouded within a layer of radiant silver light, giving him a deity-like appearance.

He began to chant an incantation, and a silver badge appeared in his grasp. The badge was shimmering with silver light, and it was also giving off bursts of spatial fluctuations.

Shi Chuankong tossed the badge forward, and it landed beneath the silver cloud.

At the same time, he began to chant an incantation, and the silver cloud immediately surged into the badge in a frenzy.

The badge instantly swelled rapidly to several dozen feet in size, and it began to radiate dazzling silver light, while the spatial fluctuations that it was releasing became significantly more powerful.

Han Li and the others were also doing their part, channeling their immortal spiritual power in preparation to attack.

Shi Chuankong continued to chant his incantation as he gestured toward the silver badge with his hand, and five streaks of silver light shot out of his fingertips before vanishing into the badge.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as a silver crescent moon that was several dozen feet in size flew out of the badge, then struck the white light barrier while rotating rapidly.

However, there was no earth-shattering boom as anticipated, and the silver crescent moon fused straight into the white light barrier upon contact.

A dull explosion rang out from within the white light barrier, and it shuddered violently as a layer of silver light appeared over its surface, giving off formidable spatial fluctuations.

The layer of silver light was flickering erratically, but it then quickly stabilized itself.

The layer of silver light was the spatial restriction within the white light barrier, and its emergence indicated that Shi Chuankong's attack had been effective.

An elated look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon seeing this, and he began to make a rapid string of hand seals, upon which more silver crescent moons shot out of the badge in a frenzy, with all of them striking the layer of silver light.

A burst of dull rumbling rang out as the layer of silver light flickered erratically while becoming dimmer and dimmer.

However, using the silver badge seemed to be extremely taxing on Shi Chuankong, and his complexion was quickly becoming paler and paler. Thankfully, the silver cloud that was surging out of the silver array was constantly injecting itself into the badge to support it.

After a round of ferocious attacks, the layer of silver light was finally shattered, and it distintegrated into specks of spiritual light.

As a result, the white light barrier was also left looking much more vulnerable than before.

"Hurry! I've only temporarily broken the spatial restriction, but it'll be back very soon!" Shi Chuankong yelled in an urgent voice.

Chapter 654: Seizing the Initiative

Han Li's trio had been preparing for this very moment, and they immediately sprang into action.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was the first to act, joining his palms before splitting them apart again to produce an antiquated golden mirror, the same time-attribute immortal treasure that he had used in that previous battle.

He then began to chant an incantation while rubbing his hands together, and two bursts of golden light shot forth before vanishing into the golden mirror.

The golden mirror instantly swelled to the size of a house, and a vast expanse of golden light surged out of its surface, then converged to form a giant golden rune that was over a hundred feet in size.

There was radiant golden light and tremendous time law power fluctuations surging out of the giant rune, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame thrust his palms forward, upon which the golden rune shot forward to strike the white light barrier with tremendous force.

The golden rune vanished into the white light barrier upon contact, and the latter shuddered violently, following which a flashing layer of golden light appeared over its surface.

The layer of golden light was quickly becoming dimmer and dimmer, but it didn't shatter like the layer of silver light from before.

At the same time, Fox 3 began to chant an incantation, and four figures that were identical to himself shot out of his body amid a flash of silver light.

The five Fox 3s each made a grabbing motion in unison, and bursts of menacing crimson light erupted out of their hands.

Immediately thereafter, all five of them opened their mouths, releasing five bursts of silver light that vanished into the crimson light in their hands in a flash.

The bursts of crimson light rapidly shrank down to form giant crimson axes that were each around a hundred feet in size, and arcs of crimson lightning were flashing over the axes.

The five giant crimson axes came crashing down viciously upon the white light barrier, and at the same time, nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords appeared in front of Han Li side by side, with all of them radiating dazzling azure light.

He opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light that injected itself into the nine flying swords, and they quickly fused as one to form an enormous azure sword that was over a thousand feet in size, with thick arcs of golden lightning flashing over them.

Tremendous sword qi erupted out of the giant azure sword, causing the nearby space to ripple and warp.

Having been nurtured in the Profound Heavenly Gourd for so many years, Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had once again become significantly more powerful than before.

The giant azure sword came swooping down as a blurry shadow, appearing in front of the white light barrier in the blink of an eye before swinging down with immense power.

At this point, Shi Chuankong's complexion was looking quite pale, but he also took a deep breath before contributing to the collective effort by summoning a black wheel immortal treasure, which crashed down upon the white light barrier with an earth-shattering boom.

In the face of such a formidable assault, the layer of golden light had already been torn apart, and the white light barrier was also being rapidly whittled down until there was only a thin layer of it left.

Countless translucent white threads appeared within what remained of the light barrier, and they intertwined with one another to form a giant net.

Despite how thin it had become, the white light barrier was displaying incredible resilience, withstanding everyone's attacks in a herculean effort.

Not only that, but golden and silver light had emerged from the edge of the white light barrier, and they were rapidly converging toward the center.

"It's time to go all out, everyone! If we let those restrictions recover, all of our efforts up to this point will be for nought!" Shi Chuankong yelled, then flipped a hand over to produce a faintly glowing purple pill.

After a brief hesitation, he swallowed the pill, and radiant purple light erupted out of his body, while his complexion also quickly returned to normal.

He made a beckoning motion to summon the black wheel immortal treasure back to himself, then began to chant an incantation, and a devilish purple projection with six arms and three heads appeared behind him.

Immediately thereafter, he made a rapid string of hand seals before pointing a finger up at the sky, and a burst of purple light erupted into the heavens.

In the next instant, a thunderous boom rang out, and a massive dark purple hole appeared in the sky with boundless devilish qi cascading down from it.

The devilish qi raining down from the heavens converged to form a series of giant dark purple runes, which surged into the weapon held in one of the purple projection's hands.

The weapon in question was a massive bow, and with the injection of dark purple runes, it was rapidly becoming clearer and clearer, almost taking on a substantial form.

A layer of purple scales with dark purple runes inscribed upon them appeared over the bow, and on each end of the bow was a demonic dragon head with the two ends of the thick bowstring held between their teeth.

With one of its other arms, the purple projection drew back the bowstring, and a giant arrow projection appeared before being released like a shooting star and striking the white light barrier.

Meanwhile, Fox 3 was chanting a rapid incantation, and all five Fox 3s instantly fused back into one, following which his body began to expand at an alarming rate, swelling to several hundred feet tall in the blink of an eye.

An enormous silver fox projection then appeared behind him amid a flash of silver light, and the five giant crimson axes also fused as one to form a gargantuan crimson ax that was over a thousand feet in size.

Bursts of crimson flames then emerged over the ax, and they burned with such ferocity that even the nearby space seemed to be melting away.

All of a sudden, Fox 3 let loose a thunderous roar as he swung his enormous ax down upon the white light barrier.

Meanwhile, Immortal Lord Hot Flame had stowed away his antiquated golden mirror, and he was chanting an ancient incantation with a solemn look on his face.

A vast expanse of crimson flames erupted out of his body, forming a giant fiery figure with a crown of flames on its head and a staff of fire in its grasp. Its facial features were blurry and indistinct, but it was giving off the boundless regal authority of a fiery deity.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame made a rapid string of hand seals, then pointed a finger at the white light barrier, and the fiery figure behind him raised its staff of flames before also pointing it forward.

A piercing shriek rang out as a thin line of flames shot out of the tip of the staff, then vanished into thin air in a flash.

In the next instant, the thin line of fire abruptly appeared in front of the white light barrier before plunging viciously into it.

At the same time, Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as a ball of green light shot out of his body before transforming into the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

All of the countless tiny runes on its surface were flashing with green light, and the nearby world's origin qi was instantly stirred up into a frenzy.

The Profound Heavenly Gourd swelled rapidly in size at Han Li's behest, and the runes on its surface brightened considerably, while a burst of blinding green light erupted out of the mouth of the gourd. At the same time, dull rumbling could be heard ringing out within the gourd, and it was as if there were a volcano on the brink of erupting inside.

"Go!" Han Li yelled, and the gourd instantly shuddered violently, as did the space around it.

A blurry golden and azure shadow then shot out of the mouth of the gourd before striking the white light barrier.

The ferocious assault unleashed by Han Li and his allies resulted in an enormous eruption of purple, crimson, silver, and azure light, and a devastating aura of destruction surged forth in all directions.

Amid the eruption of four-colored radiance, the purple and azure lights were glowing particularly bright, and there were countless purple and azure runes churning violently within them, stirring up the nearby world's origin qi into a frenzy.

The white light barrier rippled violently as countless cracks appeared over its surface, and finally, it was torn apart with a resounding boom.

The entire light barrier was shattered before disintegrating into a huge white cloud, and two flags, one golden and one silver, emerged from within the cloud.

Both flags had countless star designs embroidered upon them, and the golden flag was giving off formidable time law power fluctuations, while the silver one was giving off tremendous spatial law power fluctuations.

Han Li's eyes instantly lit up as he pointed a finger at his Profound Heavenly Gourd, and a burst of green light immediately shot out of the mouth of the gourd, covering a distance of several hundred feet in the blink of an eye to capture the golden flag.

At the same time, a giant purple palm projection emerged before grabbing onto the silver flag.

The hand belonged to the purple projection behind Shi Chuankong, and Han Li was rather dismayed at the sight of the other flag being captured.

The burst of green light sucked the golden flag into the Profound Heavenly Gourd at his behest, while the giant purple palm projection carried the silver flag back to Shi Chuankong.

By the time Fox 3 and Immortal Lord Hot Flame realized what had happened, the two flags had already been claimed by Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

The two of them exchanged a glance with each other, and both of them could see their own disappointment mirrored in one another's eyes.

It was clear that those two flags formed the basis of the restriction that they had just broken, and they were both immortal treasures of a very high caliber, with each imbued with the power of one of the paramount laws.

However, Fox 3 and Immortal Lord Hot Flame didn't feel any resentment toward Han Li and Shi Chuankong. Exploring a set of ruins was always a test of one's abilities and luck, and they only had themselves to blame for their slow reactions.

"Congratulations. We haven't even entered the ruins yet, and you two have already claimed a pair of powerful treasures," Fox 3 said with a smile as he reverted back to his original form.

"Brother Li and I were able to seize the initiative this time, but I'm sure there are many more treasures in the ruins for the two of you to claim," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile of his own as the purple devilish projection vanished into his body.

The dark purple hole in the sky also faded away, and right before it disappeared completely, Han Li took a glance into it with purple light flashing in his eyes.

The hole was filled with devilish qi, and it was so incredibly deep that he wasn't able to see all the way through it, even with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

It seemed to be a spatial passageway, but he had no idea where it led to.

Casting aside that train of thought, Han Li made a beckoning motion, and the Profound Heavenly Gourd immediately descended out of the sky before vanishing up his sleeve.

The giant azure sword also flew back to him before splitting back up into nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that returned to his sleeve as well.

Chapter 655: Turbulence

"The two of you contributed the most to breaking the restriction, so you deserve those two treasures," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a smile, and the crimson figure behind him vanished into his body as he spoke.

"Now that I think about it, that gourd that you summoned earlier was an Essential Immortal Treasures, right? It was certainly extraordinarily powerful," Fox 3 suddenly said as he turned to Han Li, and Shi Chuankong also turned to look at him with an intrigued expression.

As for Immortal Lord Hot Flame, he had already seen Han Li use the gourd in battle in the past, so he wasn't all that surprised.

"That's right. That gourd is an Essential Immortal Treasure that I managed to obtain by chance many years ago," Han Li replied in an ambiguous fashion.

There were a couple of reasons for why he had decided to summon the Profound Heavenly Gourd here. Firstly, Immortal Lord Hot Flame was already aware of its existence, so there was no need to hide it. Secondly, he wanted to display some power so that Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong didn't regard him as some Golden Immortal Stage pushover who posed no threat to them.

Of course, he had altered the power and aura of the gourd somewhat before summoning it.

"All Essential Immortal Treasures possess tremendous power, and they're only acquired by those with immense fortune. It looks like you're a very lucky man, Fellow Daoist Li. Hopefully, some of your luck can rub off on all of us on this trip," Fox 3 chuckled.

Han Li merely smiled and offered no response.

As this conversation was taking place, the white mist within the entrance of the sect had begun to churn violently, and it quickly transformed into a massive white vortex with a narrow passageway at its center.

Faint rays of light could be seen within the passageway, presenting a rather mysterious sight to behold.

"It's already taken us quite some time to break that restriction, so let's not waste any more time here," Fox 3 said as he flew into the passageway as a streak of silver light, followed immediately by Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

Han Li was just about to follow along as well when he suddenly noticed that Shi Chuankong didn't seem to be displaying any intention of moving from the spot, and he asked, "Are you not coming in, Brother Shi? All of the treasures inside could be taken if you're too slow."

"Go on ahead, Brother Li, I'll come in right after I've packed up this array. This array is a closely guarded secret of our Devil Race, so I can't afford to just leave it here," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of purple light that began quickly picking up the array tools on the ground.

"Alright, in that case, I'll be going on ahead as well," Han Li said with a nod before flying into the passageway as a streak of azure light.

A peculiar gleam flashed through Shi Chuankong's eyes as he watched Han Li enter the passageway, and after packing up the silver array on the ground, he quickly followed suit.

However, in the instant that he flew into the passageway, a small purple ball sprang out of his body before hovering in mid-air.

The ball was around the size of a walnut, and there were countless tiny silver runes etched onto its surface, giving off bursts of spatial fluctuations.

The purple ball shuddered momentarily before exploding to form a dense purple devilish cloud with countless silver runes flashing within it.

The purple devilish cloud was swirling and twisting like a living creature as it burrowed into space, but the silver runes within it were left behind to form a silver array that was several dozen feet in size.

The space at the center of the array shuddered violently before a rift opened up, then split apart even further to create a dark purple spatial passageway.

However, the spatial passageway seemed to be extremely unstable and looked as if it could collapse at any moment.

Three figures shot out of the spatial passageway before landing in front of the entrance of the sect.

All three of them were purple-robed devilish beings that were giving off tremendous devilish qi.

The trio was led by a thin elderly man with a dark complexion and a head of sparse hair. His eyes were sunken extremely deep into his face, and he resembled a skeleton wearing a skin suit, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

Furthermore, there was no flesh or blood on his arms whatsoever, and the black arm bones beneath were revealed with a series of worm-like purple runes engraved upon them, giving off formidable devilish qi fluctuations.

Standing beside him was a tall and extremely handsome purple-haired young man with a head of purple hair so long that it could trail all the way down onto the ground.

At the moment, his hair was arranged into a tall bun that was bouncing along behind him, and beneath his purple robe was another red feather robe that seemed to have been woven out of the feathers of some type of spirit bird. The red robe was extremely vibrant, and to complete his extravagant outfit, he was wearing a pair of rainbow-colored boots that were riddled with gemstones.

His overall appearance resembled that of a fancy rooster.

Standing beside him was a purple-robed young woman with a head of luscious hair and an exceptional figure, but her facial features were concealed behind a white veil.

After the three of them flew out of the spatial passageway, it was finally unable to hold itself together any longer, and it quickly collapsed before vanishing altogether.

"The fact that the spatial passageway collapsed so quickly indicates that where we are right now is extremely far away from the Black Soil Immortal Region. It's no wonder that we haven't been able to ascertain the location of these ruins prior to this. If it weren't for the young master guiding us, we could've searched for ten thousand more years without any luck," the elderly man remarked, then turned his gaze toward the white vortex.

"That's the entrance. It looks like the young master and his companions have already broken the restriction. Let's go in," the purple-haired young man said.

However, the elderly man raised an arm to stop him, and several threads of purple light shot out of his fingertips.

"Hold on. The young master told us to wait for a few minutes after we arrive before we enter the ruins."

The young man's expression changed slightly at the sight of the threads of purple light, and a sheepish smile appeared on his face as he said, "My mistake, let's wait for a bit before we go in."

The elderly man gave a cold harrumph before lowering his arm.

......

As soon as Han Li flew into the vortex passageway, his body was instantly swept up by a burst of tremendous power, following which he found himself in a vast expanse of violent white currents.

The currents of white light were surging in a completely haphazard and chaotic fashion, crashing against one another to produce a deafening noise.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this.

These white currents were somewhat similar to the spatial turbulence that he had to endure during his ascension to the True Immortal Realm from the Spirit Domain Realm. However, these currents were far more powerful and interspersed with hints of time law powers.

Even though Han Li had grown countless times more powerful since the time he first arrived in the True Immortal Realm, he was still unable to steady himself, and he was involuntarily pulled along by the white currents.

Bursts of tremendous power were constantly tearing at his body from all directions, and in response, he conjured up his True Extreme Film to form a protective layer over himself.

After that, he took a moment to inspect his surroundings, but all he could see were more chaotic white currents, while Fox 3, Immortal Lord Hot Flame, and Shi Chuankong were nowhere to be found.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he was just about to do something when a giant ball of white light suddenly appeared up ahead before sweeping up his entire body.

The ball of white light was filled with a burst of extremely chaotic time law powers, and Han Li was forced to close his eyes in the face of the blinding white light.

In the next instant, he was abruptly pulled downward by a burst of tremendous force.

A resounding thump rang out as he crashed into something, and all of the spatial turbulence around him instantly vanished.

Upon opening his eyes, he was ecstatic to discover that he had emerged from the white currents, and he had slammed into the ground, creating a massive crater with his fall.

He flew out of the crater before rising up into the air and inspecting his surroundings, upon which he discovered that he was situated on a flat and barren plain that was almost completely devoid of vegetation.

There was white mist all around him, and the sky was also a murky white color.

Due to the presence of this white mist, he wasn't able to see very far, but as soon as he released his spiritual sense to try and get a better grasp on his surroundings, he discovered that there was a burst of peculiar spatial power in the surrounding area that severely restricted his spiritual sense.

Even with his current spiritual sense, he was only able to spread it over an area with a radius of three thousand to four thousand feet.

Hence, he decided to turn to his Infernal Devilish Eyes instead, and that allowed him to see a little further, but visibility was still restricted to only around ten thousand feet.

The surrounding white mist was no ordinary mist, and it posed much impediment to his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Despite the strange nature of the surrounding environment, Han Li remained calm and collected. He had explored countless ruins and secret areas, and he had encountered more than his fair share of strange places during those adventures.

After descending back down onto the ground, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a palm-sized purple jade plate with a complex silver array engraved upon it.

This was a teleportation array plate that Shi Chuankong had given him before they entered the Illusory Smoke Swamp, and it had been refined using a secret technique unique to the Devil Race. The array plate was imbued with a hint of spatial power, allowing communication to take place even through spatial barriers, so it was far more useful in secret areas like this one than normal communication array plates.

The array plate rose up into the air at Han Li's behest, and it released a purple halo that was constantly flashing and fluctuating in brightness.

A long time passed, but no response came from the array plate.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he waited for a while longer before stowing the array plate away.

For some reason, he was unable to establish communication with Fox 3 and the others using the array plate.

If he couldn't find Fox 3, then there would be no way for him to complete this Reincarnation Palace mission, so this was a rather awkward predicament.

At this point, he still didn't even know what the mission entailed. He had raised the question to Fox 3 on multiple occasions in the past, but all Fox 3 had told him was that he would answer that question once they arrived at their destination. However, now that they had arrived, they were no longer in the same place.

Chapter 656: Dead City

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li shook his head as his brows unfurrowed.

Seeing as he couldn't find Fox 3 and the others, he would just have to explore this place by himself for now. After all, he was also very curious about these ruins.

As far as he was aware, the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Mantra Domain had both come out of True Mantra Sect, and neither of them were complete, so perhaps he could find their full versions in this place.

Right as Han Li was about to set off, a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he swept a sleeve through the air to summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd.

A streak of golden light flew out of the gourd at his behest, and it was none other than the golden flag that he had captured earlier.

He grabbed onto the flag before conducting a close inspection, and in doing so, he discovered that the flag was even more remarkable than he had first thought.

The golden star designs on the flag were flashing like living creatures, and it felt as if they could fly out of the flag at any moment.

Furthermore, he could sense tremendous time law power fluctuations surging out of the flag, and they were even more formidable than the time law power fluctuations in the golden lock given to him by Daoist Master Jingyang.

This is also a graded immortal treasure!

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes at this realization, and he opened his mouth to release a burst of golden light, which enveloped the flag before sucking it into his body for refinement.

At the moment, he was in an unknown and potentially dangerous place, so he had to elevate his own powers through any means possible.

With that in mind, Han Li stowed his Profound Heavenly Gourd away, then inspected his surroundings momentarily before flying away in a certain direction.

Due to the limitations on his spiritual sense and eyesight, he was flying very slowly while also constantly scouring his surroundings with his spiritual sense and his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Even though everything appeared to be peaceful and serene here, there was an indescribable sense of pressure in the air that kept him constantly on edge.

Right at this moment, Mo Guang's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Could it be that you've already entered the True Mantra Sect ruins, Fellow Daoist Han? I heard about the True Mantra Sect back when I was with Ma Liang. You're on your own, right? Why don't you release me to help you out?"

"You've come out of seclusion?" Han Li asked, clearly rather taken aback to suddenly be hearing Mo Guang.

"After all these years of hard work, I've finally completely fused with his body, and I won't have to worry about falling out of the High Zenith Stage anymore," Mo Guang replied in a gleeful voice.

"Is that right? Congratulations," Han Li replied.

Mo Guang seemed to be unable to suppress his own excitement, and he continued, "Who would've thought that I would get to the High Zenith Stage before you, Fellow Daoist Han?"

Han Li merely smiled in response, unbothered by Mo Guang's slightly boastful tone.

Given his mastery of the laws of time, his power didn't correspond with his cultivation base at all. Even if Mo Guang were already at the mid-High Zenith Stage, he was confident in his own ability to deal with him.

Mo Guang seemed to have realized that he had let his own excitement get the better of him, and he hurriedly added, "Of course, given your exceptional aptitude, it won't be long before you also reach the High Zenith Stage, Fellow Daoist Han."

"Even though you've successfully stabilized your cultivation base, I think it's best for you to keep consolidating in the Flower Branch domain, and I'll call upon you if I need you," Han Li said.

These ruins seemed to be quite a strange place, and it was best to keep Mo Guang concealed as much as possible, given that he was currently in the body of a Gray Immortal.

"Alright," Mo Guang sighed before falling silent, and Han Li continued to focus on scouring the surrounding environment.

Close to a day passed by in the blink of an eye, and the surrounding environment hadn't changed much at all.

At this point, Han Li was looking a little weary. Constantly maintaining his spiritual sense and his Infernal Devilish Eyes was quite taxing on him, and he had only just taken a recovery pill when he suddenly stopped in his tracks.

Something seemed to have caught his attention, and he drifted down onto the ground, right in front of an object buried in the ground.

It appeared to be a large rock, but it was concealed under a thick layer of soil, so it was impossible to tell exactly what it was.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a whirlwind that was several dozen feet tall, and the whirlwind swept away the soil up ahead to reveal the large, blue rock underneath.

It was a part of the remnants of a building, and it seemed to have been crafted out of some type of special stone material. Even after being buried here for countless years, it hadn't succumbed to erosion.

A hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he immediately continued onward.

As he progressed onward, he noticed more and more vegetation. The area was no longer as barren as before, and he also spotted more and more fallen buildings.

A short while later, he descended onto the ground once again.

Up ahead was a massive palace that was several thousand feet in size and two hundred to three hundred feet tall, entirely constructed out of the same blue stone material.

Back when it was fully intact, the palace would've undoubtedly been extremely majestic, but right now, it was severely ravaged, and a large section of it had collapsed altogether.

The ground near the palace had also been torn to shreds, indicating that a fierce battle had taken place here at some point.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li released his spiritual sense to inspect the surrounding area, and some time later, he suddenly raised an eyebrow as he flew over to a large rock, then pushed it aside to reveal the skeletal remains of a body.

The skeleton was wearing a white robe that had mostly succumbed to erosion, but Han Li was still able to tell that it was the same True Mantra Sect disciple attire that he had seen during his previous spiritual transmigration.

He heaved a faint sigh at the sight of the body.

He was using the True Mantra Sect's cultivation arts, so in a way, he was somewhat connected and indebted to this sect.

He had heard about what the True Mantra Sect had been like during its heyday from Immortal Lord Hot Flame, and it was certainly a sobering sight to see such a powerful sect fall into ruin.

Han Li quickly set aside that train of thought, then swept his spiritual sense over the body, but wasn't able to find any storage tools.

He remained unfazed as he departed and continued to search through the rest of the palace. Before long, he had discovered several more bodies in True Mantra Sect attire, but their storage tools were also missing.

It didn't take long before he had explored the entire palace, and he had nothing to show for it.

He was rather disappointed by this, and he promptly departed, flying away as a streak of azure light.

Shortly after he left the palace, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he stopped cold in his tracks, and he peered into the distance with his Infernal Devilish Eyes while sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of thick azure sword qi that struck the space up ahead.

The space there rippled violently as a vast expanse of black light appeared, and the streak of azure sword qi instantly vanished upon contact, seemingly having been devoured by the black light.

As for the black light itself, it rippled and squirmed slightly like a living creature before slowly fading away.

Is that a spatial rift?

The black light had been completely concealed in space and wasn't giving off any aura, so there was no way that he would've noticed it had it not been for the combination of his spiritual sense and his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he swept a sleeve through the air once again, this time sending a thick arc of golden lightning crashing into the spot where the black light had just faded.

The black light reappeared, and it was able to devour the arc of golden lightning with ease as well.

A hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he swept a sleeve through the air for a third time, releasing a crimson flying sword that rapidly swelled to over a hundred feet in size before striking the black light.

A dull thud rang out as the giant sword made contact with the black light, only for the former to be snapped in half in an instant.

Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon seeing this.

Thankfully, he had noticed the arc of black light ahead of time. Otherwise, if he had unwittingly flown into it, he would've definitely been severely injured, if not killed on the spot.

With that in mind, Han Li picked up the two halves of the snapped sword, then skirted around the arc of black light as he continued onward.

In the wake of that close call, he became even more cautious, and he didn't dare to withdraw his spiritual sense or Infernal Devilish Eyes for even a moment.

As he continued onward, more and more ruins appeared in his path, and all of them had been destroyed as collateral damage from previous battles.

It didn't take long before another day passed by, and at this point, he was starting to grow a little disgruntled.

The True Mantra Sect ruins had been destroyed to such an extent that he hadn't been able to find anything of use aside from several spirit medicines of a decent quality.

This entire area was like a completely dead city.

The terrain down below was still very flat, but some mountains had occasionally begun to appear.

Han Li flew onward for a moment longer before his expression suddenly changed slightly.

The ground up ahead had completely sunken downward to form a massive valley, and there were some palaces down in the valley that appeared to be relatively intact.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he flew down into the valley.

The valley was enormous, and he was only able to see a small section of it with his spiritual sense and devilish eyes.

The ground in the valley was quite flat and smooth, and there were white stone slabs that paved the earth as far as the eyes could see.

It seemed that this had once been quite an important place.

The valley wasn't spared from the ravages of battle, but the buildings here had been constructed using far better materials, so most of them were still relatively intact.

A hint of excitement welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he continued to scour his surroundings while venturing deeper into the valley.

It didn't take long before he was quite deep into the valley, and there were many bodies laying here, belonging to both True Mantra Sect disciples and Heavenly Court cultivators.

Based on what he had seen thus far, it appeared that there was a giant city in the valley, and the buildings that lined the streets he was walking along appeared to be shops.

Prior to its destruction, this would've been quite a majestic city, and along the way, Han Li had found several decent materials.

Upon arriving at the conclusion of a wide street, a huge plaza suddenly appeared ahead of him.

Chapter 657: Battle in the Water Divination Palace

Han Li quickly swept his gaze over the plaza, and something caught his attention.

He rose up into the air, then flew over to a giant palace across from the plaza.

This palace was far more massive than the other ones, and it had been constructed out of some type of translucent, dark blue crystalline material. There was a layer of faintly rippling blue light over its surface, giving it the appearance of a seabed crystal palace.

Han Li was able to identify this blue crystalline material as Seablue Crystal, a type of water-attribute crystal that was renowned for its sturdiness. It wasn't exactly a premium material, but it was still quite precious, and constructing an entire palace out of it was a huge show of extravagance.

However, he hadn't been drawn to the palace by its construction materials. Instead, he was intrigued by what was inside.

It was very faint, but he could sense a burst of time law fluctuations deep within the palace.

Perhaps it was because the palace had been entirely constructed from Seablue Crystal, but it was almost perfectly preserved, despite the fact that all of the other palaces in the same area were displaying damage to different extents.

Hanging above the entrance of the palace was a plaque that read "Water Divination Palace", and Han Li was just about to step into the palace when his gaze was suddenly drawn to something by the entrance.

It was a dark blue stone statue that had toppled to the ground. The statue was over a thousand feet tall, and it depicted a strange child with a massive head and a disproportionately thin body.

The base of the statue had been shattered, and as Han Li looked at the statue of the strange child, he was struck by a sense of familiarity, as if he had seen it before somewhere.

All of a sudden, he recalled where he had seen the child before.

Back when he was eavesdropping on Patriarch Miro's lecture through the translucent wall of light, there had been five figures seated around him, and one of them had been this strange child.

Why is there a statue of him here? Does he have something to do with this Water Divination Palace?

After lingering at the entrance of the palace for a short while longer, Han Li cast that train of thought aside before stepping inside.

As soon as he stepped into the palace, he immediately found himself in a rather dim setting with a subtle sense of pressure in the air.

His brows furrowed slightly, but he continued onward.

The palace was rather empty, with nothing inside with the exception of a few giant Seablue Crystal pillars. There were many signs of battle in here as well, and one of the stone pillars had even been severed altogether.

Han Li swept his gaze across the palace, but didn't discover anything, so he continued onward, and it didn't take long before he had reached the palace's deepest point.

There was a giant gate on the wall on either side of him, and beyond those gates were a pair of long black tunnels that extended as far as the eyes could see before vanishing into darkness.

While Han Li was outside the palace, he had noticed many more palaces behind this one, and it seemed that this was quite a large cluster of buildings.

Han Li could sense that the burst of time law fluctuations was situated somewhere to his right, so he immediately made his way into the tunnel on the right without any hesitation.

The tunnel had been entirely constructed out of a type of black stone material, and it was giving off a cold aura.

There were many signs of battle here as well, including countless gashes that had been sliced into the walls and a series of large cracks on the ground.

However, these black walls were extremely sturdy and hadn't been completely destroyed.

On top of that, there were also some bodies belonging to True Mantra Sect disciples or Heavenly Court cultivators littered throughout the tunnel, and perhaps it was because this was a rather isolated place, but the baleful qi here was quite dense, and there were gusts of yin wind sweeping through the air from up ahead.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. At the moment, he was struggling with his baleful decay, so he was naturally not fond of an environment like this one, but he wasn't going to turn back over such a trivial matter.

The black tunnel was remarkably long, and even after walking for several minutes, Han Li still hadn't reached the end. However, the more he continued onward, the wider and taller the tunnel became.

At the same time, the baleful qi in the air was also becoming denser and denser, stirring up some unrest in the baleful qi in his own body.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his cultivation arts to protect himself and keep out the external baleful qi.

After continuing onward for a while longer, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he stopped in his tracks.

He could hear the sound of faint rumbling ringing out up ahead, and it seemed that a battle was taking place.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he chanted an incantation to conjure up a dim light barrier that enveloped his entire body, then silently shot forward as a faint shadow.

It didn't take long for him to reach the end of the tunnel, and a series of connected dark palaces appeared up ahead.

All of the palaces were connected by passageways, resulting in a complex network of passageways.

Han Li followed the sounds that he was hearing and passed through around a dozen palaces, upon which he discovered the source of the sounds in a giant palace that was tens of thousand of feet in size.

There were a series of thick stone pillars standing in this palace, and all of them were riddled with countless runes.

Most of these pillars had already collapsed to create a large, open area, and at this moment, there were three cultivators in that open area, locked in battle against five or six black shadows.

The three cultivators consisted of a brawny man in a blue cloak, wielding an enormous blue sword, an elegant purple-robed woman with a veil over her face, and handsome red-robed man who seemed to be wearing some makeup on his face, giving him a rather effeminate appearance.

The purple-robed woman had dense devilish qi swirling all around her, and it was clear that she was a being of the Devil Race.

As for the red-robed man, Han Li was able to identify as Feng Qingyuan, the man that he had come across once back in the Leisure Valley, and he certainly wasn't expecting to see him again here.

It seemed that the Heavenly Court had also had its sights set on the True Mantra Sect ruins, but it was unclear to Han Li how they had managed to enter the ruins.

The black shadows that the three of them were battling were some type of black humanoid creature that was several dozen feet tall.

Their bodies were covered in black fur, giving the appearance of giant apes, and each of them also had a pair of dark red horns on their heads, as well as mouthfuls of fearsome-looking fangs.

What are those things?

To Han Li's surprise, these black ape-like creatures were quite formidable. Despite their enormous statures, they were able to move as swiftly as the wind, and their bodies were so resilient that they could directly clash against the immortal treasures of Feng Qingyuan's trio without sustaining any injuries.

Occasional bursts of black flames erupted out of the black apes' mouths, and Feng Qingyuan's trio seemed to be quite apprehensive of these black flames, mostly choosing to evade them, rather than withstand them head-on.

Even though Feng Qingyuan's trio was firmly on the back foot in this battle, they were clearly all seasoned combatants, and they remained calm and collected, managing to keep the ferocious assault from the black ape creatures at bay.

Han Li only observed the battle for a short while before turning his gaze to the rest of the palace, but he didn't notice any treasures here.

It seemed the three of them hadn't come here to pursue any treasures. Instead, they were simply unfortunate to have encountered these ape creatures.

Seeing as there were no treasures here, Han Li naturally had no intention of revealing himself, yet right as he was about to slip away, a black beastly claw suddenly appeared behind him out of thin air before making a grab for his heart.

Han Li's expression changed slightly as he shot forward like lightning while hurriedly sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of azure swordlight that appeared behind him in a flash before slashing toward the black claw.

A resounding boom rang out as the streak of azure sword light was shattered, reverting back into an azure flying sword that tumbled back through the air.

As for the black claw, a long gash had been slashed into it, one that had almost sliced the claw into two.

A giant black ape creature then shot out of the darkness before letting loose a furious roar in Han Li's direction.

This ape creature was around twice the size of the others, and its entire body was riddled with a series of crimson patterns. There was also a cloud of black qi swirling around his body, hovering within which was a large black flag that was giving off the law power fluctuations of an immortal treasure.

Black light was rapidly flashing from the palm of the black ape creature's hand, drawing the surrounding baleful qi into its body, and the gash on its hand was fully healed in the blink of an eye.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he summoned the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword back to himself before descending onto the ground.

All of this had taken place in an instant, and Feng Qingyuan's trio was currently also staring at Han Li with surprised looks on their faces.

The giant ape creature let loose a thunderous roar before pouncing at Han Li as a black shadow,and Han Li gave a cold harrumph in response as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a thick arc of Divine Devilbane Lightning toward the oncoming creature.

All of the nearby baleful qi in the wake of the arc of golden lightning instantly disintegrated into nothingness, but the ape creature was completely unfazed as it opened its mouth to blast forth a burst of black flames.

A resounding boom rang out as the lightning and flames clashed, and they began tearing at each other like a pair of wyrms, one golden and one black, with neither one able to get the better of the other.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release another azure flying sword, which pierced straight through the lightning and flames at an astonishing speed.

A dull thump rang out as the black flames were scattered, while the azure flying sword continued onward, appearing in front of the giant ape creature in the blink of an eye before piercing directly toward it.

Chapter 658: A Band of Four

The giant ape creature let loose a low roar, and the black flag above its head swooped down while giving off radiant black light, catching the oncoming azure flying sword like a giant black hand.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which the azure flying sword shuddered violently while releasing incredibly bright azure light alongside thick arcs of golden lightning.

The black flag was instantly torn to shreds, while the azure flying sword continued onward without pause.

A stunned and fearful look appeared on the giant ape creature's face, and all of the crimson patterns on its body lit up.

Immediately thereafter, a pair of crimson wings of light appeared on its back, and it flapped those wings vigorously, darting to the side while leaving a trail of afterimages in its wake.

A dull tearing sound rang out, and the giant ape creature reappeared several hundred feet away with a long and deep sword gash on its left shoulder. Its entire left arm had almost been severed, but no blood was flowing out of the wound, and the creature didn't seem to possess a body of flesh and blood.

Han Li wasn't surprised to see this, and he casually raised a hand, upon which the azure flying sword instantly flew back to him, then split up into three smaller azure swords before flying back up his sleeve.

At this moment, there was a furious look on the giant ape creature's face, but instead of pouncing at Han Li again, it opened its mouth up wide to release a relentless torrent of black flames toward him.

The black flames encompassed an enormous area, making them seem impossible to evade.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of his body, then surged forth to form a wave of golden lightning that clashed against the wave of black fire.

A string of earth-shattering booms rang out, and an impasse ensued, with neither side able to get the better of the other.

The nearby stone pillars immediately began to shatter, sending loose rocks flying in all directions, while the entire palace trembled violently.

However, the palace didn't collapse, perhaps because it possessed the innate structural integrity required to hold itself intact, or perhaps because there were fortifying restrictions set up within it.

Right at this moment, Han Li made a hand seal, and he abruptly vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning.

The giant ape creature was quite alert, and it immediately spread its crimson wings to flee the scene upon seeing this.

However, a cold harrumph suddenly rang out in its mind, and a burst of extremely sharp spiritual sense speared into its consciousness, causing it to let loose an agonized roar while also rendering it temporarily immobile.

Almost at the exact same moment, a large golden lock appeared beside it out of thin air, then locked onto its right arm.

Boundless golden radiance erupted out of the golden lock, forming a giant golden rune that imprinted itself onto the ape creature's body, instantly rooting it to the spot.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li appeared behind the ape creature amid a flash of golden lightning, then reached out and gently tapped two of his fingers against the back of the creature's head.

A burst of piercing light that contained a silver flower design instantly vanished into the creature's head, splitting it into several pieces, but instead of falling apart, the pieces remained completely still.

Han Li withdrew his fingers, then made a hand seal, and the giant golden rune on the ape creature's body instantly faded, while the golden lock also reverted back to roughly the size of the palm of his hand before falling into his grasp.

Over the past years, he had already completely refined the lock, and it was just as powerful as he had hoped.

As soon as the golden lock was removed, the ape creature's head instantly exploded into a vast expanse of baleful qi, and its headless body shuddered momentarily before also disintegrating into baleful qi, following which a black crystal came falling out.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that swept the black crystal into his grasp, upon which he discovered that it seemed to be the ape creature's core, and it was giving off incredibly formidable baleful qi.

So that thing was an earth soul demon...

Despite the "demon" in its name, earth soul demons were actually a type of ghostly creature that only had a chance of emerging in places with a high abundance of corpse-derived baleful qi. They were very adept at concealing themselves and were also quite intelligent, making them very dangerous to unsuspecting targets.

Right at this moment, Mo Guang's voice rang out in Han Li's mind.

"Give that crystal to me, Fellow Daoist Han. It'll be very useful for my cultivation."

Han Li took a glance at the black crystal, then flipped a hand over to stow it away into the Flower Branch domain.

The other black ape creatures screeched in horror at the sight of their leader's demise, and they immediately turned and fled into the distance, quickly vanishing out of sight, while Feng Qingyuan's trio made no effort to stop them.

The three of them stowed their immortal treasures away, then turned collectively to Han Li.

"Thank you for slaying that Earth Soul Ghost Monarch and scaring away its minions, Fellow Daoist. Otherwise, I don't know how much longer we would've been trapped here for," the brawny man said with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li, and his two companions also expressed their gratitude.

"You're far too kind, fellow daoists. Given your powers, you could've easily defeated those ghostly creatures even without my help," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

Even though all three of them had used secret techniques to conceal their cultivation bases, Han Li was able to tell that they were all at least at the late-Golden Immortal Stage.

None of them had displayed their full power when dealing with those earth soul demons, and it seemed that they were more wary of each other than they had been of those creatures.

"In any case, I should still thank you for your help," the brawny man said with a smile.

Han Li gave a slight nod in response, and he appeared calm and collected on the surface, but internally, his mind was racing.

He couldn't tell what the brawny man's affiliations were, but he knew that Feng Qingyuan most likely had ties to the Heavenly Court, while the purple-robed woman was clearly a devilish being, so why were the three of them seemingly traveling together in the True Mantra Sect ruins?

"Now that we've all run into each other, why don't we get to know one another and explore these ruins together? After all, no one knows what could be waiting for us up ahead, so it would surely be a good idea to band together and combine our powers," the brawny man proposed.

"That's true. This is a very mysterious place, so it would indeed be a good idea for all of us to travel together," Han Li replied.

The presence of these people in the True Mantra Sect ruins made Han Li feel as if there were some mysterious circumstances at play here.

Even though the three of them were all quite formidable, Han Li was confident in his ability to handle them, and perhaps he could uncover some secrets by traveling with them.

Feng Qingyuan and the purple-robed woman considered this offer briefly before also nodding in agreement.

"Great! Allow me to introduce myself: my name is Ren Hao," the brawny man said as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li's trio.

"My name is Feng Jiangliu," Han Li declared, providing the name on the Heavenly Sand Sect token that Fox 3 had arranged for him.

"I'm Yuan Feng," Feng Qingyuan said.

"My name is Feng Lin," the purple-robed woman said with a smile.

None of them knew if the names provided by the others were real or not, but with the self-introductions out of the way, the atmosphere had warmed up a little.

Despite Ren Hao's imposing stature, he was surprisingly sociable and outgoing, and with him initiating some lighthearted conversation, the atmosphere lightened up even further.

"How long have the three of you been in here? I only just got here, and it's been a real pain trying to navigate this place as my spiritual sense is severely restricted," Ren Hao said with a wry smile.

"I only just got here as well, probably even later than the three of you, so I'm also still just trying to get my bearings," Han Li said.

Feng Qingyuan and Feng Lin also offered similar responses, and it seemed none of them had any more information than the others.

"In that case, let's keep going. This place is still relatively intact, so perhaps there are some treasures in here. Just make sure to be careful and not trigger any restrictions," Ren Hao cautioned, and Han Li's trio raised no objections.

With that, the four of them continued onward, occasionally chatting with each other as they walked along, but still made sure to keep some distance between one another.

Han Li was walking at the very rear of the group, inspecting his surroundings with a contemplative look on his face.

He didn't know if Fox 3 and the others were aware of the Devil Race and Heavenly Court presence in these ruins.

If they didn't, then that would be fine, but if they already knew but were intentionally keeping him in the dark, then he would have to tread with caution.

With that in mind, Han Li was beginning to regret taking on this mission, but at this point, he could only forge ahead.

After passing through a few more palaces, the group finally emerged from the cluster of palaces, upon which they arrived in an open area at the foot of a hill.

There was a wide and straight white jade path that led all the way up the hill, and at this point, Han Li could sense that the burst of time law power fluctuations had become quite potent, and that it was coming straight from ahead of the jade path.

Given how pronounced the time law power fluctuations were, Ren Hao's trio had to have already sensed it as well, so he would have to think about how he was going to claim whatever it was that was at the end of the path.

With that in mind, he took a subtle glance at the trio, and he was surprised to discover all three of them looking onward with a mixture of anticipation and apprehension in their eyes, but no sense of elation, whatsoever.

Chapter 659: Five Paths

Han Li was rather surprised to see this. Judging from their reactions, it seemed like Feng Qingyuan’s trio hadn’t detected the time law power fluctuations at all.

If they were merely acting, then this was an extremely convincing act that Han Li couldn’t find any holes in.

“It looks like there are more buildings up ahead, but we haven’t even explored the cluster of palaces that we just passed through. What do you all want to do? Should we keep going or return to those earlier palaces for future exploration?” Ren Hao asked.

Han Li’s trio remained silent, but all of them cast their eyes directly forward.

“It looks like we’re all on the same page. Onward we go,” Ren Hao said with a smile.

With that, the four of them continued onward in a single-row formation.

The white jade path was quite wide, but it wasn’t very long, and the four of them quickly reached its conclusion, where they arrived before a plaza that was over ten thousand feet in size on the mountain summit.

The ground was paved with white jade slabs, and at the center of the plaza was another stone statue of the same child with the large head.

This statue hadn’t been damaged, and it seemed to have already been standing here for countless years.

Han Li and the others took a glance at the statue, then quickly turned their attention to the front of the plaza.

There were five smaller white jade paths that branched off in different directions from the plaza before fading into the white mist up ahead.

There was a tall blue jade plaque next to each path, and they carried five place names: Disciple Meadow, Three Water Pagoda, Five Spirit Pavilion, Heavenbearing Palace, and Heavenly Medicine Valley.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li’s eyes as he looked at the five place names.

The Disciple Meadow and the Heavenly Medicine Valley were most likely where the True Mantra Sect disciples resided and where their spirit medicines were stored, respectively. However, the Three Water Pagoda, the Five Spirit Pavilion, and the Heavenbearing Palace didn’t reveal much just based on their names alone.

Ren Hao, Feng Qingyuan, and Feng Lin were also observing the five paths with hesitant expressions.

“Looks like we’ll have to split up from here. Which paths are all of you planning to take?” Ren Hao asked.

Han Li turned his gaze to the second path, the one that was labeled “Three water Pagoda”.

He could sense that this was where the time law power fluctuations were coming from.

Before he had a chance to speak, Ren Hao suddenly said, “I’ll choose this path. I’m using a water-attribute cultivation art, so I should be able to find something useful at this Three Water Pagoda.”

A hint of vexation flashed through Han Li’s heart upon hearing this, but his expression remained unchanged.

“I want to take a look at this Heavenly Medicine Valley. Hopefully, I’ll be able to find some useful spirit medicines there,” Feng Lin said.

“In that case, I’ll go with the Heavenbearing Palace. It sounds like an important place, so maybe I’ll have some luck there,” Feng Qingyuan said, then wasted no time as he promptly departed.

Han Li remained silent as he made his way onto the third path, the one labeled “Five Spirit Pavilion”.

“Alright, it looks like everyone has made a decision. This is where we part ways, I wish you all good fortune,” Ren Hao said with a smile, then stepped onto the second path, quickly disappearing into the mist.

Han Li’s trio also quickly vanished into the white mist on their respective paths, and peace and quiet returned to the plaza.

Moments later, an azure shadow shot back out of the third path, then descended onto the plaza, revealing itself to be Han Li.

He took a quick glance at his surroundings, then flew down the path labeled “Three Water Pagoda”.

Shortly thereafter, a figure emerged on the fourth path, and it was none other than Feng Qingyuan.

He also immediately began making his way down the second path without any hesitation.

Mere moments later, Feng Lin also reappeared on the white jade plaza before taking the same path as everyone else.

Han Li’s aura was completely concealed as he made his way down the second path, and it didn’t take long before he arrived in an open area, where a giant three-story pagoda was standing over ten thousand feet up ahead.

The bottom level of the pagoda was octagonal in shape and constructed out of giant azure stone blocks that were riddled with tiny runes, and there was a huge arched entrance that was around thirty feet tall directly facing him.

Han Li briefly inspected his surroundings, but wasn’t able to find Ren Hao, and after ensuring that there was nothing amiss, he began making his way toward the pagoda.

Upon reaching the arched entrance, he discovered that the black pagoda gates were opened inward, and there were some signs of damage on them, indicating that whatever restrictions that had been placed upon them had been destroyed.

Instead of immediately entering the pagoda, he peered into its interior from the entrance, but all he could see was a faint layer of mist that was almost non-existent, but made it impossible to see what was inside.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he stepped into the pagoda.

As soon as he did so, he immediately felt as if the surrounding blue mist had suddenly become several times denser, and there was also an acrid stench in the air that caused his brows to furrow slightly.

He looked down at his own feet, upon which he was astonished to discover that he was standing on a crimson sea of fire, and the acrid odor that he had just caught a whiff of had come from his burning boots and robes.

This is another illusion…

As soon as Han Li made this realization, he immediately channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique.

In the next instant, a cool and refreshing sensation permeated throughout his consciousness restoring his clarity of mind.

At the same time, the flames all over his body quickly faded until all that remained in the room was the same blue mist from before, which still refused to dissipate.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes, then quickly swept his gaze over the surrounding area, and the entire room was instantly made clear to him.

The empty hall was severely ravaged, littered with destroyed stone pillars and chunks of wood, while the ground was caked in dried blood.

Virtually the entire hall was covered in a layer of bodies, all of which appeared to have suffered very horrific deaths.

From the robes that still hadn’t completely succumbed to erosion, Han Li could see that the bodies belonged to both True Mantra Sect disciples and Heavenly Court cultivators, indicating that a fierce battle had taken place here.

On top of that, there were also many blue humanoid puppets interspersed among the bodies, but they had all been destroyed beyond repair.

There were multiple partitions in the hall, and as Han Li made his way through the area, he saw more of the same, namely severely ravaged walls, bodies strewn everywhere, and the ground caked in dried blood.

Upon reaching the deepest point of the hall, Han Li spotted a white jade staircase that led up to the second floor of the pagoda.

There was an enormous sword that was still plunged into the staircase, but it was extremely severely eroded and was nothing more than a huge piece of scrap metal.

Piles of bodies were strewn around the sword, stacking up to several dozen feet tall, and after scanning the area, Han Li wasn’t able to find anything useful, so he moved on to the second floor.

As soon as he made his way onto the second floor, he was immediately struck by a bone-chilling sensation, and the immortal spiritual power in his body began to circulate on its own to protect him from the chill.

It was as if he had entered a glacial space, and everything, from the ground, the pillars, the walls, the window frames, and even the ceiling was all covered in a layer of blue ice crystals.

For a moment, Han Li came under the impression that the second floor was even larger than the first one, but he then quickly realized that this only appeared to be the case as the partitions on the first floor were absent from the second floor.

However, just like on the first floor, the second floor was also littered with bodies belonging to True Mantra Sect and Heavenly Court cultivators, all of which had suffered horrific deaths, but the owners of these bodies clearly possessed superior cultivation bases back when they were alive, as evidenced by the fact that some of the bodies hadn’t completely decayed yet.

On top of that, Han Li also noticed many giant demon beast carcasses near the walls, but all of them were so severely damaged that it was impossible to tell what they had been.

The baleful qi on the second floor was far denser than it was on the first floor, and Han Li made his way past the bodies in an expressionless manner, walking toward the staircase up ahead, which was also encased in ice.

However, after walking only several hundred feet, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he looked down, only to discover that there as nothing on the icy floor aside from his own reflection.

I clearly sensed something just now…

Right at this moment, he suddenly rasied an eyebrow as he noticed that an extremely exaggerated and gruesome smile had appeared on the face of his own reflection on the ground.

In the same instant, he summoned an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword before plunging it firmly into the ground.

However, his reflection was able to evade the sword strike as if it were an agile fish in water, and it sprang out of the ice directly ahead of Han Li before plunging its hands directly toward his chest.

Chapter 660: Corpse Wraith

At this point, Han Li’s reflection no longer bore any resemblance to him. Its body was no different from that of a normal person, but its clothes were in tatters, and its face had decayed to the point that the bone underneath was clearly visible, giving it a zombie-like appearance.

As it plunged its hands toward Han Li, its nails elongated to over a foot in length each, with dense baleful qi clinging to them.

This is a Corpse Wraith!

Han Li immediately withdrew his sword, then raised it in front of his own chest to defend himself.

A loud clang rang out as a trail of sparks erupted from the blade of the sword, and Han Li was sent flying back by a burst of tremendous force.

Corpse Wraiths were entities that combined corpses and yin souls. They were undead creatures that could only arise after being trapped in places of immense baleful qi after tens of thousands of years, and they relish in devouring the flesh and blood of living beings.

Corpse Wraiths were already dead, so they couldn’t be classified as living beings, and they couldn’t enter the cycle of reincarnation, so they weren’t ghosts, either. Instead, they were liminal beings that belonged nowhere, and this particular one possessed High Zenith Stage power.

However, Han Li could see from its eyes that it was still yet to attain intelligence, and that came as quite a relief.

It was said that once a Corpse Wraith devoured sufficient blood and flesh, it would be able to attain intelligence, thereby making it a far more formidable foe to deal with, often possessing far superior power to living cultivators of the same caliber.

This Corpse Wraith had most likely been trapped here its entire existence, thereby robbing it of any opportunity to come into contact with living beings, and that was why it hadn’t attained intelligence. It was also because of this that Han Li wasn’t fleeing the scene right away.

If another late-Golden Immortal cultivator had been in Han Li’s place, they would’ve most likely already fallen prey to that initial sneak attack.

All of a sudden, the Corpse Wraith vanished from the spot. Han LI’s pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately launched himself backward in retreat.

Almost in the exact same instant, the Corpse Wraith reappeared where he had been standing just a moment ago, and its hands pierced straight through a stone pillar, shattering it into countless pieces.

While still darting back in retreat, Han Li chanted a silent incantation, and a ball of golden light instantly erupted out of his body, forming a golden light barrier that encompassed the entirety of the second floor.

As soon as the time spirit domain was conjured up, everything on the second floor instantly slowed down.

Han Li turned to discover the High Zenith Stage Corpse Wraith charging toward him while leaving a trail of afterimages in its wake, displaying tremendous speed even within the time spirit domain.

Han Li swiveled around before piercing the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in his hand directly toward the Corpse Wraith, and a resounding clang rang out as the sword forcibly parted the Corpse Wraith’s ghostly claws before piercing straight into its chest.

However, the Corpse Wraith’s physical constitution was far more formidable than Han LI anticipated, and the sword was only able to scratch several white marks onto its chest, but was unable to harm it in the slightest.

Meanwhile, the Corpse Wraith had already withdrawn its hands, and its sharp fingernails elongated even further before piercing through the air toward Han Li’s neck from both directions.

Han Li thrust the palm of his hand against the base of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword’s hilt, and it immediately began piercing into the Corpse Wraith’s chest with renewed power while also releasing arcs of Divine Devilbane Lightning.

The Corpse Wraith howled like a wounded animal as its entire body stiffened before toppling backward.

Its chest had been completely charred black, and there were plumes of nauseating black smoke rising up from the wound.

Han Li instantly darted over to the Corpse Wraith, aiming to deal the finishing blow before it had a chance to get back up, but all of a sudden, a burst of purple light flashed through the Corpse Wraith’s eyes, and its body disintegrated into a plume of smoke right before Han Li was able to land his attack.

Han Li’s heart jolted slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly darted back in retreat.

Right at this moment, the Corpse Wraith’s body reverted back to a substantial form, and it reappeared right behind Han Li before thrusting its claws toward the back of his chest.

Thankfully, its speed was significantly hampered by the time spirit domain, so Han Li was able to easily evade the attack before swiveling around and slashing his sword toward his assailant.

Dozens of arcs of golden lightning sprang out of the sword, then intertwined with each other to form a golden lightning net, which cut off all possible avenues of retreat for the Corpse Wraith.

A loud, metallic clang rang out as the sword struck the Corpse Wraith on the head, and its entire body was inundated by golden lightning.

Countless arcs of golden lightning sprang forth in all directions as plumes of black smoke rose up incessantly.

The Corpse Wraith howled in agony as its body was being rapidly charred black, but its aura didn’t weaken in the slightest, so it was clear that this wasn’t going to be anywhere near enough to kill it.

Right as Han Li was about to summon a few more Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords to help his cause, the Corpse Wraith’s body disintegrated once again before fleeing into the icy ground.

Plumes of dense, black baleful qi began to converge from all directions beneath the layer of ice, then surged into the Corpse Wraith’s body in a frenzy.

As a result, all of the injuries that the Corpse Wraith had sustained from Han Li’s Divine Devilbane Lightning were quickly healed.

Han Li’s brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he took a step forward, then abruptly vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he appeared directly above the Corpse Wraith, then swung his sword upon its head.

A resounding boom rang out as the ice on the ground exploded, and the Corpse Wraith darted out like a slippery eel, taking on a substantial form once again as it pounced at Han Li.

Han Li raised his sword to keep it bay, but it completely disregarded the Divine Devilbane Lightning as it grabbed onto the sword with both hands, then opened its mouth up wide and let loose a shrill shriek.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li’s heart upon seeing this, and he immediately held his breath while also cutting off his five senses, but he had reacted just a split second too late.

A plume of dark purple corpse baleful qi shot forth like an arrow before striking him in the face, instantly causing his face to go numb.

Immediately thereafter, he felt a burst of burning pain in his throat and airways, and his eyes also became extremely sore and dry, causing his vision to blur.

He gritted his teeth against the discomfort as he injected his immortal spiritual power into his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, unleashing a powerful eruption of Divine Devilbane LIghtning to force back the Corpse Wraith.

At the same time, he darted back in retreat before moving back and forth throughout the hall, ensuring that he was constantly in motion.

The Corpse Wraith immediately pounced at him once again, pursuing him intently as it attempted to tear him to shreds.

At this moment, Han Li’s five senses were sealed, so he could only track the Corpse Wraith with his spiritual sense while continuing to take evasive measures.

Somehow, despite the effects of the time spirit domain, the Corpse Wraith was becoming faster and faster, and before long, it had managed to tear several gashes into Han Li’s robes.

Right at this moment, the Corpse Wraith suddenly split up into five identical figures.

All of a sudden, Han Li could detect five identical auras in his spiritual sense, and his brows immediately furrowed slightly. His eyes has been infiltrated by corpse baleful qi, so he was unable to use his Infernal Devilish Eyes to determine which of the five figures was the real Corpse Wraith.

The five Corpse Wraiths formed an encirclement around Han Li before darting at him in unison, and all of them had their claws aimed at different vital regions on his body.

Regardless of which direction Han Li chose to flee in, he would inevitably be intercepted by one of the Corpse Wraiths, following which the others would also get to him.

In this dire situation, a burst of radiant golden light abruptly erupted out of his body, and the five Corpse Wraiths were instantly rooted to the spot roughly ten feet away from Han Li as the golden light washed over them.

At the same time, Han Li opened his mouth, and a cloud of corpse baleful qi erupted out of his mouth before slamming into the ground, where it exploded.

The purple mist on his face immediately faded, and bright purple light appeared in his eyes as he cast his gaze toward the five surrounding Corpse Wraiths.

In doing so, he discovered that one of the Corpse Wraiths had several times the amount of baleful qi in its body compared with the others, and he immediately aimed the tip of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword at that Corpse Wraith’s dantian.

A ball of golden lightning then quickly took shape at the tip of the sword before being launched through the air, and a thick pillar of golden lightning emerged, instantly inundating the Corpse Wraith’s entire body.

The entire blue hall shuddered violently, and the four other Corpse Wraiths disintegrated in rapid succession, leaving only the Corpse Wraith that had been struck by Han Li’s Lightningwield Technique, still suspended in mid-air from the effects of the True Mantra Axis.

Chapter 661: Body of the Large-headed Child

What a pain in the backside...

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly as he watched the Corpse Wraith re-emerge while the lightning faded.

The Corpse Wraith didn't possess any intelligence, but its physical constitution wasn't inferior to that of a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal, and Han Li's Lightningwield Technique had inflicted severe injuries upon it, but wasn't enough to kill it.

Given the current circumstances, he couldn't afford to waste much time here.

Right as he was considering summoning the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword that had been nurtured for the longest time in his Profound Heavenly Gourd or releasing the Essence Fire Raven to incinerate the Corpse Wraith, Mo Guang's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Fellow Daoist Han, while it's true that this thing possesses similar attributes to ghostly creatures, its high cultivation base grants it some resistance against lightning and fire-attribute attacks, so it won't be easy for you to take it down. How about you leave it to me instead?"

"You have a way to kill this thing?" Han Li asked.

"Indeed. I just so happen to know where its fatal weaknesses are, and if you leave it to me, I can kill it in a very short time," Mo Guang replied.

Han Li considered Mo Guang's proposal for a moment, following which a floral design appeared on the middle and index fingers of his right hand.

A door of light that was around ten feet tall then appeared beside him, and at the same time, Han Li swept his left hand through the air, stowing his Mantra Treasured Axis away up his sleeve.

With the Mantra Treasured Axis gone, the Corpse Wraith instantly regained its mobility, and it continued to charge forward, aiming directly at Han Li's glabella.

Right at this moment, a black figure shot out of the door of silver light, and it appeared before the Corpse Wraith in a flash, then reached out with one hand. There was baleful qi swirling around the hand, and it was thrust straight through the point where the Corpse Wraith's chest and abdomen were connected.

The black figure was none other than Mo Guang, and at this moment, his hand was protruding out of the other side of the Corpse Wraith's body with a fist-sized chunk of black flesh clasped within it.

The chunk of flesh resembled a heart, but had seven orifices, and it was pulsing rhythmically as if it were breathing.

"The fatal weakness of a Corpse Wraith does not lie in its dantian, its head, or its heart. Instead, it lies in this thing, which is known as a baleful embryo. It's through this thing that it was able to gather baleful qi and become a Corpse Wraith. However, it's also exactly because of this that the baleful embryo is particularly vulnerable to baleful qi attacks," Mo Guang explained as he slowly withdrew his hand.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the Corpse Wraith's body disintegrated into countless dark purple sand-like granules before dissipating into a cloud of black smoke.

"What do you plan to do with this baleful embryo, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang asked.

"You slew the Corpse Wraith, so its baleful embryo naturally goes to you," Han Li replied.

Mo Guang gave a nod of gratitude, then crushed the baleful embryo into powder to reveal a longan-sized bead inside.

Before Han Li had a chance to catch a clear glimpse of the object, Mo Guang had already tossed it into his own mouth before swallowing it.

"If you don't need anything else from me, then I'll go back to seclusion," Mo Guang said.

"Thanks for your help," Han Li replied with a nod.

With that, Mo Guang stepped back into the door of silver light, then returned to the main building, where he sat down with his legs crossed atop his cushion.

Shortly thereafter, the door of silver light gradually faded at Han Li's behest, and he promptly swallowed a pill, then took a moment to rest and recuperate before continuing to make his way deeper into the hall.

Upon reaching the staircase that led to the third floor of the pagoda, he released his spiritual sense to scour its entrance.

Ren Hao had chosen the second path, so he should've entered this pagoda as well, yet Han Li hadn't been able to detect his presence at all on the way here, and that was very strange.

Could it be that he didn't enter this pagoda?

After conducting a brief inspection, Han Li didn't discover anything amiss, and only then did he make his way up the staircase.

Upon reaching the third floor, Han Li spotted an antiquated screen not far up ahead. The scenic painting on the screen was also severely faded, with only a faint outline remaining.

The surface of the screen was also riddled with gashes, and there were many cracks and sword marks even on the frame of the screen, so it was a small miracle that it was even standing at all.

Han Li took a step forward, then stopped in his tracks for a moment as his expression changed ever so slightly, only to continue onward as if nothing had happened.

As he reached the screen, he was able to see several wooden shelves littered throughout the room through the gashes on the screen. The shelves were laden with all types of vases and books, and it seemed that this had once been a study.

However, only after making his way around the screen did he discover that there were close to a hundred of these shelves, but most of them had already been completely destroyed, and the ones that he had seen through the screen were the only ones that remained standing.

Han Li slowly made his way through the toppled shelves, then picked up one of the books that was still relatively intact, and inscribed on the cover of the book was the title "Metal Stone Journal".

He briefly flipped through the pages of the book to discover that it wasn't a cultivation art or secret technique at all. Instead, it was a book dedicated to cataloging different metals and minerals.

After that, he flipped through a few more books, only to discover that they were also just ordinary miscellaneous books.

It looks like whoever was living here had a very broad range of interests...

Han Li continued onward, passing through a series of doors before reaching the deepest point on the third floor.

As soon as he stepped through the final door, he immediately felt a burst of formidable time law power fluctuations surging toward him.

He cast his gaze forward to discover a blue pond with a radius of around two hundred to three hundred feet, and the water in the pond was extremely clear.

The term "waters of time" immediately sprang into Han Li's mind upon seeing this.

Why are the time law power fluctuations so potent here? Could it be that this pond is filled entirely with the waters of time?

Intrigued by this discovery, Han Li carefully searched through the pond with his spiritual sense, upon which he discovered that aside from just time law power fluctuations, there was also a burst of immense vitality present within the pond.

He strode over to the pond before peering over its edge, and only then did he discover that there was a body floating on the surface of the water.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes at the sight of the body.

The body was no more than five feet tall, and it was as thin as a reed stick, but had an extraordinarily large neck that made it appear extremely disproportionate, as if it could sink headfirst into the water at any moment.

However, the body was floating on the surface of the water in a completely still and stable fashion, and it looked as if it were fast asleep.

The body was identical in appearance to the statue that Han Li had seen earlier at the entrance of the Water Divination Pagoda.

Furthermore, it was perfectly preserved without any signs of damage, but it was completely devoid of aura fluctuations. It looked as if it had only perished not long ago, and it was in vastly better condition than the decomposed bodies that Han Li had seen earlier.

Han Li turned his attention from the body to the water beside it, upon which he noticed a blue shield that was around two feet in size. The shield was shimmering brightly and had a series of complex patterns etched all over its surface.

No more than a few inches away from the badge was a blue crystalline flute that was also floating on the water. Hanging from one end of the flute was an intricate-looking tassel that had been fashioned out of seven or eight bamboo leaves.

The two objects were brimming with spiritual qi, and the ravages of time didn't seem to have affected them at all. Furthermore, both of them were giving off formidable time law power fluctuations, indicating that they were powerful time-attribute immortal treasures.

Instead of immediately reaching out to grab the two objects, Han Li turned slightly to the side, sneaking a glance at a round stone pillar situated in the northwestern corner of the hall with faint purple light flashing in his eyes.

Somehow, Ren Hao had managed to fuse as one with that pillar, and his aura had almost been completely concealed.

Thanks to the progress that Han Li had made in the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, his spiritual sense had become even more sensitive than before, so he was able to detect Ren Hao's aura fluctuations as soon as he stepped onto the third floor, but he was unable to ascertain exactly where he was.

At the same time, he knew that Ren Hao had to have spotted him as well, so he had put on an oblivious act, pretending not to have noticed Ren Hao at all.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly raised an eyebrow, then abruptly vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he landed on one of the horizontal beams up above, then completely restrained his own aura and spiritual sense fluctuations, and it was as if he had vanished into thin air.

Shortly thereafter, Feng Qingyuan emerged from the stairwell, and he slowly made his way into the hall with a slightly tense expression.

As he passed through the collapsed shelves, he briefly flipped through some of the pages strewn all over the floor, just as Han Li had done, only to also toss them aside upon realizing that none of them were very useful.

As he did this, the tension in his eyes seemed to have faded a little, but he was walking even slower than before.

Chapter 662: Bait

Feng Qingyuan appeared to be moving in a casual fashion, but in reality, he was on high alert, covertly scanning his surroundings while also releasing his spiritual sense to encompass the entire hall.

However, Han Li and Ren Hao were too well-concealed for him to detect anything.

All of a sudden, Feng Qingyuan sped up in his footsteps, rushing over to the pond in the deepest part of the hall in a flash, and from there, he immediately spotted teh blue shield and the blue flute.

A hint of greed flashed through his eyes at the sight of the two immortal treasures, but just like Han Li, he also refrained from taking them.

He had seen Ren Hao make his way down this path, and on the way here, he had noticed some clear signs of battle on the second floor, so it clearly didn't make sense for there to be no one on the third floor.

"I can see where you are, Fellow Daoist Ren. Why don't you come out to meet me?" Feng Qingyuan suddenly declared.

Han Li reflexively cast his gaze toward the stone pillar that Ren Hao was concealed in upon hearing this, and he could see that Ren Hao had no intention of revealing himself, so he knew that Feng Qingyuan had to have been merely bluffing.

As Feng Qingyuan's voice trailed off, the hall fell into silence once again.

Feng Qingyuan's brows furrowed slightly in the wake of his failed bluff, and after some extensive contemplation, he was unable to suppress the greed in his heart as he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a golden eight-armed puppet.

The puppet sprang onto the surface of the pond at his behest, darting over the water like an agile spider as it reached out for the pair of blue immortal treasures.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he intently scrutinized the golden puppet, preparing to take the immortal treasures from the puppet as soon as they fell into its grasp.

However, right as the golden puppet was about to grab onto the pair of immortal treasures, the still surface of the pond suddenly began to ripple violently, following which a blue figure shot out of the water, sending the golden puppet flying.

A resounding clang rang out as the golden puppet fell heavily onto the edge of the pond.

Immediately thereafter, a large blue foot stomped down onto its chest. The golden puppet was comparable in power to a late-True Immortal cultivator, yet it was unable to pose any resistance as its core crumbled under the foot of its assailant.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Feng Qingyuan had already shot back to over a thousand feet away in retreat. At the same time, a red oil paper umbrella had appeared in his grasp as he cast a wary gaze forward.

The foot that had stomped down onto the puppet's chest belonged to a creature with the head of a fish, but the body of a man, and its skin was covered in shimmering scales. Its aura was undetectable, but it was giving off extremely formidable time law power fluctuations.

A hint of remorse appeared in Feng Qingyuan's eyes at the sight of the creature, and he took a glance at the stairwell out of the corner of his eyes as he planned his escape.

However, before he had a chance to do anything, the humanoid fish creature opened its mouth to reveal two rows of sharp teeth, then let loose a silent roar.

Immediately thereafter, its body disintegrated into a cloud of blue mist, which surged directly toward Feng Qingyuan, who instantly opened his oil paper umbrella for protection.

Wisps of crimson light emerged from the umbrella, encompassing his entire body to form a ball of crimson light, which sped away toward the stairwell.

However, the cloud of blue mist was able to keep up with him with ease, and it reached the stairwell in the blink of an eye before completely inundating the ball of red light.

A strangled cry of agony rang out from within the blue cloud, followed by the sound of something crashing to the ground, which was, in turn, followed by complete silence.

Shortly thereafter, the blue cloud reverted back into the humanoid fish creature, and it jumped back into the pond, paying no heed to the pair of immortal treasures in the process.

All that remained at the stairwell was a body that resembled a shriveled prune, and a tattered oil paper umbrella that was completely devoid of spiritual qi.

Han Li was astonished to see this.

Right at this moment, a purple figure emerged at the entrance of the third floor, and it was none other than Feng Lin.

Han Li hurriedly concealed himself once again upon seeing this, and Feng Lin slowly made her way into the hall, then took an indifferent glance at Feng Qingyuan's body, seemingly completely unsurprised by what she was seeing.

"Are you two hoping that I would also provoke that creature on my own? I'm afraid I'm not quite as foolish as Yuan Feng. Come out now, I know where you are," Feng Lin said as she glanced at the spots where Han Li and Ren Hao were hiding.

At this moment, there was a layer of purple light flashing over Feng Lin's eyes, and Han Li was very surprised to see that not only was she also cultivating the Infernal Devilish Eyes, her level of mastery in the ocular technique was superior even to his.

Furthermore, her disposition had changed drastically. Gone was her former gentle and seductive demeanor, and in its place was the cold and regal aura of a detached queen.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li emerged from his hiding spot, and Ren Hao also followed suit.

"That was not our intention at all, Fellow Daoist Feng. That Yuan Feng was nothing more than a reckless fool who's unworthy of traveling with us. In contrast, I hold a great deal of admiration for you and Fellow Daoist Li," Ren Hao said with a smile.

Han Li took an expressionless glance at Ren Hao and didn't say anything.

"Speak up! The treasures are right in front of us, so how about we join forces to kill that thing? As for who gets the treasures, that'll be decided by our abilities," Feng Lin harrumphed coldly.

"I'm fine with that. That fish thing has some tricks up its sleeve, but it's definitely no match for all three of us," Ren Hao agreed with a nod, while Han Li continued to remain silent.

"Do you not agree to this proposal, or do you have a better way to proceed, Fellow Daoist Li?" Feng Lin asked as she turned to Han Li.

"I have no objections with joining forces, but before that, would the two of you be able to enlighten me on exactly what that creature is? I'm afraid I'm not very knowledgeable in such matters," Han Li said.

The humanoid fish creature was completely different from the average cultivator in that it seemed to be some type of being formed by spiritual power.

"I'm afraid I don't have an answer to that," Feng Lin said with a shake of her head, while Ren Hao also shook his head, expressing the same sentiment.

Han Li was a little disappointed to hear this.

With the plan established, Han Li's trio briefly discussed some strategy, then collectively darted toward the blue pond from three different directions.

Ren Hao was the fastest of the three, reaching the pond in a flash before reaching out to make a grabbing motion with one hand.

A blue beastly claw the size of house instantly appeared above the pond, and the claw was brimming with immense power as it made a grab for the blue shield in the pond.

The blue fish creature emerged from the pond once again, and it raised a hand to summon a blue staff, which struck the beastly claw with a resounding thump.

The beastly claw was instantly destroyed upon contact, but Ren Hao didn't appear all that surprised to see this as he quickly made a hand seal.

The giant blue sword behind him instantly rose up into the sky as a streak of blue light at his behest, and it swelled drastically to over a thousand feet in size before crashing down upon the blue fish creature.

The sound of turbulent waves rang out in the nearby space, and the air became incredibly heavy.

Meanwhile, Feng Lin had also sprung into action, raising a hand to release a burst of black light, which transformed into a giant black gate.

The gate was over a hundred feet tall and twenty to thirty feet wide, and it seemed to be covered in dried blood.

There was a pair of dark purple rings on the gate, and a pair of fearsome devilish deities were engraved onto its surface.

Boundless devilish qi was surging out of the giant gate, and Feng Lin chanted an incantation before opening her mouth to release a ball of blood essence that fused into the gate.

The eyes of the devilish deities engraved onto the gate instantly began to glow red, and they opened their mouths in unison to release two bursts of crimson light, which transformed into a pair of large crimson hands that grabbed onto the purple rings before wrenching the gate open.

The sound of ghostly howls instantly rang out from beyond the gate, and a thick pillar of black light erupted out from within, hurtling directly toward the blue fish creature.

The black light churned as it took on the form of a series of human and beastly faces, all of which were twisted in agony and howling in torment.

Meanwhile, Han Li had also arrived at the pond, and he was instantly struck by a sense of discomfort in the face of the pillar of black light, forcing him to channel his Spirit Refinement Technique to clear his own mind.

He took a brief glance at Feng Lin, then swept a sleeve through the air to release three small, azure swords, all of which instantly swelled drastically in size as thick arcs of golden lightning emerged over them.

Chapter 663: Joining Forces

Han Li began to chant an incantation while sweeping a sleeve through the air, and the three giant azure swords hurtled directly toward the humanoid fish creature with golden lightning crackling all around them.

In the face of all of the oncoming attacks, a fierce look appeared on the creature's face as it swept its staff through the air, unleashing countless blue staff projections around itself, forming a light barrier to withstand the assault.

It was unclear whether Han Li's trio was actually going all out, but in the face of these relentless waves of attacks, even the average early-High Zenith cultivator would've already been overwhelmed.

A string of earth-shattering explosions rang out, and the barrier of staff projections was rapidly whittled down before collapsing completely.

The staff in the humanoid fish creature's hand was also shattered, but in the next instant, an antiquated blue fishing rod appeared in its grasp, with an extremely thin and fragile-looking blue line attached to it.

The creature swung the rod through the air, and the line immediately began to spin rapidly around it, conjuring up waves of blue light in its wake.

The space around the creature began to warp, forming a series of rapidly revolving blue vortexes, and the three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords came crashing down upon the vortexes to release a vast eruption of golden lightning, but the lightning was instantly devoured upon contact.

As for the vortexes, they merely shuddered slightly before returning to a stable state.

Han Li felt as if his three swords had struck a vast sea, and the tremendous power that they possessed was completely devoured by the boundless seawater, thereby completely nullifying them.

Almost at the exact same time, the giant blue sword summoned by Ren Hao also struck the blue vortexes with tremendous force, only to also be completely nullified.

Meanwhile, the pillar of black light that had erupted out of the black gate had also been withstood by the blue vortexes, but Feng Lin seemed to have already anticipated that this would happen, and she quickly made a hand seal, upon which a series of silver spirit patterns appeared on the giant black gate.

Immediately thereafter, countless silver runes erupted out of the gate before fusing into the pillar of black light, causing it to turn semi-transparent.

A dull thump rang out, and with some difficulty, the pillar of black light was able to pierce through the blue vortexes before inundating the humanoid fish creature.

A pained look immediately appeared on the creature's face, and its movements also appeared to have been severely inhibited.

Feng Lin made another hand seal, and a giant figure with devilish qi swirling around its body abruptly sprang out of the pillar of black light.

The devilish creature was around a hundred feet tall and extremely menacing in appearance, with a pair of curved horns protruding out of its head of crimson hair. Its hands and feet were covered in scales, and it was holding a black steel trident.

Furthermore, it was giving off an incredibly fearsome aura that instantly filled the entire hall, and even Ren Hao and Han Li couldn't help but shudder slightly at the sound of its sinister cackling.

All of a sudden, Mo Guang's alarmed voice rang out in his mind.

"This is one of the thirteen devilish kings among our Extrarealm Heavenly Devil Race, the Vyasa King! Be on your guard, Fellow Daoist Han. The Vyasa King is different from normal Extrarealm Heavenly Devils as it doesn't specialize in using inner demons and illusions to harm others. Instead, it can directly harm the soul of its target, thereby making it very difficult to deal with."

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, Feng Lin let loose a loud cry, and a burst of radiant black light erupted out of the trident in the Vyasa King's hands as it was thrust into the humanoid fish creature's body.

A dull thump rang out as the creature exploded into a cloud of blue mist, and an elated look appeared in Feng Lin's eyes as a burst of black qi erupted out of the pillar of black light, then reached out for the pair of treasures in the pond like a giant black hand.

An urgent look appeared in Ren Hao's eyes upon seeing this, but with the blue vortexes standing in his way, all he could do was watch.

In contrast, Han Li merely looked on without doing anything.

Right as the pair of treasures was about to be swept up by the burst of black qi, the cloud of blue mist suddenly converged to reform the humanoid fish creature, and it appeared to be completely unharmed.

As soon as it reappeared, the creature swung its fishing rod through the air, and the burst of black qi instantly exploded.

"Impossible!" Feng Lin exclaimed in an incredulous voice.

This Vyasa Gate was her bonded immortal treasure, and it had taken her an immeasurable amount of time and effort to refine it in accordance with an ancient tool refinement manual that she had obtained from a set of ruins in the Devil Realm.

For this immortal treasure, she had spent virtually all of her savings, but given the treasure's immense power, it was a decision that she didn't regret.

Just that pillar of Vyasa Devilish Light alone would've been enough to harm the soul of a cultivator of same cultivation base as herself, and the Vyasa King projection could stand toe to toe against even a High Zenith cultivator, yet somehow, the humanoid fish creature was completely unscathed after being struck by both!

Right at this moment, the creature swung its arm through the air again, and the blue fishing line swept through the air before intertwining to form a blue net, which encompassed the Vyasa Gate.

Feng Lin's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and she hurriedly made a rapid string of hand seals.

The Vyasa Gate began to glow with radiant black light as it trembled violently in an attempt to free itself from the net, but the net only continued to constrict tighter while pulling the Vasya Gate quickly toward the pond like a floundering fish.

At the same time, two more blue lines shot out of the fishing rod, springing toward Han Li's three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and Ren Hao's blue sword.

Having witnessed the power of the fishing line, Han Li immediately sprang into action, and the three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords darted back in retreat amid a flash of golden lightning to evade the fishing lines.

Ren Hao also hurriedly summoned his blue sword back to himself, and the two of them exchanged an astonished glance with one another.

The fact that the humanoid fish creature was able to gain the upper hand while facing all three of them at once was nothing short of extraordinary.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he considered whether he should use his time law powers. Otherwise, defeating this creature seemed next to impossible.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out from Feng Lin's direction, and a wave of black light erupted out of her body, then expanded rapidly in all directions to form a black spirit domain that instantly encompassed the entire hall.

Countless black devilish shadows were flashing within the spirit domain, letting loose harrowing howls of agony.

As soon as the black spirit domain emerged, it seemed to resonate with the Vyasa Gate, and the black light radiating from the latter brightened significantly, while the pair of devilish deities engraved upon it also seemed to have sprung to life, letting loose a collective thunderous roar.

An incredibly violent burst of power erupted out of the Vyasa Gate, causing the nearby space to tremble violently, and the gate shuddered to a halt.

Enshrouded within the black spirit domain, the blue vortexes around the humanoid fish creature dimmed significantly, and Ren Hao's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this as he made a hand seal.

Bright blue light erupted out of his body, then spread outward to form another spirit domain.

Countless blue waves were churning and rumbling incessantly within the spirit domain, and the blue vortexes around the humanoid fish creature dimmed even further.

"Fellow Daoist Li!" Ren Hao yelled as he turned to Han Li, and it was clear what he wanted.

Han Li was rather hesitant to oblige, but in the end, he chose to comply, unleashing his own time spirit domain.

Both Ren Hao and Feng Lin were astonished upon sensing the time law power fluctuations within Han Li's spirit domain.

All of the laws of the Great Dao contained the profound secrets of the world, so mastering any single one of them was exceedingly difficult, and this was especially the case for the three paramount laws, one of which was the laws of time.

Han Li was but a Golden Immortal just like them, yet not only was he cultivating the laws of time, it was clear from his spirit domain that he had reached quite a high level of mastery in the laws of time, so how could they not be astonished?

Encompassed within Han Li's time spirit domain, the humanoid fish creature was rooted to the spot, and at this point, the blue vortexes around it could barely even be seen at all.

Right at this moment, a fierce look appeared in Han Li's eyes, and nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew out of his sleeve in rapid succession, then collectively swelled drastically in size.

In the next instant, all nine swords came crashing down upon the blue vortexes at his behest.

Ren Hao immediately snapped back to his senses, letting loose a thunderous roar as the giant blue sword beside him shot forth through the air.

At the same time, he began to chant an incantation, and all of the blue wave projections within his spirit domain surged into the blue sword.

As a result, the blue light radiating from the sword brightened even further, and it abruptly vanished into thin air, only to reappear above the blue vortexes just an instant later. At this point, it had already swelled to several thousand feet in size, and it came crashing down right behind Han Li's nine swords.

Even though Feng Lin's bonded immortal treasure was still trapped, she also gritted her teeth and swept a sleeve through the air to release a fist-zied black seal with a black tiger projection around it.

She then began to chant an incantation as she thrust a palm toward the black seal, and a thunderous tiger's roar instantly rang out as the black tiger projection opened its mouth up wide, causing all of the black shadows within her spirit domain to surge into the black seal.

As a result, the seal swelled rapidly in size, reaching the size of a house in the blink of an eye, and it was radiating dazzling black light as it came crashing down upon the blue vortexes.

Chapter 664: Treachery

A hint of unease finally appeared on the humanoid fish being's face, and it attempted to swing its blue fishing rod through the air, but its movements were extremely slow and sluggish in Han Li's time spirit domain, so it was unable to react before the oncoming attacks struck the blue vortexes around it.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as radiant light of different colors erupted into the heavens, presenting a blinding sight.

The blue vortexes trembled violently, and a series of cracks appeared over them. The cracks quickly spread, following which the vortexes collapsed to reveal the humanoid fish being behind them.

"Die!" Feng Lin yelled as she thrust her palms forward, and the black light radiating from the black seal brightened even further as it hurtled directly toward the creature.

Ren Hao also let loose a low roar before swinging an arm through the air, sending the giant blue sword crashing down upon the creature.

A hint of panic finally appeared on the humanoid fish creature's face, and it opened its mouth to release a cloud of dense blue mist, which drifted toward the black seal and the blue sword while the creature sprang back toward the pond.

At the same time, blue light flashed erratically over its body, releasing violent time law power fluctuations, and it was quickly recovering its speed and agility.

"You're not getting away!" Han Li yelled as he flipped a hand over to summon the small golden lock, then opened his mouth to release a burst of golden light into it.

The lock instantly lit up with dazzling golden radiance, transforming into a ball of golden light that vanished into the time spirit domain in a flash.

In the next instant, a giant golden lock appeared beside the humanoid fish creature amid a flash of golden light, and it locked itself around one of the creature's arms.

Immediately thereafter, a giant rune emerged from the lock before encompassing the creature's entire body.

Thanks to the support provided by Han Li's time spirit domain, the rune released by the golden lock was several times larger than before, and not only was it able to trap the humanoid fish creature, most of the blue mist around the creature was also encompassed within it.

Both the humanoid fish creature and the cloud of blue mist were instantly immobilized, and in the next instant, the black seal and the blue sword came crashing down upon the creature's body in unison.

A dull thump rang out as the creature's body exploded into a burst of blue liquid that splattered in all directions.

Much of the blue liquid splattered onto the immortal treasures being wielded by Han Li's trio, and a sizzling sound instantly rang out as the spiritual light on the surfaces of the three immortal treasures flashed erratically, then began to rapidly dim, as if they were being subjected to severe corrosion.

Ren Hao hurriedly withdrew his blue sword to avoid further damage, but right at this moment, Han Li and Feng Lin shot right past him, flying toward the blue pond without any regard for their respective immortal treasures.

Ren Hao also sprang into action upon seeing this, letting loose a loud roar as he shot forward as quickly as he could, but ultimately, he was too slow to react, and at this point, Han Li and Feng Lin had already arrived above the pond.

Feng Lin swept a hand through the air, releasing a burst of black light to envelop the blue flute, while Han Li released a burst of azure light, which transformed into a large azure hand that grabbed onto the blue shield.

The shield was slightly cool and soft to the touch, but was also quite resilient and sturdy.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes, and he was just about to stow the shield away when he noticed something out of the corner of his eye.

The space beside him was rippling slightly, and immediately thereafter, a crimson bead appeared out of thin air.

Han Li's expression changed drastically as bright golden light erupted out of his body, but before he had a chance to do anything else, an earth-shattering boom rang out as the crimson bead exploded into a crimson sun that was several hundred feet in size, completely inundating his body.

Bursts of white flames emerged within the crimson sun, and they were giving off incredibly fearsome heat, burning a series of holes into the nearby space.

The time spirit domain that encompassed the entire hall instantly vanished, reverting the flow of time in the area back to normal.

A burst of devastating shockwaves spread through the air in all directions, forming ferocious gusts of wind, and the entire hall trembled violently, but managed to remain standing.

The hall had to have been constructed out of some type of exceptionally sturdy material, considering it had survived everything that had transpired up to this point.

A ball of blue light tumbled through the air, and it was none other than the blue shield.

Ren Hao rushed over to the shield in a flash, then grabbed onto it with an ecstatic expression.

"What the hell are you doing?!" Feng Lin yelled in a cold voice as she darted away to avoid being caught up in the crimson sun.

At the same time, the black seal and the Vyasa Gate shot back through the air before circling around above her head.

With the humanoid fish creature slain, the threads of blue light that were trapping hte Vyasa Gate had vanished.

"What am I doing? I'm claiming this treasure, of course!" Ren Hao chuckled coldly as he opened his mouth to release a ball of blue light, which carried the blue shield into his body.

"That was a Nine Destructions Flame Bead just now! I've heard that it's capable of killing even High Zenith cultivators. Looks like I underestimated you," Feng Lin said in a cold voice as she took a wary glance at the raging crimson sun.

Having been struck by such a powerful weapon, Han Li was most likely already dead.

"Of course I had to have some trump cards up my sleeve for this foray into the True Mantra Sect ruins. I'm sure you also have similar treasures in your possession, you're simply saving them for another time," Ren Hao chuckled.

"We agreed to join forces against that creature, then let our abilities decide who gets to claim the two treasures in the pond, yet you've betrayed our agreement and attacked your own ally! As expected, the Robe Change Order is filled with treacherous scum!" Feng Lin spat in a cold voice.

"This is how things should be. I don't feel safe traveling with someone capable of wielding time law powers, and only by killing him can I ensure that you and I won't be under threat from him, wouldn't you agree? Besides, he deserved what he got. If he had been more powerful than me, then he would've been well within his rights to kill me instead," Ren Hao scoffed with a disdainful expression.

Right at this moment, a cold voice rang out from within the crimson sun.

"Is that right? In that case, I'll take you up on that offer."

Ren Hao and Feng Lin's expressions changed drastically upon hearing this, with the former displaying a particularly strong reaction.

Right at this moment, Han Li emerged from the crimson sun completely unscathed, and even his robes hadn't been damaged at all.

His Mantra Treasured Axis was slowly revolving behind him, and the entire area within a radius of roughly ten feet around his body was enshrouded within a series of golden ripples.

In the face of the golden ripples, all of the surrounding fearsome white flames fell completely still, and only after he passed them by did the flames revert back to normal.

Ren Hao stared at Han Li with an astonished expression for a moment, then fled toward the stairwell as a blue shadow.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face as he instantly released his time spirit domain to encompass the entire hall, and Ren Hao's escape immediately slowed down to a crawl.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li appeared in front of him amid a flash of golden lightning, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The nine swords combined into a single giant azure sword at his behest, and he swung the sword down upon Ren Hao with tremendous power.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as Ren Hao shot back like a cannonball before crashing heavily into a wall, causing the entire hall to tremble violently.

He immediately scrambled to his feet with a horrified look on his face, having donned a suit of blue armor that consisted of countless blue scales.

He was also wearing a helmet that resembled a dragon's head, while his limbs were sheathed in protective armor that resembled dragon claws. It was as if he had suddenly transformed into a blue dragon.

The nostrils on the helmet were dilating and contracting incessantly as if they were breathing, and the entire suit of armor was giving off an incredibly formidable draconic aura.

However, there was currently a large gash on the shoulder of the suit of armor, clearly having just been inflicted by Han Li's sword strike.

"That's the Dragon Battle Armor of the Black Soil Immortal Region's Holy Dragon Palace!" Feng Lin exclaimed at the sight of the suit of blue armor, and a hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Upon arriving in the Black Soil Immortal Region, he had been reading extensively to learn as much as he could about the immortal region, and during the process, he was able to accumulate a great deal of knowledge pertaining to all of the major sects in the immortal region.

The Holy Dragon Palace was one such sect, and it was founded by a formidable cultivator who carried a true dragon bloodline. Hence, the dragon was a symbol of reverence for the sect, which ranked among the top five sects of the Black Soil Immortal Region.

Furthermore, the Holy Dragon Palace excelled in refining all types of immortal treasures and armor, and in particular, the armor that it produced wasn't inferior even compared with the armor refined by the Hundred Creations Mountain.

During a conversation with Daoist Master Jingyang in which they had discussed matters related to tool refinement, Daoist Master Jingyang had mentioned this sect with a great deal of praise and respect.

As it turned out, the armor of the Holy Dragon Palace truly did live up to its resounding reputation, allowing Ren Hao to survive that all-out sword strike from Han Li.

"You think a mere suit of armor will be enough to save your life?" Han Li sneered, and instead of immediately pouncing at Ren Hao, he remained still on the spot as nine balls of light of different colors erupted out of his body, then took on the form of a series of true spirit projections.

In addition to Han Li's previous collection of true spirit bloodlines, he now also possessed the Nightmare Dragon bloodline, which he had obtained from Qu Ling.

After slaying Qu Ling, Han Li had taken her body, and while traversing through the primordial land, he had taken the time to refine Qu Ling's Nightmare Dragon bloodline and integrate it into his own body.

All of a sudden, all of the true spirit projections vanished into Han Li's body at his behest, and in the next instant, he transformed into a purplish-golden devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

With a flick of his wrist, nine time law threads shot forth before fusing into the giant azure sword in his grasp, and a row of golden runes instantly appeared on its surface.

The nearby world's origin qi shuddered, then converged to form countless specks of five-colored light that surged toward the giant sword from all directions, drastically enhancing its already formidable aura.

Chapter 665: Pleasant Surprise

All of the color was drained from Ren Hao's face at the sight of Han Li's astonishing display of power, and he hurriedly fled the scene as a blue shadow.

At the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air to release seven or eight glowing immortal treasures, filling the entire hall before hurtling toward the devilish deity from all directions, ensuring that there was no way for Han Li could get to him through the immortal treasures.

However, Han Li was completely unconcerned as he swept an arm through the air, releasing a vast expanse of green light that swept up all of the immortal treasure.

The spiritual light emanating from the immortal treasures instantly faded, and all that remained were the immortal treasures themselves, suspended in mid-air within the green light like fish caught in a net.

With another sweep of Han Li's arm, all of the immortal treasures vanished along with the green light, and all of this had taken place in an instant.

An incredulous look appeared on Ren Hao's face upon seeing this.

After stowing the immortal treasures away, Han Li took a step forward, instantly vanishing from the spot.

In the next instant, he appeared right in Ren Hao's path, blocking his path of escape as he swung down his giant azure sword.

Enshrouded within the time spirit domain, Ren Hao was far slower than Han Li, and there was no way for him to escape.

"Curse you!" Ren Hao roared in a desperate voice as a hint of despair surfaced in his eyes, and he lashed out with his giant blue sword.

The two swords clashed, and the azure sword was able to slice its counterpart into two with ease, then continued onward without pause to strike Ren Hao with immense power.

Ren Hao's eyes opened up wide as he opened his mouth to release a burst of blood essence into his suit of armor, and at the same time, he injected all of the immortal spiritual power in his body into his armor as well.

The suit of armor instantly began to glow radiantly, and a blue film of light similar to Han Li's True Extreme Film emerged to oppose the azure sword.

However, the giant azure sword possessed unmatched power, and it was able to quickly slice through the blue membrane of light before striking the suit of armor, where it drew to a halt for a split second before slicing into the armor as well.

"No! You're going to regret this!" Ren Hao howled in a despairing voice as his body exploded into countless scraps of flesh and blood.

The tremendous sword qi of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had infiltrated his body and detonated it from the inside.

On top of that, his nascent soul had also been completely destroyed by the sword qi, while the suit of blue armor had exploded into countless pieces as well.

Han Li made a beckoning motion with one hand, plucking out a shimmering blue storage ring from Ren Hao's remains, then reverted back to his human form in the blink of an eye, while the giant azure sword also split back up into nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords before vanishing into his body.

A hint of wariness emerged in Feng Lin's eyes as she gazed upon Han Li, but Han Li didn't even bother to look at her as he turned his gaze to the body of the large-headed child instead.

He didn't have to expend much of his energy in killing Ren Hao, but senseless battle was still something that he wanted to avoid, so he had no intention of fighting over the flute with Feng Lin, and his attention was instead turned to the body floating in the pond.

He was aware of who this child was, so even during his battles against the humanoid fish creature and Ren Hao, he had been keeping an eye on the body this entire time, but he didn't notice anything amiss during his observation.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li reached out to make a grabbing motion, and a burst of azure light surged out of his sleeve, gently enveloping the child's body before slowly dragging it out of the pond.

All of a sudden, the body accelerated without any warning, arriving before Han Li in an instant. Its large head was almost in direct contact with Han Li's forehead, while the tip of its nose was on the verge of reaching Han Li's chin.

Under normal circumstances, Han Li would've been able to react in a timely fashion, but for some reason, the body's movements were extremely strange and also seemed to be imbued with some type of time law powers, catching him completely off guard.

Immediately thereafter, the body's eyelids shuddered slightly before its eyes sprang open, and it observed Han Li momentarily through a pair of blue eyes, then abruptly opened its mouth to release a ball of blue light toward him.

The ball of blue light struck him on the glabella, and he felt as if a thunderclap had exploded in his consciousness, causing his ears to ring incessantly.

Before he had a chance to inspect his own internal condition, the body uttered the phrase "kill Qi Mozi", following which its eyes and mouth fell shut again.

Immediately thereafter, countless thin cracks that were glowing with blue light emerged over the body, and it began to shatter like a piece of porcelain before disintegrating into a cloud of blue smoke that dissipated into nothingness in an instant.

Han Li shuddered as he snapped back to his senses, and he felt as if he had just awoken from a dream.

Meanwhile, Feng Lin was standing several thousand feet away, looking on with a perplexed expression. From her perspective, Han Li seemed to have experienced a moment of disorientation after bending down, and she had no idea what had happened after that.

However, when she turned to look into the pond again, she was surprised to discover that the body of the large-headed child had vanished.

Right at this moment, the sound of splashing rang out from within the pond, and Feng Lin noticed that a vortex that was around half a foot wide had taken shape within it.

The vortex swept up all of the blue liquid in the pond, sending it rapidly funneling downward, and the pond was almost completely emptied in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was right beside the pond, and he reacted very quickly, hurriedly making a grabbing motion to conjure up a large azure hand that scooped up a ball of blue water from the bottom of the pond.

However, that was all that he managed to scoop up before the remaining water in the pond was completely funneled away.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh as he flipped a hand over to produce a white jade vial, then deposited the blue water into it before stowing the vial away in his storage bracelet.

He then took a glance at the bottom of the pond to discover that there were thousands of fist-sized blue rocks embedded into its surface, and they were giving off abundant spiritual qi. They contained no law powers, but they were clearly some type of exceptional water-attribute material.

"There are still some water-attribute materials left in this place. How about we split them among ourselves and avoid further battle, Fellow Daoist Feng?" Han Li proposed as he turned to Feng Lin with a smile.

"That would be best," Feng Lin replied with a smile of her own.

With that, both of them sprang into action, collecting the water-attribute materials in the pond and the rest of the hall.

After that, the two of them conducted a thorough search through the three-story pagoda, and only after ensuring that there was nothing else of value to be taken did they exit the pagoda together.

"I'm planning to keep going down this path. Would you like to accompany me, Fellow Daoist Feng?" Han Li asked as he cast his gaze toward the area beyond the pagoda, which was enshrouded in mist.

"I'll pass. I'm planning to return the same way I came and go down one of the other paths," Feng Lin replied.

After witnessing Han Li's powers, she had become very apprehensive of him, so she naturally didn't dare to accompany him any longer.

Of course, this was precisely the response that Han Li wanted, so he made no effort to keep her.

"In that case, this is where we part ways. Take care, Fellow Daoist Feng."

Following Feng Lin's departure, Han Li directed his spiritual sense deep into his own consciousness to conduct a close inspection.

At this moment, all was calm and tranquil in his consciousness, but there was a ball of blue light hovering within it.

As soon as Han Li's spiritual sense made contact with the ball of blue light, it immediately transformed into a screen of blue light that was rippling incessantly, and there was a passage of text consisting of thousands of golden characters on the screen.

Han Li discovered that this was the full nine-part cultivation art of the Water Divination Time Arts, two more than what he had received from the Vast Flow Palace.

Enclosed after the cultivation art were some of the insights that the large-headed child had gleaned while cultivating the Water Divination Time Arts, and that by itself was over three thousand characters in length.

After Han Li memorized everything, the screen of blue light faded away along with the golden characters inscribed upon it.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes as a hint of elation flashed through them, but given his current circumstances, this was naturally not the right time to be studying the cultivation art.

With that in mind, he continued to make his way deeper down the path.

Beyond the pagoda was a sparse forest that was also filled with the same mist that impeded both visibility and spiritual sense, so Han Li had no choice but to progress slowly through the area.

Thankfully, the trip proved to be quite uneventful, and all Han Li encountered along the way were some bodies belonging to True Mantra Sect and Heavenly Court cultivators.

After traveling for around six hours, the surrounding vegetation became even sparser, but the mist up ahead had become even denser.

Upon emerging from the forest, Han Li discovered that there was a giant lotus pond that was over ten thousand feet in radius up ahead, and the water in the pond resembled rippling green jade.

White mist was surging incessantly over the pond, and there were numerous pink and white lotus flowers littered over its surface, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

Unfortunately, Han Li was in no mood for sightseeing, and he was just about to pass over the pond when he suddenly spotted something and drew to a halt.

Interesting... No wonder the world's origin qi is so abundant here.

Chapter 666: Translucent Lotus Flower

Han Li hovered in mid-air as he carefully observed the pond below for a moment, and he discovered that the lotus flowers on the pond appeared to be distributed in a completely haphazard fashion, but in reality, they were arranged into a large array.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he descended onto the pond, then looked down with his Infernal Devilish Eye, which allowed him to see the distribution of lotus flowers over the pond with even greater clarity.

A faint smile appeared on his face as he swept a hand through the air, releasing a burst of silver flames that transformed into a silver fire raven, which flew in a circle around the pond, and all of the lotus pads in the pond were instantly set alight.

Within mere moments, all of the lotus pads in the pond had been incinerated into ashes by the Essence Fire Raven, and the pond had become completely barren and lifeless.

Even so the dense white mist over the pond refused to dissipate, and the lotus flowers also still remained.

This seemed to have come as no surprise to Han Li, and he made a beckoning motion to summon the Essence Fire Raven back to himself.

Upon flying back to Han Li, the fire raven transformed into a tiny silver figure that skipped its way onto his shoulder.

The silver figure then began to look around with a perplexed expression, wondering why Han Li had instructed it to burn down all of the lotus flowers in the pond, but not finish the job.

If it had been granted just a little more time, it would've reduced all of the lotus flowers to ashes as well.

All of a sudden, specks of green light began to appear around the lotus flowers, following which some green buds began to sprout among them, and the surrounding mist also began to swirl violently.

Shortly thereafter, the buds began to unfurl at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, and before long, the entire pond was filled with lotus pads once again.

This was not the result of some illusion. Instead, there was simply such an immense abundance of spiritual qi in the pond that these lotus pads were able to almost instantly regrow, albeit with the assistance of an array.

The silver figure's eyes widened with shock upon seeing this, and silver flames rose up all over its body as it prepared to swoop down to incinerate the lotus pads once again.

However, Han Li raised a hand to pat it on the head, indicating for it to stay put, and the flames around its body faded, following which it flew back up Han Li's sleeve.

At this point, the layout of the pond had already become clear to him, and he flew several thousand feet horizontally, arriving above one of the pink lotus flowers before reaching down toward it.

He then made a grabbing motion, and a large azure hand appeared, then grabbed onto the pink lotus flower before uprooting it.

Its roots were glowing blue, and there was an incredibly beautiful translucent blue lotus flower hanging from them.

As soon as this blue lotus flower emerged from the water, all of the other pink lotus flowers in the pond instantly began to wilt.

However, all of the lotus pads in the pond were still standing instead of also withering away, but they had lost their previous green luster, as if they had also been robbed of their vitality.

At the same time, the dense white mist over the pond slowly began to dissipate bit by bit.

Han Li paid no heed to the changes taking place in the pond as he observed the translucent blue lotus flower in his hand, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he sensed the potent water law power fluctuations emanating from it.

All of a sudden, his right index and middle fingers lit up, and a door of silver light emerged before him.

He stepped through the door into the Flower Branch domain, arriving at the golden lotus pond outside the bamboo building before planting the blue lotus flower and the pink lotus flower that it was connected to into the pond.

The blue lotus flower instantly took root where it was planted, and six pink lotus flowers quickly emerged within the pond, releasing wisps of faint mist.

At the same time, a faint breeze began to blow through the area, carrying the faint mist to all parts of the domain, creating an even greater abundance of spiritual qi in the entire area.

Mo Guang was cultivating on the second floor of the bamboo building, and his eyes instantly sprang open as he sensed this sudden change.

However, he only briefly observed the changes that had taken place in the domain, then took a glance in Han Li's direction before closing his eyes again.

Over at the spirit medicine garden, Daoist Xie was standing by the railing of a recently constructed bamboo building, looking on with a surprised expression.

Han Li stood in mid-air with a faint smile on his face and his hands clasped behind his back, allowing his robes to flap in the breeze.

After ensuring that nothing was going amiss, he gave a pleased nod.

With this blue lotus flower working in conjunction with the existing array and the golden lotus flowers, the circulation of spiritual qi in the domain had become far more fluid, thereby severely reducing the rate of energy expenditure from the Immortal Origin Stones.

With no more work left to be done, Han Li emerged from the Flower Branch doman, then flew over the lotus pond outside to continue onward.

......

Meanwhile, in another set of ruins somewhere in the True Mantra Sect.

The ruins were filled with collapsed buildings, walls, and pillars, and littered throughout the wreckage were countless bodies belonging to True Mantra Sect and Heavenly Court cultivators. Some of them clearly possessed very advanced cultivation bases at their time of death, as evidenced by the fact that their skeletons were still glowing faintly, even though it had already been countless years since they perished.

At the center of the set of ruins was a relatively well preserved giant palace, but it was rather strange in appearance, looking much like a crimson flame that was completely still. Above the entrance of the palace hung a giant plaque that read "Flowing Fire Palace".

Even now, there were still waves of heat slowly surging forth from the walls of the palace, causing the nearby air to shimmer and warp, and it was unclear whether this was because the palace had been constructed out of some type of special material, or if there were things like pill refinement cauldrons inside it.

At this moment, a string of resounding booms were ringing out incessantly in front of the entrance of the palace.

There were two spirit domains overlapping one another, one purple and one yellow, and inside the two spirit domains was a seductive woman in a purple palace dress locked in battle against an hunch-backed elderly man with a sickly yellow complexion.

The woman was none other than Yan Ziyan, the city lord of Illusory Smoke City.

At this moment, there was a furious look in her eyes, and her brows were tightly furrowed, pushing the red mole on her glabella. She was holding a purple jade lute, and her fingers were quickly strumming over the lute's strings.

Beautiful maidens conjured up out of illusory smoke emerged one after another, and all of them were holding curved purple blades as they launched themselves at the hunch-backed elderly man, who was swaying back and forth on the plaza in front of the palace, evading the oncoming smoky maidens with ease.

His cultivation base was far superior to Yan Ziyan's, so there was no fear in his eyes, whatsoever. Instead, his eyes were filled with mockery, and he seemed to be thoroughly enjoying the experience of having so many beautiful women around him, even if they were only conjured up out of smoke.

His gaze was blatantly roaming over Yan Ziyan's chest and backside, and there was perverted smile on his face as he chuckled, "You and I stuck in the middle of nowhere in these ruins, all by ourselves, so why don't we engage in some more fun activities than senseless battle, City Lord Yan?"

"You recognize me?" Yan Ziyan asked in a grim voice.

"How could I not? You're the mistress of the vastly renowned Palace Master Fu. Unfortunately for you, Fu Yuanhai isn't around to save you in these ruins," the elderly man chuckled.

"You're nothing but a perverted coward! If you truly had a spine, then you'd discard your Robe Change Order disguise and show me your true appearance! I assure you that once we're out of these ruins, I'll call on Palace Master Fu, and the two of us will pay you a visit together!" Yan Ziyan spat through gritted teeth.

Despite what she was saying, she didn't dare to look down on her opponent. The elderly man's cultivation base was far superior to hers, and if it weren't for the fact that he was intentionally toying with his prey, there was no way that she would've been able to survive to this point completely unscathed.

"Fine. If that's what you want, then your wish is my command." the hunch-backed elderly man said with a smile, then grabbed onto his own collar from behind before wrenching it forward.

As a result, his robes and his skin were torn away, revealing a handsome man in a pristine white robe.

"How about now? Is this appearance of mine more appealing to you?"

Not only had his appearance completely changed, his demeanor and voice had also been drastically altered, and in the blink of an eye, he had become a completely different person.

Yan Ziyan could see that there were no longer any signs of disguise on his body, indicating that this really was his true appearance, and a sense of foreboding immediately welled up in her heart.

The fact that he was willing to reveal his true appearance to her indicated that he was going to make sure that she wasn't going to live to tell the tale of their encounter.

The white-robed young man licked his lips at the sight of Yan Ziyan's apprehensive expression, then burst into laughter as he said, "Rest assured, there's no way I could bring myself to kill a woman as beautiful as you. Instead, I'm going to cut off all of your limbs and deprive you of all of your senses, then add you to my collection."

A chill ran down Yan Ziyan's spine upon hearing this, and she grabbed tightly onto her lute, then suddenly pulled back its strings like bowstrings before releasing them in the white-robed young man's direction.

A loud twang rang out as a pillar of purple light erupted out of the lute, transforming into a giant purple bat that swooped directly toward him.

Within Yan Ziyan's purple spirit domain, the bat let loose a sharp screech, sending invisible soundwaves sweeping through the air.

Chapter 667: Fire Age Fireflies

In the face of this latest round of attacks, the white-robed young man merely smiled as he raised a hand, then released a string of incantation seals that vanished into the surrounding space.

In the next instant, a series of large disks of light appeared within his yellow spirit domain, and they were revolving incessantly to weaken the soundwave attacks unleashed by the purple bat, but layers of creases were still appearing on his white robe.

Shortly thereafter, the sound of tearing rang out, and countless tiny gashes appeared on his robes, while the disks of light began to disintegrate one after another.

At the same time, the palatial ruins beside and behind the white-robed young man were trembling incessantly in the wake of the soundwaves, and they quickly disintegrated into dust.

A hint of elation appeared in Yan Ziyan's eyes upon seeing this, and she hurriedly began chanting an incantation while rapidly strumming the strings of her lute.

A fierce look flashed through the purple bat's eyes, and it spread its wings before hurtling toward the white-haired young man as a streak of purple light.

A hint of anger flashed through the young man's eyes at the sight of his torn robes, and he yelled, "I gave you a chance, but seeing as you insist on making things difficult for yourself, I suppose it can't be helped!"

He flipped a hand over as he spoke to summon a giant metal fan that was around six feet in length. Circles of complex yellow runes were etched onto the fan, and they were giving off formidable earth law power fluctuations.

The metal fan spread open in front of him with a loud clang, revealing a creature with yellow fur etched onto its surface. The creature burst out of the fan as if it had sprung to life, then opened its cavernous mouth to release a ferocious tornado that was interspersed with yellow sand.

A burst of violent rumbling rang out as the tornado swept through the air, pulverizing the purple bat in its path.

All of a sudden, Yan Ziyan felt her own body become impossibly heavy, and she was unable to take evasive measures at all as she was sent flying by the yellow tornado, crashing through the gates of the Flowing Fire Palace behind her.

"Crap! I should've held back more. I really hope I didn't scar that pretty little face of hers," the white-robed young man cursed to himself as he hurriedly stowed away his metal fan before rushing before.

However, before he had even reached the entrance of the palace, he suddenly heard a buzzing sound that resembled the sound of countless beetles flapping their wings at once.

Immediately thereafter, Yan Ziyan's panicked voice rang out from within the palace.

"No! What are these things?!"

As soon as her voice trailed off, she shot out of the hall, but only managed to rise about a thousand feet up into the air before plummeting to the ground with a heavy thump.

The white-robed young man faltered slightly upon seeing this, but he then immediately drew a sharp breath as soon as he caught a clear glimpse of Yan Ziyan.

At this moment, her entire body was covered in tiny dark red insects with specks of red flames dancing over their bodies.

She was rolling on the ground in a frenzied panic with an agonized look on her face while moaning hoarsely, and there was a layer of faint golden mist around her. Wrinkles were beginning to appear on her youthful face at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, and her hair was also beginning to turn white.

Whatever those insects were, they seemed to be burning through her vitality!

Even though Golden Immortals were unable to avoid baleful decays, aside from that, they were theoretically immortal, so it was extraordinary that these insects were able to do this to her.

A grim look instantly appeared on the white-robed young man's face, and he was just about to flee the scene when a giant figure came crashing down from the heavens like a steel pagoda, following which a fiery red spirit domain instantly spread over the surrounding area.

The white-robed young man turned to discover an imposing foreign being with fiery red hair and the nose of a rhinoceros. There was a large golden ring hanging from each of his tapered ears, and a look of cold disdain on his face.

The man was none other than Chi Rong.

The white-robed young man was instantly plunged into the depths of despair upon sensing the late-High Zenith Stage aura emanating from Chi Rong's body.

"To think that a mere Golden Immortal would dare to try and claim Master's Fire Age Fireflies! Let's see how long it'll take to burn through your vitality!" Chi Rong harrumphed coldly.

What? Fire Age Fireflies actually exist?

The white-robed young man's entire body stiffened upon hearing this, and he recalled a rumor that had been circulating in the True Immortal Realm for a very long time.

It was said that Fire Age Fireflies were a type of spirit insect that was very similar in appearance to fireflies of the mortal world, but they possessed flames of time, which were imbued with time law powers, thereby allowing them to burn through the vitality of living beings. This vitality is then used as energy for them to reproduce, and anyplace that these insects pass through is generally left completely devoid of living beings.

However, their lifespans were extremely short, generally only living for around a month, and if they couldn't find any living beings to incinerate, then they wouldn't be able to reproduce. Hence, there hadn't been many sightings of them.

However, it was said that some cultivators who were adept at raising insects could use certain time-attribute treasures or special restrictions to preserve these insects and only release them when necessary.

It was clear that such a restriction had existed in the Flowing Fire Palace, and only after Yan Ziyan inadvertently broke the restriction were these insects freed.

With that in mind, a sheen of cold sweat surfaced on the white-robed young man's forehead, and he was contemplating how he was going to escape when he noticed the red-haired man staring intently at him.

His heart instantly jolted slightly upon seeing this, and he made a hand seal without any hesitation, upon which a yellow vortex appeared beneath him, swallowing up his body in the blink of an eye.

However, it was a few seconds later when the white-robed young man was forcibly ejected out of the earth several thousand feet away, having been plucked out of the ground by a giant fiery hand extending out of the surrounding crimson spirit domain.

"Did you think you could get away?" Chi Rong chuckled as he raised a hand before pressing it downward forcefully, and the large fiery hand emulated this gesture, forcing the white-robed young man into the ground.

Immediately thereafter, Chi Rong pulled a dark red flute out of the chest of his robes. The flute was covered in black spots, giving it the appearance of an old blowpipe.

As Chi Rong began to play the flute, an ancient melody rang out, and the sound of buzzing from the Flowing Fire Palace grew louder and louder as thousands upon thousands of Fire Age Fireflies were freed from the restriction, then converged upon the white-robed young man.

A blood-curdling howl instantly rang out, but Chi Rong paid no further heed to Yan Ziyan and the white-robed young man as he crossed the plaza to the other side.

A relatively intact statue of a foreign race being stood on the other side of the plaza.

The foreign being's hands and feet were as large as banana leaves, and their hair resembled flames. Their upper body was bared, and a series of strange patterns were etched onto their skin.

Chi Rong made his way over to the statue, then extended a deep bow as he said, "Master, please forgive me for coming here of my own accord to claim these Fire Age Fireflies. The intruders of our Flowing Fire Palace have already been dealt with."

......

Around half a month later.

An azure figure was flying through the air on a green jade flying carriage above a forest in the True Mantra Sect ruins. It was none other than Han Li, having adopted another disguise, and after passing through the lotus pond from before, he had only encountered some sporadic sets of ruins.

He wasn't met with any more danger, but nor had he found any more treasures.

On the flying carriage, he cast his gaze into the distance, and all of a sudden, his brows furrowed slightly, following which the carriage descended toward the ground at his behest.

Upon his landing, Han Li stowed the flying carriage away, then made his way down a small bluestone path in the forest, quickly arriving before a giant arched bridge.

The bridge was over three hundred feet wide and primarily constructed from wood and stone, consisting of a bluestone staircase and a flat carriage path, as well as a gray stone lion placed on either side of the bridge's entrance.

Han Li strode forward before raising a hand to stroke one of the stone lions, which was even taller than himself, and he was able to ascertain that they were nothing more than normal stone lions that were completely devoid of spiritual power fluctuations.

After a brief hesitation, he made his way onto the bridge, but right as he was about to reach the center of the bridge, he suddenly stopped in his tracks.

The bridge had been snapped here, and up ahead was a giant spatial rift that was tens of thousands of feet in length. The spatial rift was filled with nothing but darkness, and there were formidable spatial fluctuations constantly surging out of it.

It seemed that the other half of the bridge had been devoured by the spatial rift.

Aside from this giant spatial rift, there were also countless smaller rifts around it, and even though they hadn't completely blocked Han Li's path forward, he didn't dare to recklessly pass through them.

Han Li peered into the spatial rift, but couldn't see anything in it, and the longer he stared into it, the more an irrational fear of being devoured by the rift began to take root in his heart.

He withdrew his gaze before turning his attention to either side of the bridge, upon which he discovered that half of all of the trees and buildings within an area that spanned tens of thousands of feet had been erased.

What was left was either standing resiliently like this half-intact bridge, or had completely collapsed, presenting a very strange sight to behold.

Chapter 668: Spatial Storm

Looks like I won't be able to keep going forward...

With that in mind, Han Li began to make his way down from the bridge, but he had only just raised his foot when the bridge beneath him began to tremble.

He instantly swiveled around to discover bursts of fearsome spatial fluctuations surging out of the giant black rift behind him, and the area around it was slowly beginning to expand like a giant mouth aiming to swallow what remained of the arched bridge.

Han Li hurriedly darted forward before descending beside the stone lions, and by the time he turned around again, the commotion had subsided. The spatial rift had expanded slightly, but it seemed to have stabilized itself again.

Could it be that the True Mantra Sect ruins are still in a state of ongoing spatial disintegration?

If that were the case, then he would have to proceed with more caution.

Right at this moment, a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations suddenly erupted out of the ground beneath the stone lion beside him, immediately following which a black vortex that was over a hundred feet in radius emerged without any warning, and it was continuing to expand while releasing tremendous suction force.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his Mantra Treasured Axis as he attempted to flee the scene, but he was locked into place by a burst of formidable spatial power, rendering him unable to get away.

His expression instantly changed drastically as he hurriedly released his time spirit domain, and a layer of golden scales appeared over his body, as did the suit of dark green armor formed by his Xuanwu bloodline.

However, before he had a chance to summon his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, the burst of suction force became significantly more powerful, and he was sucked into the vortex along with the stone lion.

All of a sudden, Han Li felt the ground give way beneath his feet, and he found himself in a dim, black space.

The stone lion that had fallen into the spatial rift with Han Li was swept up by a whirlwind that enshrouded in murky gray light, and it was instantly reduced to dust.

Han Li knew that he had been sucked into a spatial rift, and he immediately began to carefully inspect his surroundings with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

At the same time, he flipped both hands over at once to summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd and a sword formed by nine combined Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The sound of howling wind was ringing out incessantly from all directions, and everywhere he looked, he could see a series of gray spatial vortexes and spatial rifts of different lengths, giving the surrounding area an extremely unstable appearance.

Hovering extremely far away in the distance were landmasses of different sizes, and they seemed to be enveloped within transparent bubbles as they hovered between all of the spatial rifts and vortexes.

Some of the landmasses were larger and appeared relatively more stable, while some of the smaller ones were disintegrating at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye under the compressive and tearing forces exerted by the surrounding spatial rifts.

Right at this moment, a deafening boom rang out in the distance, and Han Li hurriedly turned in that direction to discover an enormous gray current sweeping rapidly toward him.

The space in its wake was trembling incessantly, and the spatial fluctuations being released by the wave were so formidable that even the surrounding darkness was warping slightly. None of the nearby spatial rifts were able to hold themselves together, and they were all sucked into the wave.

That's a spatial storm!

Han Li couldn't help but curse his own luck. It was already extremely unfortunate that he had been inexplicably sucked into a spatial rift, and now, his woes were being compounded even further.

Even with his current physical constitution, he still wouldn't dare to face such formidable spatial power head-on.

Not daring to remain where he was any longer, he cast his gaze toward the nearest floating landmass, then channeled his Reversal True Axis as he sped toward it.

Due to the abundance of spatial rifts in the area, Han Li didn't dare to accelerate too much, and he could only move toward the landmass in an extremely wary fashion.

After flying for just over ten thousand feet, Han Li took a glance back at the spatial storm, and a grim look instantly appeared on his face.

The spatial storm had only been around a hundred thousand feet in size just a moment ago, yet since then, it had swelled to several times its original size. Even though it wasn't advancing directly toward Han Li, as it continued to expand, it was only going to exert more and more influence upon this already unstable space.

If he couldn't reach the landmass up ahead before the spatial storm reached him, then he would be sucked into the storm and pulverized.

If he were to die here, not only would his remains be completely destroyed, even his nascent soul would be eradicated as well.

I have to make a run for it!

Han Li gritted his teeth as the time spirit domain around him swelled to several times its original size, and he abruptly sped up significantly, racing through the air as a streak of golden light.

As the landmass drew closer and closer, Han Li was able to see the landmarks on it with increasing clarity, and he was even able to catch a whiff of the scent of spirit plants in the air.

Right as he was about to reach the edge of the continent, a resounding boom suddenly rang out, and the enormous spatial storm suddenly exploded as a ball of blinding white light appeared within it, which countless blades of gray light erupted forth in all directions.

These blades of gray light ranged from only around an inch in length to several thousand feet long, and they were imbued with immeasurable spatial power.

Han Li's expression darkened even further upon sensing this, but he had no time to turn around, and he could only continue to rush toward the landmass up ahead as quickly as he could.

Right at this moment, he felt a burst of violent spatial fluctuations behind him, and before he had a chance to do anything, several loud explosions rang out behind him as several blades of gray light struck his time spirit domain.

The spirit domain didn't even get a chance to exert its slowing effect before it was torn apart by the blades of gray light, and Han Li let loose a desperate roar as he sped toward the landmass with all his might.

A loud thump rang out as he crashed into an invisible, yet extremely sturdy spatial barrier, and he was sent flying back from the force of the collision.

At this point, it was already too late to make a second dash for the landmass as there was a blade of gray light that was around three feet in length hurtling toward him from behind.

In this dire situation, he had no time to think as he placed his Profound Heavenly Gourd behind himself while making a rapid string of hand seals with his other hand.

The gourd began to glow radiantly as a vortex appeared at its opening, and a faint thud rang out as the blade of gray light was sucked into the gourd.

A burst of tremendous force surged through the gourd, almost wrenching it out of Han Li's grasp, and he hurriedly tightened his grip around the gourd before darting toward the landmass again.

Right at this moment, he suddenly felt a sharp, burning pain in his hand.

He looked down to discover that the gourd had become red hot, resembling a piece of smelted metal, and it was also trembling incessantly, looking as if it could explode at any moment.

Han Li immediately stowed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords away upon seeing this, then thrust his palm firmly into the underside of the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

A faint thud rang out as the blade of gray light that had been sucked into the gourd erupted forth before hurtling toward the spatial barrier around the landmass, and a long and thin gash similar to a spatial rift was instantly sliced into the surface of the spatial barrier.

The gash was several dozen feet in length, but it was very unstable and looked as if it could disappear at any moment.

Han Li knew that this was his only opportunity, so he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to its limits, then shot through the gash at an astonishing speed.

In the next instant, he began plummeting toward the ground like an asteroid, crashing straight through a mountain and emerging on the other side.

From there, he hovered in mid-air as he looked up at the gash in the spatial barrier, which was slowly closing, and he heaved a long sigh of relief with more than a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

If he had reacted just a little slower, or he didn't have the Profound Heavenly Gourd in his possession, then he would've most likely been in a world of trouble.

It seemed that under the tranquil facade of the True Mantra Sect ruins was an extremely dangerous place, and he had been too complacent up to this point.

Moments later, he slowly drifted down onto the ground near a lush tree, then sat down onto a strange-looking rock.

He then raised the Profound Heavenly Gourd in his hand, which was still carrying some of its residual heat, but it was no longer as scorching hot as before. Furthermore, its red coloration was slowly fading as it gradually reverted back to its original green color.

After inspecting the gourd momentarily with his spiritual sense, he discovered the circulation of spiritual power within it had become a little chaotic, but aside from that, it was completely fine.

Hence, he stowed the gourd away, then promptly swallowed a pill before closing his eyes to meditate.

Around an hour later, his eyes sprang open, and at this point, his aura had settled down again.

After rising to his feet, he began to inspect his surroundings, upon which he discovered that there were many more strange rocks like the one that he had been sitting on in the surrounding forest, and they extended all the way into the forest.

What is this place? Is it still somewhere within the True Mantra Sect ruins?

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li began to make his way along the trail of strange rocks.

Chapter 669: Reliving an Old Vision

As soon as Han Li emerged from the forest, he immediately stepped into an open area.

He inspected his surroundings momentarily before continuing onward, and it didn't take long before he arrived at a rocky forest formed by all types of strange-looking rocks.

At the exact center of the rocky forest was a round stone platform that was around ten thousand feet in radius and roughly a thousand feet tall. It was connected to the mountain below it, and its surface was riddled with cracks and moss, indicating that it was a very old structure.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he felt like this platform was somewhat familiar.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he sprang up into the air before landing on the platform.

The entire platform was riddled with cracks that were filled with green vines, and the one remarkable thing about the structure was that it was giving off a hint of faint law power fluctuations.

Furthermore, there was a giant stone plaque that was around a thousand feet tall standing on the edge of the platform, and it was also crawling with moss and vines.

Only after Han Li drew close to the plaque did he discover that the words "Mantra Domain" were inscribed upon it in large golden characters beneath the masses of vines.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he turned around to inspect his surroundings once more, and a look of realization suddenly appeared on his face.

This was the exact same stone platform that he had witnessed Patriarch Miro deliver his lecture from on the translucent wall of light.

At the time, he had only heard eight and a half sentences of Patriarch Miro's profound lecture, and that had allowed him to open up eight immortal acupoints in succession.

Unfortunately, he was never able to conjure up that same vision again since then.

However, he had now arrived at the site of the lecture in person, seemingly completely by chance, or perhaps fate had guided him here.

All of a sudden, Han Li made a hand seal, and his Mantra Treasured Axis emerged behind him, then began to revolve on the spot.

In the next instant, he rose up into the sky and stood in mid-air.

The wall of translucent light had restricted his field of view, preventing him from seeing the entirety of the stone platform, but he was able to see everything from this vantage point.

He made a hand seal as he chanted an incantation, and all of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis lit up in unison.

The Eye of Truth at the center of the axis also sprang open, and a beam of golden light erupted out of the giant eyeball before shining down upon the stone platform.

Basked within the golden light, the stone platform also began to glow faintly with a golden hue, and a series of familiar figures began to take shape.

I knew it!

He turned his gaze to the yellow-robed tree being by the name of Mu Yan, then to the large-headed child that he had seen earlier in the Water Divination Palace. One after another, his gaze roamed over the people seated on the stone platform before finally settling on the rotund monk that was Patriarch Miro.

He wore a benevolent expression as he sat in a casual manner with his legs crossed, gently massaging a string of green jade Buddhist prayer beads as he delivered his lecture.

Whenever he opened his mouth, a string of five-colored runes would emerge from within, then rise up into the sky as a burst of five-colored light to resonate with heaven and earth and conjure up all types of phenomena.

Even though this was already Han Li's second time witnessing this scene, he was still stunned by what he saw.

However, in contrast with last time, everything that was unfolding was merely a projection that was being restored by the Eye of Truth, and it wasn't happening in real time. Hence, he wasn't able to glean the same profound insights as before.

He watched as all types of phenomena emerged one after another, and as he did so, a hint of befuddlement welled up in his heart.

Even with his unfathomable powers, Patriarch Miro was still unable to prevent his own death, nor the destruction of the True Mantra Sect. In that case, just how powerful was the Time Dao Ancestor that had laid waste to the True Mantra Sect?

Moments later, Mu Yan raised a question, and Patriarch Miro offered a response, to which all five of his disciples reacted with enlightenment and gratitude.

Patriarch Miro continued his lecture, but all of a sudden, he stopped as a surprised look appeared on his face, and he turned his gaze to a certain direction.

Han Li turned his gaze in that direction, but didn't see anything there.

Right as he was wondering what Patriarch Miro had just reacted to, his five disciples also snapped back to their senses before turning to the same direction, and Mu Yan sprang to his feet as he said something in a loud, questioning voice with an angry look on his face.

Only then did Han Li realize that this was the scene where he had been caught eavesdropping on Patriarch Miro's lecture.

A wry smile appeared on his face as he turned his gaze back to Patriarch Miro, and he spotted a fat rat seated on the cushion that Mu Yan had just gotten up from. It was standing upright on its hindlegs, and it was also looking in the same direction as everyone else.

It immediately occurred to Han Li that this rat was identical to the giant green rat that he had seen in that abyss in the primordial land, except this one was far smaller.

Right at this moment, Mu Yan returned to his seat, flicking the fat rat on the head to send it tumbling several thousand feet away.

As soon as the rat got up, it immediately rushed over to Patriarch Miro's side, where it sat down right beside him with its legs crossed, much like a human would.

Patriarch Miro took a glance down at the rat and made no attempt to chase it away as he continued his lecture.

Mu Yan also made no further effort to chase the rate away upon seeing this.

Even though Han Li wasn't able to benefit from this vision as he did last time, he still observed carefully as Patriarch Miro answered his disciples' questions, memorizing all of the gestures made by Patriarch Miro and his disciples.

Some time later, as Patriarch Miro's lecture drew to a close, a warm smile appeared on his face, and his gaze roamed over his disciples one after another as he waved a hand to dismiss them.

A stunned look appeared on Han Li's face as he stared at Patriarch Miro. Just now, he felt as if Patriarch Miro's gaze had settled on him for a brief moment.

It was only for a split second, but it was a very profound feeling, as if there were some deeper meaning to that look from Patriarch Miro.

Could it be that not only had Patriarch Miro noticed him eavesdropping on his lecture, he had also discovered the current Han Li, who was reliving this scene through his Eye of Truth?

After some contemplation, Han Li felt like this wasn't very plausible, and he shook his head with a wry smile, feeling as if he were overthinking the situation.

Even after all of the disciples and the fat rat had departed, Patriarch Miro remained seated in silence for a while, then stowed his prayer beads away before slowly rising to his feet.

He then shuffled over the stone wall with the words "Mantra Domain" inscribed upon it, and he observed it in silence for a moment before suddenly raising a hand to point at one of the golden characters.

A beam of golden light shot out of his fingertip before vanishing into that character in a flash, and after that, he clasped his hands behind his back as he looked up at the sky.

His body began to blur, as if he were integrating himself into heaven and earth, and before long, he had vanished altogether.

For some reason, Han Li was struck by a sense of loneliness at the sight of Patriarch Miro's rotund figure, and he was left in a daze for a long while.

After the scene had played out in full, Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis, then flew over to the stone plaque.

With a sweep of his sleeve, he conjured up a gust of wind that cleared the moss and vines from the surface of the plaque to reveal the character that Patriarch Miro had been pointing at in the scene from earlier.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li carefully gazed upon that character with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and sure enough, there was a layer of faint golden light glimmering at the topmost tip of the character, indicating that it was harboring some type of secret.

Han Li reached out with his right hand, and he was able to pierce his index and middle fingers into the stone wall with ease before slowly pulling out an azure bamboo slip from within.

He then channeled his immortal spiritual power to refine the bamboo slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it, and moments later, his eyes abruptly sprang open as an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

As it turned out, the bamboo slip contained the nine levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture, as well as a strange text titled "Sumeru Insights."

The Mantra Axis Scripture was naturally very familiar to him, and he quickly read through the entire scripture to find that some of the passages were a little different from what he had seen in the past. However, these differences were very minute, so they had no significant bearing and certainly wouldn't lead to qi deviation.

Furthermore, enclosed within the scripture was a detailed account of the Mantra Domain ability that he had already obtained from Mu Yan, and in this case, there were also some minor, insignificant differences.

As for the Sumeru Insights text, that was completely unintelligible to Han Li. It only consisted of several thousand words, but the contents were very difficult to understand, and it didn't seem like a cultivation art, nor did it appear to be any type of secret technique.

Han Li spent a long time reading through the text, but to no avail, so he could only give up for now.

After that, he carefully examined the nine levels of the Mantra Axis Scripture once more, and he suppressed the elation in his heart, as well as the urge to begin cultivating on the spot, as he flew over to the stone plaque again.

There, he gazed upon the "Mantra Domain" inscribed on the stone wall, then extended a deep and respectful bow toward the long-gone figure before flying down the mountain.

Chapter 670: Frozen in Time

It didn't take long for Han Li to reach the foot of the mountain, and it seemed that he had arrived in a huge valley with a relatively flat and level terrain.

There were numerous tall buildings standing in the valley, and its layout was rather similar to that of the Water Divination Palace from before.

However, these buildings were primarily golden in color, and even though most of them were damaged, they were still glowing radiantly.

Han Li began to search through the valley, and before long, close to half a day had passed by.

During this time, he had searched through most of the valley, but wasn't able to find much of use aside from some spirit medicines.

Hence, he continued deeper into the valley, and he had only flown a few hundred kilometers when a hint of elation suddenly appeared on his face.

He could sense another burst of time law power fluctuations a few hundred kilometers up ahead!

He immediately flew in that direction without any hesitation, but at the same time, he made sure to keep constant tabs on his surroundings with his spiritual sense.

Shortly thereafter, he was able to find the origins of the burst of time law power fluctuations, and he found himself standing in front of a golden palace.

The palace was constructed beside a mountain, and it was several thousand feet tall, taking up an area in excess of a thousand acres. It was entirely constructed out of some type of jade material that was plated in a layer of golden material, giving it a shimmering golden appearance.

There were many signs of battle around the palace, and holes had even been punched through some places. Beams of golden light were shining through these holes, giving off formidable time law power fluctuations.

A hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of the golden palace, and he carefully released his spiritual sense to scour the area around the building.

Only after ensuring that there was no danger did he slowly make his way over to the shut gate of the palace, and he laid a palm flat against the gate before giving it a firm push.

The gate flashed momentarily with golden light, then swung open, much to Han Li's surprise.

A burst of blinding golden light instantly erupted out of the palace, and it was as if there were a golden sun trapped inside.

Instead of immediately stepping into the palace, Han Li first used his spiritual sense to inspect its interior.

However, his spiritual sense had only just extended into the palace when it was stopped in its tracks by a burst of gentle yet resilient force, preventing it from advancing any further.

Hence, Han Li had to turn to his Infernal Devilish Eyes, but he soon discovered that his Infernal Devilish Eyes were also unable to see through the burst of gentle force within the palace.

All he could see were several indistinct shadows, but he couldn't make out exactly what they were.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li stepped into the palace, and as soon as he did so, his vision immediately blurred, and he felt as if he had entered another space.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of tremendous force enveloped him from all directions, making it impossible for him to even lift a finger.

Thankfully, his vision hadn't faded, and he hurriedly cast his gaze forward in an alarmed manner.

The entire palace was filled with waves of golden light that were rippling like water while giving off bursts of formidable and profound time law powers, and it was precisely these time law powers that had immobilized Han Li.

In addition to Han Li, there were several dozen more cultivators split up into two factions in the palace, and judging from their attire, it was apparent that one side consisted of Heavenly Court cultivators, while the other consisted of True Mantra Sect disciples.

In contrast with the bodies outside, these people still appeared very much alive, and they were still locked in poses that suggested that they were engaged in battle, with all type of treasures hovering around them.

Han Li was unable to detect their cultivation bases, but judging from the visual clues that he was able to gather, he speculated that most of them were True Immortals, while the leader of each group were Golden Immortals.

At this moment, all of them were completely still, as if they had been frozen in time, presenting a very peculiar sight to behold.

Han Li was astonished to see this.

It was clear that this had something to do with the burst of time law power fluctuations in the palace, and they seemed to have a similar effect to that of his Mantra Treasured Axis, except his Mantra Treasured Axis was only able to slow the flow of time, while time seemed to have completely stopped here.

These cultivators had most likely already been trapped here and immobilized for countless years.

Han Li was stunned by what he was seeing, but he quickly gathered himself as an important question sprang into his mind.

Now that he had stumbled into this place, how was he going to get out?

His physical strength was clearly insufficient to struggle free from the restrictive effects of the time law powers here, and the only thing that he could take solace in was that his immortal spirit power and time law powers hadn't also been restricted. Instead, they were able to circulate at a very slow speed.

Perhaps this had something to do with the fact that he was using a time-attribute cultivation art.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately attempted to channel the immortal spiritual power with all his might, and a speck of golden light emerged over his body, then slowly expanded to completely inundate him.

This would've only taken him an instant under normal circumstances, but the same maneuver took him several hours to complete here.

Han Li remained patient as he continued to circulate his immortal spiritual power while also using his own time law powers to ward off the effects of the external time law powers as much as possible.

After what seemed like an eternity, his Mantra Treasured Axis finally appeared behind him, following which he was able to unleash his Reversal True Axis ability.

The flow of time within his body began to speed up as a result, slowing counteracting the restrictive forces around him.

His body was still immobilized, but his immortal spiritual power and time law powers were beginning to circulate a little faster.

This came as quite a relief to Han Li, but he still didn't dare to let down his guard as he continued to channel his Reversal True Axis with all his might.

As the Mantra Treasured Axis revolved in reverse faster and faster, the restrictive forces around him quickly lessened, and over an hour later, the Mantra Treasured Axis had picked up so much speed that it had transformed into a blurry golden disk.

An elated look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he was finally able to slowly raise an arm.

However, even with his Reversal True Axis ability activated to its limits, he was still unable to ward off the surrounding restrictive forces.

Thankfully, the entrance of the palace was just nearby, so he wouldn't have to move far to leave.

With his mobility restored, Han Li was feeling much more reassured, and he began to inspect his surroundings again.

His gaze fell upon the two nearby groups of cultivators, and he began to make his way toward them in an extremely slow and sluggish fashion.

All of them were still carrying their storage tools, and the treasures hovering around them also appeared to be quite powerful.

Han Li strode over to these cultivators before stowing away their storage tools and the treasures floating in the air around them one by one.

After that, he began to make his way toward the other parts of the hall.

These storage tools and treasures made for a nice haul, but they weren't all that appealing to him. Instead, what he was far more interested in was finding out why time had come to a stop here, and that was why he hadn't left the palace right away.

Unfortunately, with his spiritual sense completely impeded here, he could only inspect the palace with his eyes.

The palace wasn't very large, and it didn't appear to be remarkable in any way. At the deepest part of the palace was a stone platform that resembled an altar, and it had already mostly collapsed.

Han Li quickly examined the rest of the palace, but didn't find anything worthy of note.

He turned his gaze to the collapsed altar, then made his way up the steps leading up to it.

As soon as he set foot on the stone platform, Han Li immediately felt a burst of incredibly potent time law power fluctuations.

His eyes immediately lit up, and he knew that he had found the source of this time-stopping effect.

He really wanted to speed up, but the time law power fluctuations up ahead only became more and more potent, so he was slowing down further and further instead. Fortunately, he wasn't immobilized again.

It took Han Li half a day to finally step onto the small altar, and at the center of it was a bottomless hole that seemed to have resulted from some type of attack.

Within the hole was a ball of radiant golden light that was giving off tremendous time law power fluctuations, and that was the reason why time had fallen still in this palace!

The ball of golden light didn't contain any time-attribute immortal treasure or anything like that. Instead, it seemed to be some residual power left behind by some type of attack.

Han Li raised his head to discover that there was a large hole in the ceiling of the palace as well, and its angle was identical to that of the hole in the ground.

A stunned look appeared on Han Li's face upon making this discovery.

Just the residual power from whatever attack had been unleashed was enough to bring time in the palace to a complete standstill for so many years. Han Li couldn't even begin to fathom just how powerful the one who unleashed the attack had to have been.

Could it have been the Time Dao Ancestor?

The Eye of Truth slowly appeared at the center of the Mantra Treasured Axis, and a beam of golden light shot out of the eye and into the hole.

A burst of bright golden light appeared within the hole, and the ball of golden light began to rapidly change form, reverting back into a golden finger projection that was several feet in length before flying back up into the sky.

The broken altar also quickly reverted back to its complete form, but Han Li paid no heed to it as his gaze was focused solely on the golden finger projection.

Bursts of golden light were flashing over the finger projection, and upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered that the finger projection was formed by numerous time law threads intertwined together in an extremely profound fashion.

The finger projection seemed to be able to pierce through all things, and Han Li was struck by a sense of vulnerability just from looking at it.

Ever since his arrival in the True Immortal Realm, he had been constantly working hard in his cultivation, and he was now able to wield the power of time laws, but in contrast with this golden finger projection, his mastery of time law powers was downright abysmal.

Chapter 671: Already Dead

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li.

Back in the Water Divination Palace, the large-headed child had bestowed upon him some memories containing his cultivation insights in addition to the Water Divination Time Arts.

In those memories, the term "law abilities" was brought up, but no explanation of exactly what this concept was had been provided.

At the time, Han Li had only memorized all of this information in the hope that it would be useful to him in the future, and it seemed that perhaps it had something to do with this.

Could it be that this golden finger projection is a type of law ability?

However, he didn't dwell on this train of thought for long as he began staring intently at the golden finger projection, carefully observing the time law power permutations and distribution of time law threads within it.

The profound permutations in the time law powers were extremely mesmerizing to behold, and he quickly found himself completely immersed, as if he were looking at a piece of unmatched artwork.

The finger projection flew back upward, and it quickly vanished through the large hole in the ceiling.

Han Li immediately closed his Eye of Truth upon seeing this, then closed his own eyes as he carefully recalled the incredibly profound sight that he had just witnessed.

A long while later, his Eye of Truth sprang open again at his behest, and a beam of golden light shot out of it and into the hole.

Once again, the same golden finger projection appeared, and Han Li was able to observe it for a second time.

He repeated this process over and over again, and in doing so, he was able to slowly glean a great deal of insight into the golden finger projection, but at the same time, he discovered that there were only more and more things that he didn't understand.

However, he had already memorized all of the time law power permutations within the golden finger projection, so he would be able to continue studying it once he left this place.

At this point, not only was he utterly exhausted, he had also gained as much insight as he could into the golden finger projection, so there was no point in continuing this exercise any further.

With that in mind, he cast his gaze into the hole up ahead, and the ball of golden light inside was still flashing incessantly.

With his Reversal True Axis ability channeled to its maximal extent, he quickly recovered his mobility, then raised an arm as a burst of bright golden light that was interspersed with ten time law threads appeared over the palm of his hand.

He then made a grabbing motion, and the golden light and time law threads instantly transformed into a large golden hand that grabbed onto the ball of golden light before pulling it upward.

However, the ball of golden light seemed to be completely rooted to the spot, refusing to budge.

Han Li's expression changed slightly seeing this, and he took a deep breath, following which sixteen additional time law threads appeared within the large golden hand.

The hand instantly swelled to around twice its original size, and the time law power fluctuations emanating from it were significantly enhanced.

Even so, the ball of golden light still appeared to be completely unmovable.

A hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face as he withdrew the golden hand, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he raised his hand once again, this time to summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd.

A dull thump then rang out as a beam of green light shot out of the gourd before hurtling directly toward the ball of golden light.

However, the beam of green light had only just shot out of the area encompassed within the Reversal True Axis when it was instantly stopped in its tracks by the surrounding time law powers.

Han Li slowly crouched down upon seeing this, extending his hand into the hole on the ground, and only then was the beam of green light able to make contact with the ball of golden light inside.

The beam of green light then attempted to drag the ball of golden light into the Profound Heavenly Gourd, but despite its best efforts, the ball of golden light remained completely still on the spot.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he stowed his Profound Heavenly Gourd away before unleashing another secret technique...

Some time later, Han Li stopped what he was doing as a resigned look appeared on his face.

He had already tried everything that he could think of, but the ball of golden light simply refused to budge.

A conflicted look appeared on his face as he gazed upon the ball of golden light inside the hole.

Was he really just going to have to leave something so precious behind?

He simply couldn't bring himself to give up.

The ball of golden light contained more time law powers than his golden lock and his golden flag combined, and that wasn't even taking into account all of the profound complexities that it also harbored.

If he could secure it, then it would undoubtedly be very useful to him.

All of a sudden, a thought sprang into Han Li's mind, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which a burst of radiant golden light erupted out of his Mantra Treasured Axis.

At the same time, the golden light in front of him converged to form the Clear Time Vial.

Han Li then switched to a different hand seal, and the golden light around his body swept through the surrounding area before forming countless grains of golden sand.

The three bursts of time law powers intertwined to form a golden vortex that was revolving rapidly, and the vortex then began to compress inward at his behest.

A burst of incredibly formidable time law powers flashed past, and the golden vortex transformed into a revolving golden ring.

At this point, Han Li was able to conjure up this golden ring using his three time-attribute cultivation arts with relative ease,

"Go!"

Han Li thrust his palm forward, and the golden ring immediately shot forth before making contact with the ball of golden light.

The golden ring then began to revolve rapidly while giving off dazzling golden light, easily outshining the pervasive golden light that filled the entire palace.

At the same time, a burst of tremendous suction force erupted out of the golden ring to envelop the ball of golden light.

Finally, the surface of the ball of golden light began to ripple slightly, and this was the first sign of wavering that it had displayed thus far.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this.

Several strands of golden light rose up reluctantly from the ball of golden light, then vanished into the golden ring.

The ball of golden light seemed to be trying to resist, but to no avail.

At the same time, the golden ring was glowing brighter and brighter, and more and more golden light was drawn upward before being sucked into the golden ring.

Moments later, the golden ring shuddered as it released a strand of golden light, which vanished into Han Li's body in a flash before appearing on the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he continued to inject more power into the golden ring.

The suction force released by the golden ring became stronger and stronger, and more and more golden light was sucked out of the ball of light before vanishing into the golden ring, only to then transform into time law threads.

The ball of golden light was rapidly shrinking at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, and it didn't take long before it disappeared entirely.

In the instant that the ball of golden light vanished, all of the golden light within the palace rippled slightly before fading away.

The restrictive time law powers within the palace also vanished, and for the first time in countless years, the flow of time was restored to normal.

Immediately thereafter, a string of dull thumps rang out as the Heavenly Court cultivators and True Mantra Sect disciples fell out of the air before crumpling to the ground.

A surprised look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he withdrew the golden ring before making his way over to the cultivators that had crumpled to the ground, only to discover that they were all dead.

How did this happen? They looked very much alive just a moment ago...

The bodies were entirely unharmed, and the nascent souls were still present within them, but their souls had completely vanished without a trace.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense carefully over the bodies, and he quickly noticed something.

As it turned out, there was an extremely faint time law aura left behind in the mind of the body closest to him, and if it weren't for his tremendous spiritual sense and the fact that he had cultivated the laws of time, there was no way that he would've been able to detect it.

The time law aura was imbued with a burst of extremely aggressive intent, similar to that of the golden finger projection, and it was clearly this aggressive finger intent that had destroyed this person's soul.

Han Li then examined all of the other bodies to find that they had suffered the same fate.

So not only does that golden finger projection possess tremendous penetrative power, it can also attack one's soul!

With that in mind, Han Li was only becoming more intrigued by the golden finger projection.

After determining the cause of death of these cultivators, Han Li captured the nascent souls of the two Golden Immortals in the palace, then paid no further heed to the bodies as he turned his gaze to the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him.

At this point, there were as many as thirty-nine time law threads around it.

By refining that ball of golden light, Han Li had earned himself thirteen time law threads.

However, all of the profound time law power permutations within the ball of golden light had been erased after it was converted into time law threads, and that was a little disappointing to Han Li, but having already gained thirteen time law threads, it would've simply been excessively greedy to ask for anything more.

After that, Han Li searched through the palace one more time, but wasn't able to find anything else of use.

After departing from the palace, Han Li continued to make his way deeper into the valley.

Before long, he reached the end of the valley without encountering any more buildings, and he flew out of the valley to continue his search.

Chapter 672: Heaven Piercing Finger

While flying through the air, Han Li summoned a series of storage tools before injecting his spiritual sense into them one after another.

These storage tools were the ones that he had just obtained from the True Mantra Sect disciples. He hadn't taken the storage tools because the treasures inside appealed to him. Instead, he wanted to find out more information about the True Mantra Sect for risk mitigation purposes, as well as to aid him in his search for more treasures.

It hadn't been very long since he entered these ruins, but he had obtained both the Water Divination Time Arts and the Mantra Axis Scripture. On top of that, he had also acquired that golden flag, the blue shield, thirteen additional time law threads, and dozens of storage tools, amounting to an incredible haul.

He was very much looking forward to seeing what else he could find in these ruins, and he didn't really care about his Reincarnation Palace mission anymore. Even in the worst case scenario, he would just have to fail the mission and submit the fifty thousand Immortal Origin Stones instead.

It didn't take long before Han Li had checked through all of the storage tools, but to his dismay, none of them contained any useful information pertaining to the True Mantra Sect.

Han Li stowed the storage tools away, then began examining the storage tools of the Heavenly Court cultivators as well.

All of a sudden, an intrigued look appeared on Han Li's face, and a jade slip emerged in his grasp amid a flash of white light.

It was a map of the True Mantra Sect that he had found from the storage tool belonging to the Heavenly Court Golden Immortal.

He didn't really have much high hopes for the storage tools of the Heavenly Court cultivators, so this was certainly a pleasant surprise.

That Golden Immortal had most likely obtained this map through whatever means in the hope that he would be able to scour the True Mantra Sect for treasures during the Heavenly Court invasion, and now, the map was going to benefit Han Li countless years later.

Han Li drew to a halt, then descended onto a mountain and injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip.

Perhaps the map had been made in a hurry, but it was quite crude, only marking out the main landmarks and areas of the True Mantra Sect.

According to the map, the True Mantra Sect had been far more massive than the Blaze Dragon Dao, and it was split up into five areas, namely Water Divination, True Mantra, Flowing Fire, Earth Dawn, and Wood Emperor. Every single one of those areas was several times the size of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and the True Mantra area was situated at the center, while the other four areas were located in the north, south, east, and west.

The Water Divination Palace was most likely in the Water Divination area, while I currently appear to be in the True Mantra area.

After stowing the jade slip away, Han Li rose up into the air to inspect his surroundings.

There was some white mist in the air here, but it was far thinner than in the Water Divination area, so Han Li was able to enjoy much better visibility with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Down below as a rather unremarkable mountain range with no standout features, and the map was too crude, so it was impossible for Han Li to determine exactly where he currently was in the True Mantra area.

However, he remained unfazed as he continued onward.

It was already a great development that he had a rough map of the True Mantra Sect ruins. At the very least, he wouldn't be stumbling around completely blind anymore. Furthermore, some of the important locations in the five areas had been labeled on the map, so as long as he could ascertain his approximate location, he should be able to follow the map to the important landmarks in the sect.

Around a week flew by in a flash.

On this day, a streak of azure light shot forth from afar before descending onto a mountain.

The azure light faded to reveal Han Li, and on the way here, he had made some more useful discoveries.

Judging from what he had seen in the past few days, Han Li had become even more convinced that he was in a fragmented section of the True Mantra area. Unfortunately, he still hadn't been able to ascertain exactly where he was on the map.

At this moment, Han Li was looking a little wary, and he took a pill before resting for a moment, then quickly continued onward.

After flying for a while longer, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he darted to the side.

There was a spatial rift that was over a hundred feet in length hanging in the air up ahead, and he carefully skirted around the rift before continuing.

He had almost lost his life after unwittingly falling into that spatial rift, so he was making sure to proceed with extra caution.

It didn't take long before another spatial rift appeared up ahead, and there were also bursts of spatial fluctuations surging through the air.

A thought occurred to Han Li as he raised an eyebrow, and he carefully flew forward before descending in front of a cliff.

This was the end of the landmass that he was situated on.

Ahead of the cliff was a vast expanse of nothingness that was filled with countless spatial rifts of different sizes, resembling sets of all-devouring mouths.

Further away in the distance was a giant translucent light barrier that connected heaven and earth, and it was the spatial barrier that he had encountered earlier.

Outside the barrier were countless chaotic spatial currents, but Han Li paid no heed to the spatial turbulence and spatial rifts as he cast his gaze even further into the distance.

There, he could see another spatial barrier, beyond which was what appeared to be a corner of another landmass.

Even through the spatial turbulence and spatial barriers, he could still detect hints of spatial fluctuations emanating from that landmass.

A hesitant look appeared on his face as he peered into the raging spatial turbulence, but he quickly made a decision as he summoned a pair of treasures, one golden and one blue.

These were the two time-attribute immortal treasures that he had obtained earlier, and at this point, he had been able to mostly refine them.

He began to chant an incantation, and waves of rippling blue light emerged from the blue shield to encompass his entire body, while the golden flag also swelled to several times its original size.

Countless specks of golden light surged out of the flag, then rapidly revolved around his body, forming a glittering river of golden light that presented a spectacular sight to behold.

Han Li took a glance at the pair of immortal treasures around him, then gave a pleased nod as he flew straight into the space up ahead.

The space here was extremely unstable, and the area was rife with spatial rifts.

The spatial rifts weren't moving like the ones in the spatial storm from earlier, but that certainly didn't mean that they were stable.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes to their limits as he carefully traversed through the space between the spatial rifts, and he was able to make decently fast progress.

Before long, he arrived at the spatial barrier, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of azure swordlight that struck the barrier in a flash, and the streak of azure swordlight instantly shattered before being repelled back as an azure flying sword.

As for the spatial barrier, it only shuddered slightly before reverting back to normal.

Han Li was rather surprised to see this, and he stowed his flying sword away before extending a finger forward.

Bright golden light appeared over his body as thirty-six time law threads emerged before converging toward his finger in unison, and an indistinct golden finger projection shot forth toward the spatial barrier.

Not only was the finger projection formed by thirty-six time law threads, it was also imbued with bursts of time law powers. It was the best attempt that Han Li could currently muster up at replicating the finger projection that he had seen, but it was still very far from the real thing.

The finger projection unleashed by Han Li was very indistinct, and it possessed nowhere near the power of the finger projection from the palace, but it was still far more formidable than the sword strike that he had just unleashed.

A faint thud rang out as his finger tore through the spatial barrier like a sheet of paper, and an elated look appeared on his face as he lowered his arm while murmuring to himself. "Not bad. I think I'll call this the Heaven Piercing Finger."

After that, he flew out into the spatial turbulence from the large hole in the spatial barrier.

As soon as he did this, he was immediately buffeted by a gust of ferocious gray wind from the side, but he was already prepared for this and summoned a pair of protective immortal treasures to help him weather the storm.

At the same time, the river of golden light swirling around his body swelled drastically in size and instantly overcame the gust of gray wind.

As it turned out, the golden flag was a very rare immortal treasure that possessed both defensive and offensive capabilities.

After vanquishing the gust of gray wind, Han Li continued onward without pause, quickly flying toward the other landmass in the distance.

Gusts of fierce wind were howling in all directions alongside glacial currents and even waves of fire, as well as countless spatial vortexes and spatial rifts.

This spatial storm was significantly more formidable than the last one he had encountered, and he was feeling rather perplexed to see this.

Ever since he entered the True Mantra Sect ruins, he had encountered three spatial storms, with each successive one more powerful than the other.

Han Li channeled the river of golden light around him to ward off the oncoming waves of spatial turbulence as he forged ahead as quickly as he could

The spatial turbulence by itself wasn't a cause for concern, but the spatial rifts carried by the spatial turbulence were extremely powerful and contained immense spatial power. Even the river of golden light around Han Li struggled to contend with them, so Han Li was forced to repel them through other means, and as a result, his progress was very slow.

Thankfully, the two landmasses weren't very far apart, and it didn't take long before most of the distance was covered.

Right at this moment, what sounded like a furious draconic roar rang out, and Han Li turned to the source of the sound, upon which his expression instantly changed drastically.

As it turned out, an enormous white storm was hurtling toward him, tearing through the surrounding spatial turbulence with ease, and it was yet another spatial storm.

This spatial storm was even more formidable than the one that Han Li had encountered after being sucked into that spatial rift, and it was filled with blades of white light that were imbued with violent spatial power capable of shredding through everything in their path.

The spatial storm was extremely fast, and it reached Han Li in the blink of an eye before swallowing him up.

Chapter 673: Acquaintance

Situated in the spatial storm, Han Li was like a leaf that had fallen into a vast sea. There were turbulent currents all around him, tossing him around against his will.

He immediately released his time spirit domain, and the surrounding spatial storm instantly slowed down significantly under the effects of the spirit domain, allowing him some respite, but the blades of white light weren't slowed down by much at all as they continued to rain down upon him.

Han Li took a deep breath, then made a rapid string of hand seals, and the golden flag around him brightened even further before fusing into his time spirit domain.

The surrounding river of golden light instantly swelled to around ten times its original size with a dull thump, and the golden stars within it also expanded drastically as it surged forward with tremendous power.

The blue shield was also glowing radiantly as it swelled to several times its original size, and a projection of a winding river appeared on its surface.

As soon as the blades of white light entered the river of golden stars, they were all involuntarily swept away, so none of them were able to strike Han Li.

However, there were far too many of these blades of light, and some would occasionally force their way through the river of golden stars, but they were kept at bay by the blue shield, which was also a very profound treasure.

All of the blades of white light would instantly warp upon making contact with the shield, causing them to veer off their original trajectories, and Han Li was feeling very reassured upon seeing this.

He was able to refocus his attention on forging ahead, but he didn't have much time. After all, using his spirit domain and two time-attribute immortal treasures at full capacity at once was extremely taxing, and even he wouldn't be able to keep this up for long.

Around fifteen minutes later, Han Li was finally able to rush out of the spatial storm and stumble out into the open.

However, the sight that greeted him on the other side was far from an encouraging one.

The entire surrounding space was filled with chaotic spatial turbulence, and both of the nearby continents had vanished without a trace.

He immediately came to realize that he had been swept away to an unknown place by the spatial storm from earlier, and he currently had no idea where he was.

The spatial turbulence was extremely dangerous, and he didn't have much immortal spiritual power left, so if he couldn't find a safe place soon, then he really was at risk of dying here.

With that in mind, he immediately took a pill, then flipped his hands over to produce a pair of mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones, replenishing his immortal spiritual power while doing his best to recall the location of the two continents from before.

However, he had completely lost all sense of direction while in the spatial storm, so there was no way that he could recall where those two continents were.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he set off in a certain direction while continuing to maintain his time spirit domain and the two immortal treasures.

Even though using all three of those things at once was very taxing on his immortal spiritual power, it also allowed him to traverse quickly through the spatial turbulence, and his current top priority was to find somewhere safe.

Thankfully, his luck wasn't completely terrible, and after flying for some time, he spotted a landmass up ahead.

An ecstatic look appeared on his face as he hurriedly flew toward the landmass, and at the same time, he channeled the remaining immortal spiritual power in his body as he extended a finger forward.

A golden finger projection instantly appeared before striking the spatial barrier, poking a large hole through it.

Han Li shot through the hole like lightning, and the surrounding violent pressure instantly faded.

At this moment, he was looking as pale as a sheet, and he withdrew his time spirit domain and the two immortal treasures, then took a few deep breaths to steady himself.

He cast his gaze downward to discover a large mountain range down below. The mountain range was quite abundant with spiritual qi, and it appeared to be free from the ravages of battle.

The white mist that obstructed one's view was absent here, so even though he still couldn't release his spiritual sense very far, he had great visibility with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

After taking a moment to observe his surroundings, he descended out of the sky, avoiding several nearby spatial rifts en route to the ground.

He then sat down with his legs crossed to rest, and close to half a day later, he opened his eyes before setting off in a certain direction.

He was constantly scouring his surroundings with his eyes and spiritual sense as he flew through the air.

The mountain range here stretched as far as the eyes could see, and it was covered in lush greenery, including some spirit plants that were abundant with vitality.

Han Li naturally wasn't going to leave these spirit plants behind, and all of them were stowed away into storage tools.

While flying through a valley, Han Li's expression suddenly changed slightly as he turned to a certain direction with a peculiar look on his face.

There were violent spiritual power fluctuations coming from that direction, and it was clear that a battle was taking place there.

It seemed that all of the combatants possessed lofty cultivation bases, and they had to also be cultivators who had entered the True Mantra Sect ruins in search of treasures.

At this point, Han Li's mindset had changed from back when he first entered the ruins. All he wanted was to mind his own business and search for treasures, and he had no desire to be swept up in pointless conflicts.

However, right as he was about to depart, a burst of radiant crimson light suddenly erupted into the air from the site of the battle, and the aura fluctuations emanating from the crimson light weren't unfamiliar to him.

He heaved a faint sigh, then began flying in that direction as an indistinct shadow.

At his speed, he was able to reach the site of the battle very quickly, and sure enough, there were two figures up ahead, locked in a heated battle.

One of them had a giant fiery crimson sword hanging above his head and an antiquated golden mirror strapped to his waist, and it was none other than Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

His assailant was a tall and thin azure-robed man. It was the same immortal envoy that had appeared in Jade Gathering City with Gongshu Tian all those years ago, and Han Li recalled that his surname was Wang.

Instead of immediately revealing himself, Han Li observed the battle from a hiding spot nearby.

The azure-robed man's cultivation base was far superior to Immortal Lord Hot Flame's, and he was definitely the one with the initiative.

A giant azure moon projection was hovering above his head, releasing waves of azure light, and each wave of azure light would transform into hundreds of beams of light that hurtled directly toward Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

The giant fiery sword above Immortal Lord Hot Flame's head was revolving rapidly as it released waves of crimson sword projections toward the oncoming beams of azure light.

At this moment, he had changed into a crimson robe with a series of fiery holy birds, including the phoenix and the vermilion bird, embroidered upon, and it appeared to also be an immortal treasure that was constantly blasting forth bursts of scorching crimson flames.

The beams of azure light appeared to be quite unremarkable, but they were extremely formidable, able to pierce through the opposing sword qi and flames with ease before raining down upon Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

Thankfully, the waves of golden light released by Immortal Lord Hot Flame's golden mirror were able to significantly slow down the beams of azure light.

However, there were simply too many of these beams of azure light, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame was still forced to constantly take evasive measures.

"Don't test my patience any further, Huo Zhuozi! Hand over the map, and I'll let you leave. If you continue to resist, then I'll just have to kill you first!" the azure-robed man yelled.

There were already quite a few wounds on Immortal Lord Hot Flame's body, but he wasn't backing down in the slightest as he spat, "Shut your mouth, you Heavenly Court scoundrel! If you want the map, then come and get it!

"In that case, I'll grant you the fate that you desire and send you to your grave!" the azure-robed man harrumphed coldly as a hint of killing intent flashed through his eyes.

Immediately thereafter, the azure moon above his head swelled drastically in size at his behest, and the number of beams of azure light that it was releasing instantly increased by severalfold.

A grim look appeared in Immortal Lord Hot Flame's eyes upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence into the golden mirror strapped to his waist.

The mirror immediately shot forth while releasing bursts of fiery golden light, and at the same time, it swelled to several times its original size before positioning itself in front of Immortal Lord Hot Flame like a shield.

The mirror had only just settled into place when it was struck by countless beams of azure light, and the golden ripples released by the mirror still had their usual slowing effect, but these oncoming beams of azure light were far faster than the ones from before, so the slowing effect wasn't all that apparent.

A string of resounding clangs rang out as the golden mirror trembled violently, and the golden light emanating from it was also flickering incessantly, looking as if it could completely fade at any moment.

However, the mirror remained in place in a resilient fashion, and the golden light around it refused to fade.

A hint of surprise flashed through the azure-robed man's eyes upon seeing this, and a greedy look appeared on his face as he gazed upon the golden mirror.

He then gave a cold harrumph as a burst of azure light erupted out of his body, forming an azure spirit domain that was several dozen kilometers in size.

Right at this moment, a burst of green light suddenly appeared beside the azure moon without any warning, then instantly enveloped it.

The azure moon instantly dimmed as the azure light emanating from it faded, revealing it to be an azure jade bead immortal treasure.

At the same time, a large golden lock appeared out of thin air behind the azure-robed man, then sped toward him like lightning.

"Who goes there?"

The azure-robed man's expression changed drastically as he swiveled around while opening his mouth to release a silver plate, which clashed against the golden lock with a loud clang.

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air to release an azure bamboo slip immortal treasure that transformed into an azure light barrier that encompassed his body from all directions.

At the same time, he reached out with his other hand to make a grabbing motion toward the azure jade bead up above, and a resounding boom rang out as a mountainous azure hand appeared above the jade bead before grabbing forcefully down upon the burst of green light.

The green light was instantly shattered with a dull thump to reveal a green gourd, and there were countless green runes surging around the gourd, giving off tremendous law power fluctuations that caused the nearby space to buzz and tremble incessantly.

That's an Essential Immortal Treasure!

The azure-robed man was ecstatic to see this, and a massive azure rune appeared over the mountainous azure hand at his behest, following which the enormous hand closed itself around the green gourd.

The gourd immediately began to tremble violently, as if it were struggling to free itself, but the giant azure hand held it firmly into place, refusing to let it escape.

Chapter 674: Concerns

That gourd! Could it be...

A peculiar look flashed through Immortal Lord Hot Flame's eyes at the sight of the green gourd.

The azure-robed man quickly inspected his surroundings, then made a hand seal, and the rune on the mountainous azure hand lit up as it released a burst of tremendous law powers.

A loud thump rang out as the protective green light around the gourd was crushed, and the gourd's struggles instantly ceased.

An ecstatic look flashed through the azure-robed man's eyes as he made a beckoning motion to draw the green gourd back to himself.

The gourd was no more than several dozen feet away from the azure-robed man when a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted behind him, and Han Li appeared out of thin air in a stealthy fashion.

As soon as he appeared, he immediately swept both sleeves through the air, releasing a pair of giant azure swords that came crashing down upon the azure-robed man.

Radiant azure swordlight erupted out of the swords, and they were giving off tremendous power that threatened to slice the very heavens into two.

The azure-robed man's expression remained unchanged, save for a disdainful twitch of his lips, and it seemed that he had already anticipated such a sneak attack.

He made a hand seal with one hand, and the azure jade bead above his head freed itself from the green light released by the Profound Heavenly Gourd, then began to glow radiantly as it released two thick pillars of azure light that struck the pair of oncoming swords.

Two earth-shattering thumps rang out as the nearby space shuddered violently, and the pair of giant swords shrank down significantly while flying back through the air. The azure swordlight radiating from them had also dimmed significantly, as if their spiritual nature had been severely damaged.

Han Li's complexion paled slightly, and he stumbled back in retreat as if he had also sustained substantial internal injuries.

The azure-robed man turned to Han Li with a cold sneer, then turned his attention back to the green gourd.

From his perspective, his late-Golden Immortal Stage assailant clearly had a death wish, but at the same time, he had to thank him for fetching him this Essential Immortal Treasure.

The green gourd continued to fly toward him while locked in the grasp of the giant azure hand, but right at this moment, the gourd suddenly began to tremble violently once again.

At the same time, radiant green light erupted from its surface, while a burst of thunderous rumbling rang out within it.

The azure-robed man's expression changed drastically, yet before he had a chance to do anything, a burst of blinding golden light shot out of the gourd before striking the protective azure light barrier around him.

A resounding boom rang out, and despite the azure bamboo slip's indestructible appearance, the burst of golden light was able to pierce through it with ease before going on to punch a large hole into the chest and abdomen of the azure-robed man.

His entire body was almost split into two, but not a single drop of blood flowed out of the wound, and the edge of the hole was smooth and charred black.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and even Immortal Lord Hot Flame was astonished by what he had just witnessed.

A large torrent of blood gushed out of the azure-robed man's mouth as a shocked and enraged look appeared on his face.

If he hadn't managed to dodge slightly to the side just in the nick of time, the burst of golden light would've already pierced through his dantian and killed him on the spot.

Despite his bewilderment, he reacted very quickly, making a hand seal as he opened his mouth to release a ball of azure flames. The azure fire spread outward to encompass his entire body, and he fled the scene as an azure fireball, abandoning all of his immortal treasures with the exception of the azure jade bead.

However, right at this moment, several translucent chains appeared out of the space around him without any warning, and they pierced straight into his mind, with the protective light barrier around him unable to pose any resistance.

He was instantly completely immobilized, and the look on his face abruptly stiffened.

He was still flying forward, but his speed had been drastically reduced.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li appeared in front of the azure-robed man amid a flash of lightning.

His complexion had returned to normal, and he immediately threw a powerful punch forward, conjuring up an azure fist projection that struck the azure-robed man on the head, smashing it like a watermelon.

A translucent cage was revealed inside, trapped within which was an azure soul.

Han Li flicked a finger through the air, and an arc of golden lightning shot out of his fingertip and into the Spiritual Sense Cage, instantly destroying the soul inside it.

The Spiritual Sense Cage then reverted back into several translucent chains that vanished into his mind.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to capture the azure-robed man's remains and the immortal treasures around him before stowing them into the Flower Branch Space.

"There was no need for you to employ such underhanded tactics against a mere mid-High Zenith cultivator, Fellow Daoist Han," Mo Guang remarked in Han Li's mind in an unimpressed voice.

Han Li paid no heed to Mo Guang. He would've indeed been able to kill the azure-robed man with ease using his time law powers, but he didn't want to reveal too much to Immortal Lord Hot Flame for the moment.

He made a beckoning motion to summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd, the two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and the golden lock back to himself, then turned around to face Immortal Lord True Flame.

"You've saved me yet again, Fellow Daoist Li. I really don't know how to thank you," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said in a grateful voice as he flew over to Han Li.

"There's no need to thank me, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame. We agreed to forge an alliance, so it's only right that I do what I can to help you. Having said that, I certainly wasn't expecting to run into you here. Where are Fellow Daoist Fox and Fellow Daoist Shi right now?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid I don't know. We were all separated by the spatial turbulence, and initially, upon being teleported here, everything was going quite smoothly for me, but I encountered that immortal envoy not long ago. If you hadn't arrived when you did, I would've most likely died here,"Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed.

"I've also encountered some outsiders during my time in these ruins, not just from the Heavenly Court, but from some other powers as well," Han Li said.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was very surprised to hear this, and he immediately asked, "Were you able to determine where those people had come from?"

"As far as I'm aware, there was a member of the Robe Change Order and a devilish being from the Devil Realm," Han Li replied.

"The Robe Change Order? How did they find an entrance to these ruins? And a devilish being as well?"

Immortal Lord Hot Flame's brows furrowed tightly as he fell into deep thought.

Han Li waited for Immortal Lord Hot Flame to process this information, but after some time, the latter was still silent, so Han Li called out to him.

"Fellow Daoist Hot Flame..."

"My apologies, I got too caught up in my own thoughts. Back when our True Mantra Sect was destroyed by the Heavenly Court, Patriarch Miro had used his unfathomable power to transfer our entire sect into the boundless expanse of spatial turbulence, so there shouldn't be anyone aside from me who knows the location of the entrance.

“Could it be that we've been followed this entire time without our knowledge?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame mused with tightly furrowed brows.

"Those people have already made it in here, so there's no point in thinking about them. There are many treasures in these ruins, so let's focus on exploring this place and improving our chances at self-preservation," Han Li said, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame nodded in agreement.

"There's most likely no one nearby, but we did cause quite a commotion just now, so we should leave this place as a safety precaution, then think about what we want to do next," Han Li said.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame nodded in response, and the two of them departed.

"You were a disciple of the True Mantra Sect, so you must be very familiar with everything here, right, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame? I'm sure you must've reaped a lot of rewards already. I recall that you entered these ruins for the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, right? Have you found it yet?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid not. My luck has not been great, and I didn't get much of a chance to do any treasure-hunting before I ran into that immortal envoy. As for the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, I don't even know where it's hidden, so how could I possibly have found it?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed with a wry smile.

"Oh? You're also unaware of where the cultivation art is hidden? That's a bit of a problem," Han Li said with a slightly surprised expression.

"If the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra remains permanently lost, then that would be fine, but I'm worried that the Heavenly Court or some other power could get their hands on it," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed with a concerned expression.

Han Li offered no response to this.

"Right now, it seems like there are many powers in the True Mantra Sect ruins. If the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra emerges, I'm doubtful of my ability to secure it on my own, so I hope that you can help me secure it. I'll be sure to compensate you for your help," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as he turned to Han Li with a serious expression.

"At the moment, it's unclear how many powerful cultivators are currently in the True Mantra Sect ruins, so I can't make any promises, but as long as my life doesn't come under threat, I'm willing to lend you my assistance," Han Li replied.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Li," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with an elated expression.

"Speaking of which, what exactly is this Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra? You mentioned that it's a cultivation art?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra is a time-attribute cultivation art. As I'm sure you're aware, there are many time-attribute cultivation arts in the True Mantra Sect, and the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra is the most confidential one," Immortal Lord Hot Flame explained.

"I see. In that case, we really do have to ensure that it doesn't fall into the hands of any outsiders," Han Li replied with a nod.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was secretly observing Han Li's expression, and he was quite relieved to see that there was no greed on Han Li's face as he spoke of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

Chapter 675: Untitled

[1]

As it turned out, the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra really wasn't all that alluring to Han Li. After all, he had already obtained the entirety of the Mantra Axis Scripture, and according to its description, that should be sufficient to support his cultivation to the Great Encompassment Stage.

The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra was the highest caliber cultivation art that the True Mantra Sect had to offer, but it was definitely not going to be easy to cultivate, so it may not be the most suitable choice for him.

At the same time, Han Li knew the dangers of being sucked into the game of jumping from one cultivation art to another in pursuit of greater power. Ultimately, that would only result in failure to master any one cultivation art.

At the moment, his top priority was to attain more power and advance in his cultivation so that he could ensure self-preservation in the ever more chaotic True Immortal Realm. Only then could he think about anything else.

Of course, he was still curious about this cultivation art, and if he could get his hands on it, he certainly wouldn't reject such an opportunity.

The two of them continued to chat while flying through the air, and the terrain up ahead was gradually becoming flatter, smoothing out from an undulating mountain range to a series of hills.

These hills were rather peculiar in that most of them were standing in clusters of two, much like camel humps, and it was unclear why this was the case.

Despite the change in the terrain, the landscape was still extremely abundant with vegetation.

"The spiritual qi here is quite abundant. Which area of the True Mantra Sect are we in right now?" Han Li asked.

A hint of surprise flashed through Immortal Lord Hot Flame's eyes upon hearing this.

"It sounds like you know quite a bit about the layout of our True Mantra Sect, Fellow Daoist Li."

"I obtained a rough map of the True Mantra Sect earlier, so I know the general layout," Han Li explained.

"I see. Right now, we're in the Wood Emperor area, but we're near the edge of the area, so there won't be many valuable treasures. Right now, we're traveling toward the central region, and there used to be many medicine gardens there. Hopefully, they haven't been destroyed," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed.

"Please lead the way," Han Li replied with a nod.

With that, the two of them sped up a little, flying through the air as two streaks of light before vanishing into the distance.

......

At the same time.

A streak of purple light was flying over a set of barren ruins enshrouded in white mist. Trailing along close behind it were two more streaks of light in hot pursuit.

The streak of purple light contained a purple-robed young man with curly white hair, and at this moment, he was racing along with tightly furrowed brows, and he was taking occasional backward glances with a hint of disgust in his eyes.

Close to ten kilometers away, a slightly hunch-backed elderly man with a bald spot was flying through the air alongside a man in a white scholarly robe, and the two of them were riding atop a sleek flying shuttle.

These two were none other than Palace Master Lu Wuliang of the Origin Contention Immortal Region and Immortal Envoy Zhao Zhen, who was previously stationed at Abyssal Lake City of the Concealed Lake Immortal Region, and the person that the two of them were pursuing was Shi Chuankong.

"I didn't think that his mastery over the laws of space would be so advanced. Even with the two of us combining our powers to pilot this seventh-grade immortal treasure flying shuttle, he's still able to keep us at arm's length," Lu Wuliang mused with tightly furrowed brows.

"It's fine. Using one of the three paramount laws is extremely taxing on one's immortal spiritual power, and he's already slowed down quite a bit, so he's clearly feeling the strain. He won't be able to last much longer at this rate. On top of that, given the current fragmented state of the True Mantra Sect, the landmass that we're currently on most likely isn't that large, so he'll have nowhere to run once we force him to the edge," Zhao Zhen said in a composed fashion.

"That's true. Right now, it's only a matter of time before he's cornered," Lu Wuliang chuckled.

"The main issue now is deciding what to do with him once we catch him," Zhao Zhen said as a hesitant look appeared on his face.

"Oh? Why is that a concern?" Lu Wuliang asked with a perplexed expression.

"You may not have heard of this, but this man has previously appeared in Jade Gathering City. He fought briefly with Fellow Daoist Su Liu, and I've heard that his identity is rather sensitive," Zhao Zhen said.

"Don't leave me hanging, Fellow Daoist Zhao. What exactly is so special about his identity?" Lu Wuliang hurriedly asked.

"He's from the Vast Origin House, and he seems to possess a very high status there. It's a pity that we can't get into contact with Fellow Daoist Su Liu right now. Otherwise, we'd be able to get a concrete answer," Zhao Zhen said.

A hesitant look appeared on Lu Wuliang's face upon hearing this, but it didn't take long before he arrived at a decision.

"Given the current circumstances, a peaceful resolution is already out of reach. In any case, we're in the True Mantra Sect ruins right now, so let's kill him here so he can't exact revenge on us at a later date."

"I suppose that's the only feasible option," Zhao Zhen replied with a nod.

As the two of them were speaking to each other, the streak of purple light up ahead suddenly descended toward a large valley down below, and the two of them hurriedly followed along atop their flying shuttle.

There were two tall mountains facing each other at the entrance of the valley, and many holes had been burrowed into the mountains with all types of runes engraved onto the rock face around them. It seemed that some type of restriction had been set up here, but it had since been destroyed, and in particular, half of the mountain on the right hand side had already collapsed.

Zhao Zhen and Lu Wuliang flew into the valley, and they soon spotted a figure on a giant stone plaza inside the valley, setting up something around a black rock at the center of the plaza.

"He's just going to stop here? Does he have a death wish?"

Lu Wuliang was rather taken aback to see this.

"Don't get complacent, Fellow Daoist Lu. As a cultivator of spatial law powers, he's far more dangerous than the average cultivator of the same cultivation base," Zhao Zhen said in a solemn manner.

"Regardless of what he's trying to do, we just have to stop him before he can get it done," Lu Wuliang said with a cold sneer, and as soon as his voice trailed off, a yellow spirit domain instantly erupted out of his body, encompassing the entire surrounding area in a radius of over ten thousand feet.

Immediately thereafter, he sprang forward as his skin turned an earthy brown color, and while in mid-air, he suddenly began to plummet rapidly toward Shi Chuankong as if he had become as heavy as a mountain.

Zhao Zhen opened his mouth to say something, but decided against it in the end and merely looked on with a tense expression.

Lu Wuliang's body was crashing down with such tremendous force that even the air around him was rumbling incessantly, and the very space within the spirit domain was collapsing downward beneath him.

Right as he was about to land on the stone plaza and completely pulverize Shi Chuankong, a burst of silver light suddenly erupted out of Shi Chuankong's body, forming a silver spirit domain that instantly encompassed the entire surrounding space within a radius of several dozen feet.

Lu Wuliang saw a blur flash before his eyes, and the space around him became slightly distorted and indistinct. In the next instant, he crashed down onto the ground with a deafening boom.

An enormous cloud of dust rose up into the air as rock fragments and debris erupted in all directions. The entire earth had caved in by close to a thousand feet, forming an enormous crater in the ground.

Zhao Zhen's eyelids twitched slightly as he observed the unfolding scene from above.

From his perspective, Lu Wuliang had clearly been crashing down toward the white stone plaza, yet somehow, he had landed outside the plaza.

He hurriedly flew down right as Lu Wuliang flew out of the crater, and he asked, "What happened, Fellow Daoist Lu?"

"I'll give it to him, that kid does have tricks up his sleeve. In the instant that I was about to crash down onto him, he used some type of spatial distortion technique to divert me far away from my intended target. Having said that, this is no cause for concern. All I have to do is immobilize him so that he can't use the same technique again, and he'll be a sitting duck for you, Fellow Daoist Zhao," Lu Wuliang said with a cold smile.

"I'll be counting on you then, Fellow Daoist Lu," Zhao Zhen said as he turned to Shi Chuankong with a hint of skepticism in his eyes.

Lu Wuliang nodded in response, yet right as he was about to do something, Shi Chuankong suddenly turned in their direction and gave them a provocative smirk.

Immediately thereafter, he flipped a hand over to produce a fist-sized plate, then extended the index finger of his other hand over the plate to drip a drop of silver blood essence onto it.

All of the spirit patterns on the plate lit up one after another with dazzling silver radiance, and it began to release bursts of formidable spatial fluctuations.

At the same time, a circular array lit up around the black rock behind Shi Chuankong, and the silver light that it was releasing was so radiant that Zhao Zhen and Lu Wuliang were forced to avert their eyes.

After the silver light faded, the two of them discovered that two people had appeared within the silver array.

The one on the left was a seductive woman with a white veil over face, and it was none other than Feng Lin. Standing beside her was a young man wearing a large red feather robe with his purple hair arranged into a tall bun, and as soon as the two of them appeared, they immediately extended a collective respectful bow toward Shi Chuankong.

"We pay our respects to Young Master Shi."

At this point, the plate that Shi Chuankong was holding had already been completely destroyed, and he casually discarded it as his brows furrowed slightly, and he asked, "Why are there only two of you? Where's Elder Jing?"

"I was separated from Elder Jing and Zi Qing after we entered the ruins," Feng Lin hurriedly replied.

The purple-haired young man by the name of Zi Qing cupped his fist in a salute as he explained, "While exploring a set of ruins, Elder Jing and I either triggered some type of restriction or fell prey to a sneak attack.

“In any case, Elder Jing was swallowed up by a cloud of gray mist, and he vanished before he had a chance to resist. I immediately retreated upon seeing this, and I was summoned here before I had a chance to investigate any further."

[1]. Not sure why, but this chapter and the next one (Chapter 676: Untitled) both appear to be untitled.

[Back]

Chapter 676: Untitled

Shi Chuankong was silent for a moment, then said, "Forget about it. I've already found some leads on what I'm looking for, so let's take care of this matter first, then get out of here."

Both Feng Lin and Zi Qing heaved an internal sigh of relief upon hearing this.

Zi Qing cast his gaze toward Zhao Zhen's duo, and a mocking sneer appeared on his face as he scoffed, "You two must have a death wish to be attacking the young master of our Vast Origin House. Have you grown bored of your immortal lives as Jade Immortals?"

At this point, Zhao Zhen and Lu Wuliang had already retreated to over ten thousand feet away, and all of a sudden, they felt like they had made a grave mistake.

......

Several days later.

Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame were making their way through a wide passageway toward a palace.

The passageway was lined with weeds and tall grass, as well as broken stone statues and lanterns, presenting a bleak sight to behold.

"This is where ceremonies used to be conducted in our sect. The round altar that we passed by earlier was used for the major ceremony that was held once every one thousand years. At the time, the concept of the four allied immortal regions still didn't exist, but every single one of those ceremonies was treated as a grand event, with all of the nearby immortal regions sending representatives to attend the event.

“It's very saddening to see the sect reduced to such a state now," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed with a reminiscent look in his eyes.

"Countless empires and sects have risen and fallen over the course of history. It's impossible to predict the future, so don't dwell on reminiscing about the past or fearing the future. Right now, we should focus on finding the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra," Han Li consoled.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame nodded in response, but it was clear that he was still lost in his own thoughts.

The palace at the end of the passageway was enormous, and even though most of it had already collapsed, the part of it that was still standing presented a glimpse into how majestic the building would've been in its heyday.

There was a tall gate not far away, hanging above which was a plaque that read "Reverence Pavilion" in large golden characters.

Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame made their way to the palace, and they looked up at the giant gate for a moment, then exchanged a glance with each other, following which the latter stepped forward to push the gate open.

The gate creaked open with a depressing sound resembling a reluctant sigh from the ancient palace, and Han Li's duo stepped into it to find that it was in a state of complete disarray.

There were broken tiles and bricks everywhere, and everything was covered in slick moss and messy weeds.

There was half a jade plaque jutting out of the debris, and half a golden character that seemed to read "heaven" was visible on it.

It was impossible to tell what furnishings had originally been in the palace as most of the place had been reduced to rubble, and the only areas that were somewhat clearly visible were the ones directly adjacent to the walls.

As Han Li passed by a wall, he noticed that there were some extremely vibrant murals painted upon them. Even though it had already been countless years, the colors were still very bright and fresh, as if they had only just been drawn.

"What are these?" he asked.

"This Heaven Calendar Pavilion is a very special place in our sect, and it holds many of our sect's secrets. It's strictly off limits to ordinary disciples unless express permission is given, and the murals here mostly depict some important events in our sect's history.

“If the array in the palace were still intact, all of the murals would be able to move and depict different scenes, but with the array destroyed, they've been reduced to still images," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed with a shake of his head.

Han Li turned to one of the murals beside him, and his attention was immediately drawn to it.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame also turned his gaze to the mural to discover that it depicted what appeared to be a grandiose banquet.

The main color tone of the mural was a vibrant and festive red, and there was a lively and bustling celebration taking place within it.

The murals beside it also presented different scenes that depicted the same event, with Patriarch Miro, his five disciples, and many other important figures of the True Mantra Sect occasionally featuring in the murals.

"Fellow Daoist Hot Flame, am I correct in saying that the people depicted here are from the Heavenly Court?" Han Li suddenly asked as he raised an eyebrow.

In one of the murals, the guests in attendance were dressed in attire that was identical to that of the Heavenly Court cultivators.

"That's right. This banquet was held to welcome a group of extremely prestigious envoys from the Heavenly Court. They were official envoys from the Middle Earth Immortal Region, so a welcome of the highest order was arranged. That was truly a grand event of the True Immortal Realm, and I still remember it like yesterday," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a nod.

"In that case, it sounds like the True Mantra Sect and the Heavenly Court weren't on bad terms. Why did the two ultimately go up in arms against each other?" Han Li asked.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame shook his head in response. "One of the reasons I came back to the sect is to find out the answer to that question. Not long after this banquet, I was sent out on a mission, so I know very little about the events that transpired next."

Han Li nodded in response, but he was left feeling even more perplexed.

After a brief pause, he continued to roam his gaze over the wall, and he noticed a corner of a mural protruding out from behind a rubble, so he swept a sleeve through the air to sweep the rubble aside, revealing the full mural to discover that it was depicting a rather strange image.

The setting was a dimly lit underground palace, and a meeting was taking place between Patriarch Miro, the yellow-robed tree being by the name of Mu Yan, the imposing man with the fiery red hair, the dark-skinned young man who was built like an iron pagoda, and a mysterious figure wearing a black cloak with their entire body shrouded in gray mist.

Particular attention had clearly been paid to the illustrations of Patriarch Miro and his three disciples, and Han Li was even able to see the minute differences in their expressions, which told a story of surprise, fear, suspicion, and befuddlement.

However, the face of the cloaked figure was completely concealed beneath the hood of his cloak.

At the end of the mural, Patriarch Miro traveled alone into another strange space, where he obtained a millstone-sized silver plate from a devilish being with a pair of curved horns on their head.

That was where the images concluded, and there were no further murals on the collapsed wall.

"Do you know who that is, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li asked as he pointed at the cloaked figure.

"I'm aware that our patriarch, my master, and some others suddenly left the banquet at some point, but I don't know what they were doing, and I don't know who that mysterious visitor is," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a shake of his head.

"Your master? Which one of these was your master, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li asked.

"The man with the red hair was my master, Qi Mozi. The yellow-robed man was my Senior Martial Uncle, Mu Yan, and the dark-skinned man behind him was my Third Martial Uncle, Wu Yang. The other two child-like figures that you saw at the banquet were my Fourth Martial Uncle, Jin Yuanzi, and my Fifth Martial Uncle, He Ze," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied.

Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon hearing the name "Qi Mozi". He thought back to the large-headed child that he had seen in the Water Divination Palace, the one whose name was He Ze, and that child had clearly told him to kill Qi Mozi.

Was He Ze referring to Immortal Lord Hot Flame's master? If they were fellow martial brothers, then why had they become sworn enemies?

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face as he grappled with these confounding thoughts.

"Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist Li?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, but ultimately decided against telling Immortal Lord Hot Flame about his encounter with He Ze. Instead, he merely shook his head and replied, "No, I'm just curious about what they were discussing. I presume that mysterious visitor was no ordinary person."

"There's no way to tell what they were discussing, but it's clear that they were discussing something very important. Otherwise, there's no way that our patriarch would've left my martial uncles behind to entertain the Heavenly Court guests on their own, while he took my master and my other two martial uncles to see this visitor," Immortal Lord Hot Flame mused.

"So you left the sect not long after that, and it was during your absence that the True Mantra Sect was attacked, is that right? In that case, perhaps this visit from this mysterious figure had something to do with the Heavenly Court. Perhaps it was even the key to the True Mantra Sect's downfall," Han Li speculated with a contemplative expression.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame offered no response as he also fell into deep thought while staring at the mural with slightly furrowed brows.

Han Li didn't speak any further on this matter, and he returned his gaze to the mural as he also became lost in his own thoughts.

Some time later, Han Li suddenly asked, "By the way, do you know the location of the secret chamber depicted in this mural?"

"I'm not certain, I can only think of several possible locations, but there's only one way to find out if any of them is actually where the secret chamber is situated," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied.

"Given the importance of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, I'm sure Patriarch Miro would've treasured it greatly as well. Hence, there's a decent chance that he hid it here or somewhere of similar importance. I guess we'll just have to see," Han Li said.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame nodded in response, and the two of them carefully searched through the area before departing and continuing onward.

Chapter 677: Remains

Over half a month later.

Han Li's duo had arrived at a rippling lake, and they were hovering in the sky above it, looking ahead with tightly furrowed brows.

The space there had been severed once again, and the entire area was filled with countless spatial rifts. Even the lake down below had been sliced into two, and on the edge was an invisible barrier that resembled a wall of water.

On the other side of the spatial rifts was a moderate-sized landmass and a series of independent mountains that had dense clusters of white jade palaces on them. However, most of them were displaying signs of damage, and some of the mountains had even mostly crumbled away.

As he gazed upon the floating mountains and the white plaza, a sense of familiarity welled up in his heart, and right as he was trying to figure out where he had seen it before, Immortal Lord Hot Flame's voice suddenly rang out beside him.

"It looks like we won't be able to continue any further, Fellow Daoist Li. We may have to find another path."

"Do you recall what place that landmass used to be, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li asked.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame faltered slightly upon hearing this, then stared at the landmass for a moment before replying in a hesitant voice, "I think that was the Twin Birth Palace of Senior Martial Uncle Mu Yan. It's one of the most important locations in the sect outside of our patriarch's True Mantra Palace. Having said that, this entire space is in a state of complete disarray, so I can't say for sure."

At this point, Han Li was almost completely certain that this was where he had been during the instance of transmigration where he had witnessed the fall of the True Mantra Sect, and it was also where he had hidden Mu Yan's body.

"If it's that important a place, then we should check it out. What if the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra is hidden there?" Han Li said.

"But the problem is that we can't advance any further beyond this point. Let's go somewhere else, and there may be another route that we can take," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied.

Han Li scoured his gaze over the area for a moment, then pointed in a certain direction as he said, "There's no need for that. The spatial rifts here are quite concentrated, but it's not like there's no way through at all. Take a look over there, that's a passageway that leads to the other landmass, is it not?"

Immortal Lord Hot Flame turned his gaze to that direction to discover a pillar of water that was around ten feet in radius extending out of the edge of the lake several thousand feet away, and it resembled a water bridge that led to the landmass close to ten kilometers away.

"Is that supposed to be a joke, Fellow Daoist Li? That pillar of water is surrounded by spatial rifts in all directions, and we could easily get sucked into one of them if we're not careful. On top of that, the other side is also cut off by a spatial barrier, so even if we can make it safely through the pillar of water, we'll only be hitting a deadend anyway. Why take the risk?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a perplexed expression.

"Risks have to be taken. We may not be able to find an alternative route to that landmass, and even if we can, it would be too much of a delay, so the best course of action is to cross from here," Han Li countered.

He had already used this method to successfully cross landmasses, so he had built up some confidence.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame knew that he wouldn't be able to dissuade Han Li, so after some contemplation, he didn't raise any further objections, but he was clearly still rather hesitant.

"Once we reach the other spatial barrier through the pillar of water, I'll find a way to open the spatial barrier, and we'll burst through in one go," Han Li said.

"Do you really have a way to break open the spatial barrier without impacting the nearby spatial rifts?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked as he raised an eyebrow in a skeptical manner.

"The spatial barrier here is far more brittle than spatial barriers you'll find elsewhere, so it won't be difficult to break it. As long as we're fast enough, I'm at least 70% sure that we'll succeed," Han Li reassured with a smile.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was left a little speechless upon hearing this, but at this point, he could only take a gamble on Han Li.

After completing the required preparations, the two of them darted straight into the lake down below before swimming toward the opposite landmass through the channel of water like a pair of fish.

After entering the channel of water, both of them were extremely anxious, and they advanced extremely slowly while also suppressing their spiritual power fluctuations as much as possible for fear of inadvertently moving one of the nearby spatial rifts.

It took the two of them over two hours to cover the short distance of less than ten kilometers, ans as they drew close to the spatial barrier, Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he summoned his Profound Heavenly Gourd, aiming its mouth up ahead while also turning to Immortal Lord Hot Flame, gesturing for him to get ready.

After that, he thrust the palm of his hand firmly into the underside of the gourd, and a burst of piercing green light erupted out of its mouth amid a thunderous boom.

Immediately thereafter, an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords shot out of the green vortex within the gourd, then pierced into the spatial barrier up ahead as a blurry sword projection.

A burst of violent rumbling rang out, and before the spatial barrier was shattered, the channel of water began to churn violently from the shockwaves resulting from the force of the impact.

The surrounding space was also affected, and the tenuous balance was instantly broken as all of the surrounding spatial rifts instantly expanded to devour the surrounding water while converging toward Han Li's duo.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame's expression changed drastically upon hearing this, and he hurriedly summoned his golden mirror before injecting his immortal spiritual power into it with all his might.

A vast expanse of golden light erupted forth, forming a golden area around Han Li's duo, and the rate of expansion of the surrounding spatial rifts slowed down significantly, but they were still expanding ever so slightly.

Right at this moment, a loud crack rang out, and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword finally pierced through the spatial barrier up ahead to create an opening that was only around half the height of a grown man.

Han Li immediately grabbed onto Immortal Lord Hot Flame's collar before rushing through the opening, and after that, he summoned his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword back to himself and flew forward for over ten thousand more feet before turning back around.

The spatial passageway that they had opened up was still open, but the channel of water had already been completely destroyed by the spatial rifts, and there were tiny black cracks entering through the opening on the spatial barrier.

However, thankfully, the cracks were all extremely small, and they didn't expand the opening any further.

Moments later, the opening slowly closed, and Han Li heaved a sigh of relief upon seeing this.

"Thanks for holding off those spatial rifts back there, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame," Han Li said with a smile as he stowed his Profound Heavenly Gourd away.

At this moment, there was still a hint of lingering fear in Immortal Lord Hot Flame's eyes, and a wry smile appeared on his face as he sighed, "I now understand how you became so powerful, Fellow Daoist Li. Fortune truly does favor the brave."

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame. I have been very fortunate in the past, but I'm far from brave," Han Li replied with a smile.

After a brief rest, the two of them began to make their way over the white plaza that was littered with scattered rocks, and they soon spotted an enormous set of palatial ruins.

In contrast with the ruins from before, this palace had clearly been severely burned. Many of the remaining palace walls were displaying signs of melting under intense heat, but there wasn't a single body to be seen, as if they had all been incinerated into nothingness.

"I was right, this is indeed the Twin Birth Palace of old. In the past, Senior Martial Uncle Mu Yan was responsible for taking care of most of the sect's affairs, so his Twin Birth Palace was the busiest place in the sect, but it appears that it's also the most severely damaged place in the sect," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed.

During the battle that he had witnessed, Han Li recalled that the attack unleashed by the Time Dao Ancestor had landed not far away from here. The center of the battlefield couldn't have been far from this place, so it was no wonder that it was so severely damaged.

Upon arriving near the palace, Han Li began to examine it while recollecting his memories of the area.

Some time later, his gaze fell upon a tall pile of rubble, and he stopped in his tracks, then began to inspect the pile of rubble with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame also stopped in his tracks upon seeing this, and Han Li feigned an uncertain expression as he said, "Fellow Daoist Hot Flame, there seems to be something under that pile of rubble over there."

"Is there? Could it be a hidden underground palace?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I don't think so, but there's only one way to find out," Han Li replied.

With that, the two of them flew over to the pile of rubble before digging into the ground beneath it, and a long while later, they emerged with a body carried on Immortal Lord Hot Flame's back.

The body was wearing a tattered yellow robe, and it had a head of limp, yellow hair that resembled withered straw. It was none other than Mu Yan!

His body was virtually completely unchanged from when Han Li had last seen it during his transmigration, except his complexion had grown a little darker, and his yellow robe had also become severely decomposed.

"That spirit eye ability of yours is truly incredible, Fellow Daoist Li. It's amazing that you were able to detect Senior Martial Uncle Mu Yan's body when it was buried so deep," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as he smoothed down Mu Yan's yellow robe.

In reality, given the spiritual sense restrictions in these ruins, there was no way that Han Li would've known that there was a body here if he wasn't the one that had buried it in the first place.

"I don't know what compelled me, but as soon as I got here, I had an instinctive feeling that there was something under here," Han Li explained as he feigned an oblivious expression.

"In that case, it sounds like it was fate at work," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said.

"Is Senior Mu Yan carrying the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra?" Han Li asked, even though he already knew the answer.

"No, but there's a chance that it could be hidden in his Twin Birth Palace," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied as he cast his gaze toward the completely collapsed palace in the distance.

After that, he hoisted Mu Yan's body back onto his own back, then made his way toward the palace with Han Li in accompaniment.

Nothing remained of the wooden structures in the palace, and the brick walls that were still standing had been melted into a completely unrecognizable state.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame strode over to a half-standing brick wall at the rear of the palace, then swept away the soot and dust on it with his hand to reveal a set of strange patterns that resembled the rings of a tree, upon which he exclaimed in an ecstatic voice, "I knew it!"

In response to Han Li's perplexed expression, he explained, "This is a secret chamber symbol. There was one in my master's Flowing Fire Palace in the past, and there's one here as well, in the exact same location, at that."

"Were they on good terms with each other?" Han Li asked in a seemingly casual manner.

"Well... Senior Martial Uncle Mu Yan had a very short temper, so they got along worst out of Patriarch Miro's five disciples, but overall, my master and my senior martial uncles were very close," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied.

Han Li nodded in response and didn't speak any further on this matter.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame picked up one of Mu Yan's hands before pressing it down upon the secret chamber symbol. He then injected some of his immortal spiritual power into Mu Yan's body, and a layer of azure light appeared over the palm of Mu Yan's wizened hand, much like a dead tree recovering some of its vitality with the arrival of spring.

The secret chamber symbol flashed with azure light, and an azure doorway of light that was around as tall as a grown man emerged from it.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame ceased his injection of immortal spiritual power upon seeing this, and Mu Yan's hand returned to its original lifeless, gray color.

He then took a glance at Han Li, indicating for him to follow along before stepping into the door of light with Mu Yan's body on his back.

Han Li hesitated momentarily before stepping into the door of light as well, and in the next instant, the two of them appeared in a giant underground palace.

Chapter 678: Baleful Embryo

Han Li took a moment to regain his bearings, then glanced at Immortal Lord Hot Flame before casting his gaze forward.

The underground palace was completely dark and silent, and it was impossible to tell what laid ahead.

"Let's go, Fellow Daoist Li," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as he led the way from the front, flipping a hand over to summon a bright, walnut-sized jewel, which he tossed upward to send it burrowing its way into the ceiling above.

The jewel was giving off radiant white light that illuminated the entire underground palace, and it was revealed that there was a strange wooden chair up ahead.

The chair seemed to have been interwoven out of the branches of a pair of short trees, and half of it was a dark green color, while the other half had a withered yellow hue.

"I thought this would be where Senior Martial Uncle Mu Yan stored his spirit pills and immortal plants, but it appears that there's nothing here," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as a hint of disappointment flashed through his eyes.

"Given how secretive this place is, I'm sure there's more to it than meets the eye. Perhaps there's something hidden here, and we just need to look a little harder," Han Li said as his gaze fell upon the wooden chair.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame nodded in response, and he strode forward until he reached the wooden chair. After that, he gently set Mu Yan's body down onto the chair so that it was in an upright seated posture, then extended a respectful bow toward the body.

Meanwhile, Han Li waited for Immortal Lord Hot Flame to pay his final respects to Mu Yan, and only after that did they begin to search through the palace together.

Some time later, the two of them met back up at the center of the palace, and they exchanged a glance to discover their own disappointment mirrored in each other's eyes.

"I wasn't able to find any concealed mechanisms or restrictions here," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said.

"It looks like whatever was in here has most likely already been taken," Han Li sighed in response.

All of a sudden, he noticed out of the corner of his eye that Mu Yan's body seemed to have moved ever so slightly.

He immediately turned his gaze to Mu Yan's body, only to find that it remained seated in a completely still manner on the strange wooden chair, but he was certain that he hadn't just imagined the movement.

"I don't think so. I doubt anyone else aside from myself would've been aware of the existence of this underground palace," Immortal Lord Hot Flame mused, clearly having failed to detect what Han Li had just seen.

"Perhaps the True Mantra Sect was already looted when it was destroyed all those years ago..."

All of a sudden, Han Li's voice trailed off as his expression changed drastically, and he yelled, "Look out, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame!"

At the same time, a layer of peculiar green light emerged over Mu Yan's body, and black baleful qi was gathering within the large wound on its abdomen, forming a grape-sized bead in the blink of an eye.

There was black qi swirling incessantly around the bead, presenting a strange sight to behold.

Immediately thereafter, the branches on the wooden chair beneath Mu Yan's body suddenly parted as if they had sprung to life, then swept toward Immortal Lord Hot Flame like masses of vines.

All of this had taken place in an instant, and even though Immortal Lord Hot Flame had been alerted by Han Li, he was still just a little too late to react, and he had only just sprung into action when several of the vines wrapped themselves around his arm.

He immediately let loose an agonized howl as the sleeve around his arm was instantly reduced to ashes, and a series of black char marks appeared over the exposed skin of his arm. At the same time, his arm was being rapidly drained of its vitality, and his skin was becoming as wizened as tree bark.

He immediately opened his mouth to release a burst of scorching crimson flames, which flowed along the vines ensnared around his arm toward the wooden chair.

However, these incredibly formidable flames simply slipped off the vines like rain, and the vines were left completely unharmed.

Right at this moment, a streak of azure swordlight shot forth through the air, swooping down with arcs of golden lightning flashing around it.

A loud snap rang out as the vines were severed, dark green liquid came gushing out alongside bursts of baleful black smoke.

As soon as Immortal Lord Hot Flame was freed, he immediately rushed over to Han Li's side, then summoned a golden talisman that he pressed onto his arm with his uninjured hand.

A faint sizzling sound rang out as plumes of pungent white smoke began to rise up from the talisman.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was sweating profusely from the intense agony, but he had no time to dwell on his own pain as he hurriedly asked, "What's going on, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"I'm not sure, but it looks like Senior Mu Yan is about to transform into a baleful entity," Han Li replied with tightly furrowed brows.

At the same time, he was staring intently at the strange wooden chair. At this point, all of its vines had shrunk back and were waving incessantly like a head of devilish hair, but they were no longer lashing out at Han Li's duo.

"How is that possible? It's already been countless years, how could it possibly be that this just so happens to be the exact moment that he transforms into a baleful entity?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with an incredulous expression.

"I don't have an answer to that, but I feel like it most likely has something to do with that wooden chair," Han Li speculated.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he hurriedly yelled, "That's not a wooden chair, that's a..."

Before he had a chance to finish his sentence, Han Li interjected in an urgent voice, "He's about to form a baleful embryo! Fellow Daoist Hot Flame, help me ward off those vines!"

At this moment, Mu Yan's body had begun trembling violently, and his eyes were darting around back and forth beneath his eyelids, looking as if they could spring open at any moment.

Han Li immediately sprang forward while summoning nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once, then combined them into a single sword before piercing it directly toward Mu Yan's abdomen, where the baleful embryo was taking shape.

As soon as he reached within several hundred feet of the body, the nearby vines instantly erupted into a frenzy, lashing out at him from all directions.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame hurriedly summoned his golden mirror upon seeing this, then tossed it forward before making a hand seal.

The mirror shuddered violently as a complex rune appeared on its surface, and it released countless rays of golden light that encompassed the entire space around Han Li.

A burst of formidable time law power fluctuations surged through the golden light, and all of the vines that were sweeping toward Han Li instantly became extremely slow and sluggish.

At the same time, Han Li channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to drastically enhance his own speed while a ball of Divine Devilbane Lightning was conjured up at the tip of his azure longsword using his Lightningwield Technique.

The sword was able to pierce straight through the barrier formed by interwoven vines before plunging into the hole in Mu Yan's abdomen, and a resounding thunderclap rang out as the ball of golden lightning exploded in all directions as countless tiny arcs of golden lightning, instantly tearing the baleful embryo to shreds.

The destroyed baleful embryo reverted back into baleful qi that was completely eradicated, but right at this moment, Han Li saw Mu Yan's body open its eyes.

However, the figure that was reflected in the pupils of Mu Yan's eyes was Qi Mozi instead of Han Li.

In the next instant, countless bursts of formidable sword qi erupted in all directions, tearing Mu Yan's body to shreds along with the two trees beneath it.

"No!"

An anguished cry rang out, followed by a forlorn sigh, and the former had come from Immortal Lord Hot Flame's, while the sigh had been heaved by Mo Guang.

As soon as Han Li landed on the ground, Mo Guang's voice rang out in his mind.

"What a pity... If only I hadn't been so engrossed in my cultivation just now..."

Han Li was naturally aware of what Mo Guang was referring to. If he could've devoured that baleful embryo, then his cultivation base would've definitely advanced even further, but deep down, that wasn't what Han Li wanted to see.

An early-High Zenith Stage Mo Guang was already rather difficult to control, if he allowed Mo Guang to become even more powerful, then there was no telling what could happen.

"My apologies, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang. The situation was very urgent, so I had to act," Han Li said, communicating internally with Mo Guang.

"It's fine, it simply wasn't meant to be," Mo Guang sighed.

Han Li turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame, then asked, "Why did you call out to stop me just now, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?"

At this point, Immortal Lord Hot Flame had already stowed his golden mirror away, and he stormed over to Han Li, then looked down at the charred wooden chair with a forlorn expression as he sighed, "You went too far overboard, Fellow Daoist Li."

"What's the problem?" Han Li asked with furrowed brows.

"This thing is not some wooden chair. Instead, it's an immortal plant by the name of Twin Birth Tree. I recall that this was the thing that Senior Martial Uncle Mu Yan used to overcome his baleful decay," Immortal Lord Hot Flame explained.

An intense pang of remorse instantly welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this, but there was nothing that he could do.

He leaned down to examine if there was any chance that the tree could be saved, and in doing so, he noticed a green branch among all of the charred branches. Only after plucking out that particular branch did he discover that it was actually a branch-shaped jade slip.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame's expression instantly changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly asked, "Could this be the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra?"

"Why don't you find out?" Han Li asked as he handed the jade slip over to Immortal Lord Hot Flame without any hesitation.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was rather embarrassed by Han Li's forthright attitude, and he said, "To think that I still harbored some reservations about you, even after you saved my life so many times. I'm truly ashamed. Regardless of whether the jade slip contains the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, you can examine its contents. But after that..."

Chapter 679: Ethereal Bamboo Melody

"Of course, this jade slip belongs to you after that," Han Li said with a smile before Immortal Lord Hot Flame had a chance to finish his sentence.

"You're a far better man than I am, Fellow Daoist Li," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said in a genuine voice as he extended a respectful salute toward Han Li.

Han Li waved a dismissive hand, then picked up the jade slip and pressed it against his glabella to inject his spiritual sense into it.

Immediately thereafter, he raised an eyebrow as he discovered a passage of small golden text hovering within a body of azure light within the jade slip.

It was a rather complex cultivation art, but it was one by the name of the Eastern Vicissitudes Scripture, rather than the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

It took Han Li only a moment to memorize the entire cultivation art, following which he removed the jade slip from his forehead and handed it to Immortal Lord Hot Flame, who hurriedly accepted it before also inspecting its contents.

Han Li watched as his expression gradually turned from elation to disappointment, which was then replaced with a pleased smile.

The Eastern Vicissitudes Scripture had a total of nine parts, and it was also a time-attribute cultivation art. On top of that, it seemed to be closely interconnected to the Water Divination Time Arts and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture.

"Fellow Daoist Li, this may not be the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, but it's still a secret cultivation art of our sect, nonetheless, so please don't distribute it to any outsiders," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said in a serious manner after stowing the jade slip away.

"Of course. By the way, if you have no use for this ruined Twin Birth Tree, then may I have it?" Han Li asked.

"You've already completely destroyed the tree's vitality with your last attack, why would you want to keep it?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a surprised expression.

"I was thinking that if, by some miracle, I could resurrect this Twin Birth Tree, then I'll have a chance of overcoming my baleful decay," Han Li replied with a wry smile, but internally, he was wondering if he could somehow revive the tree using the spirit liquid produced by his Heaven Controlling Vial.

"I see. In that case, be my guest, Fellow Daoist Li," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a smile.

"Also, do you know how Senior Mu Yan used this Twin Birth Tree to overcome his baleful decay?" Han Li asked while carefully stowing away the remnants of the tree.

"I'm afraid I'm not familiar with the intricacies of Senior Martial Uncle Mu Yan's cultivation, but I presume it's just the same old process of guiding one's baleful qi out of their body and into an external object," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied.

"I thought so, too. In that case, it makes sense why Senior Mu Yan's body suddenly began to transform into a baleful entity. It most likely had something to do with the large quantity of baleful qi within the Twin Birth Tree," Han Li said with a nod.

After the tree was packed away, the two of them didn't immediately depart. Instead, they only left the underground palace after Immortal Lord Hot Flame's arm was mostly healed.

"If the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra isn't in the Twin Birth Palace, then there aren't many places left in the sect where it could be hidden. The Hidden Truth Valley shouldn't be far away from this place, assuming it's not on a separate landmass, so let's go there first," Immortal Lord Hot Flame suggested after the two of them returned to the plaza.

"What was this Hidden Truth Valley previously used for?" Han Li asked.

"The Hidden Truth Valley was where Patriarch Miro normally cultivated in seclusion. Our patriarch spent most of his time there and only came out to deliver lectures or to address important sect affairs. Hence, I think it's one of the places where the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra could be hidden," Immortal Lord Hot Flame explained.

"Alright, then let's go," Han Li replied with a nod.

After that, the two of them got onto a flying boat, then set off in the direction of the Hidden Truth Valley under Immortal Lord Hot Flame's guidance.

Along the way, they could see the ground below was severely ravaged by all types of fearsome attacks.

Han Li couldn't help but think back to the scene that he had witnessed during his transmigration, particularly that almighty palm strike that had descended from the heavens, the recollection of which still struck him with a sense of lingering fear.

With that in mind, he couldn't help but look up into the heavens, but of course, he saw nothing but the clear, blue sky.

Close to an hour later, the flying boat flew over a large set of ruins, then arrived in the air above a large plain, where it slowed down significantly.

"It's a good thing that the Hidden Truth Valley hasn't collapsed and is still connected to the Wood Emperor area," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a smile as he cast his gaze toward an azure valley in the distance.

Han Li was also observing the valley, and he noticed that the two mountains on either side of it weren't very tall, and the terrain in the valley was quite flat, so most of the valley was basked under the light of the sun.

"This valley doesn't appear to be remarkable in any way. I'm assuming there must be some special restrictions set up here, right?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"You're overthinking things, Fellow Daoist Li. This is not the place in our sect with the most abundant world's origin qi, nor have I heard of any hidden restrictions here. Our patriarch chose this place to cultivate purely because he likes the Ethereal Bamboo growing here," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a smile.

"I see," Han Li mused with a slightly surprised expression.

Right as they were speaking to each other, the two of them arrived at the entrance of the valley.

Even before they landed on the ground, they heard a collection of pleasant sounds ringing out within the valley, culminating in a beautiful melody.

"What's this?" Han Li asked with an intrigued expression.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame basked in the sound with his eyes closed for a moment, then explained, "That's the Ethereal Bamboo Melody, which comes from the sound of the Ethereal Bamboo striking against each other in the wind. Listening to the melody for long periods of time can clear one's mind and calm one's heart."

"No wonder Patriarch Miro chose this place to go into seclusion, this is truly an exceptional place to be," Han Li praised.

"We're only at the entrance of the valley right now. Inside the valley is a type of spirit bird by the name of the Windchime Magpie. Their birdsong is very pleasant on the ears, and it forms a truly exquisite combination with the Ethereal Bamboo Melody," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a proud expression.

Not long after they entered the valley, Han Li spotted clusters of thin bamboo trees littered across the mountains on either side. The bamboo trees were thin and ramrod straight, and sure enough, they were gently crashing into each other in the wind to produce a beautiful melody.

The deeper they advanced into the valley, the denser the bamboo trees on either side became, until they took up virtually the entire valley. All that was available for Han Li's duo to walk on was a small stone path that was around six feet wide, leading deeper into the bamboo forest.

Sure enough, Han Li began to feel more and more at ease as he listened to the Ethereal Bamboo Melody, and the same applied to Immortal Lord Hot Flame as well.

After walking for over an hour, a cloud of murky mist emerged within the bamboo forest, causing the sound of the Ethereal Bamboo Melody to become slightly muffled.

Han Li peered into the mist, which was only growing denser and denser, and a hint of unease welled up in his heart.

He activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he swept his gaze over his surroundings, but his visibility was limited to no more than a thousand feet, beyond which he was unable to see anything.

What was even more alarming to him was that all of the Ethereal Bamboo deep within the mist had turned a strange gray color, and they weren't producing much sound as they tapped against each other.

"Something's very strange about this mist, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame. It's extremely restrictive on spiritual sense, and it also seems to be interspersed with some baleful qi. Could it be that we've unintentionally triggered some restriction in the valley?" Han Li asked with furrowed brows.

"Our patriarch once issued an order prohibiting the setup of restrictions in the Hidden Truth Valley, and disciples of our sect were free to enter the valley as they pleased, so I've been here many times. Occasionally, some mist would arise here, but it's always very thin, and I've never seen mist this dense and strange. Perhaps this mist only arose at some point after the sect's demise?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame speculated.

"In any case, it's definitely not a good thing that our spiritual sense has been so severely restricted, so we need to be on our guard," Han Li said with tightly furrowed brows.

Right at this moment, a loud explosion suddenly rang out, and hundreds of specks of green light suddenly emerged deep within the surrounding mist, then shot forth toward Han Li's duo from all directions.

"Look out!" Han Li yelled as he flipped a hand over to summon an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword with arcs of golden crackling all over its blade.

With a slash of his sword, the golden lightning converged to form a while that swept through the surrounding area.

At the same time, Immortal Lord Hot Flame summoned his golden mirror in one hand and a large crimson fan in the other before sweeping the fan toward the dozens of specks of green flames directly up ahead.

The whip formed by the Divine Devilbane Lightning swept through the air in front of Han Li in a golden arc, instantly striking the balls of ghostly flames amid a string of resounding booms.

Over a hundred balls of ghostly flames instantly exploded like overripe watermelons, but they didn't dissipate. Instead, they split up into countless fist-sized balls of fire that continued to hurtle toward Han Li's duo, although slightly slower than before.

At the same time, a series of fiery patterns lit up on the crimson fan, and crimson fireballs of a comparable size to the green fireballs shot forth before clashing against the green flames and exploding violently.

The green and crimson flames seemed to be able to cancel each other out, and one fireball after another was snuffed out as they clashed against one another.

"It looks like my flames can counteract these things, Fellow Daoist Li!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame yelled.

Han Li immediately sprang into action upon hearing this, summoning his Flame of Essence, which appeared on his shoulder in the form of a fiery silver figure.

The tiny figure stretched lazily as it inspected its surroundings, then turned to the surrounding green flames with an eager expression, looking as if it were raring for battle.

Chapter 680: Strange Beings

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of the silver figure's eager display, and he instructed, "Go!"

The silver figure immediately sprang into action, spreading its arms and transforming into a giant silver fire raven as it flew toward the oncoming wave of green fireballs.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame had his back facing Han Li, and he was given quite a fight by the scorching heat that erupted behind him. As he turned around, he caught sight of the silver figure transforming into a fire raven, and he exclaimed, "That's a Flame of Essence!"

An envious look then appeared on his face as he turned his gaze to Han Li, who paid no heed to his reaction.

He had already heard from Ma Liang about just how extraordinary his Essence Fire Raven was. It was an extremely rare being, even in the True Immortal Realm, and it had been a massive waste for him to use it solely for pill refinement all these years.

A string of loud explosions rang out as the Essence Fire Raven swept a wing through the air, releasing a burst of silver flames that caused the green fireballs to explode in rapid succession.

However, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this as just now, he had clearly sensed an emotion of disgust well up in the Essence Fire Raven's heart.

In the past, it had always been extremely excited to devour any new flame, yet this time, it was clearly averse to these green flames, and that was very abnormal.

As a safety precaution, Han Li hurriedly summoned the Essence Fire Raven back to his side, but to his surprise, it didn't immediately return to him. Instead, it continued to fly through the forest, eradicating all of the strange green fireballs while also evaporating much of the surrounding mist in the process.

Only then did Han Li discover that there were many strange figures littered throughout the forest, previously concealed by the mist.

Most of them were hunched over like elderly men, and behind them were seven or eight giant figures that were each over a hundred feet tall, with a series of sharp spikes all over their bodies.

At the center of these strange figures was another special figure who appeared to be no different from the average person. They seemed to be wearing a long robe, which was gently flapping in the wind.

The figures were all standing completely still within the mist, and it was as if they were one with the mist. If the Essence Fire Raven hadn't evaporated much of the surrounding mist, Han Li wouldn't have been able to detect them at all.

Right at this moment, the Essence Fire Raven flew back to Han Li's side, then landed on his shoulder after reverting back to its humanoid figure, and it was looking a little weary.

Han Li examined its condition and was relieved to find that it was only suffering from minor spiritual power overexertion.

"What are those things?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a puzzled expression as he retreated back to Han Li's side.

Han Li shook his head and offered no response.

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out up ahead.

"I was hoping that those Grave Oil Flames would've been enough to kill the two of you without your detection, but you're more alert than I expected..."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and he noticed that the one who had spoken was the robed figure at the center of the group.

"Who are you?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

The robed figure offered no response. Instead, it said something in a foreign language, and all of the figures enshrouded in the mist up ahead abruptly sprang into action.

Despite their hunched-over appearance, they were extremely agile, spreading themselves out before springing up into the air to rush over the tops of the bamboo trees, surrounding Han Li's duo from all directions.

Meanwhile, the giant figures behind them were even more direct, simply charging straight at Han Li's duo, destroying all of the bamboo trees in their path.

The only one who did nothing was the robed figure in the middle, who remained still and quickly vanished again into the converging mist.

"Here they come!" Han Li warned as he looked up into the sky with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame hurriedly looked up as well.

At this point, the hunched-over figures were already descending upon them, and they were revealed to be around a dozen ape-like creatures, but with completely hairless gray bodies.

On top of that, there seemed to be a pair of fleshy gray wings under their armpits, and they would spread those wings whenever they leaped through the air, allowing them to glide using the air currents.

As they drew close to Han Li's duo, the ape-like creatures launched themselves from the Ethereal Bamboo trees, and Han Li immediately stepped away to the side to evade their attacks.

A resounding boom rang out as the ape-like creature at the forefront of the group slammed forcefully into the ground, causing the earth to tremble and crack violently.

Han Li raised an eyebrow with a surprised expression.

These creatures weren't very large, but they were extremely fast and strong, but what was truly surprising to Han Li was the deathly gray color of their eyes.

Before he had a chance to think about anything else, several more figures came pouncing down at him from above, and all of them were wielding clubs that they were swinging at him from different directions.

Han Li raised a hand to summon two balls of lightning, one golden and one silver, and they flew up into the air before clashing against each other and exploding in unison.

A vast expanse of golden and silver lightning spread through the air, and from within it emerged a giant ring of golden lightning that erupted outward in the form of an incredibly formidable shockwave.

An acrid, charred odor instantly wafted through the air, and plumes of smoke rose up from the bodies of the ape-like creatures as they were sent flying back before tumbling toward the ground.

Meanwhile, the crimson fan in Immortal Lord Hot Flame's hand was flashing incessantly, and it was releasing a steady stream of fireballs to strike the ape-like creatures. However, he was also only able to keep them at bay, but was unable to inflict any severe injuries upon them.

Right at this moment, Han Li abruptly vanished from the spot, then appeared in front of one of the ape-like creatures that had just fallen to the ground before plunging his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword forcefully down toward it.

The creature was clearly quite startled by this, but it reacted very quickly, raising its gray club to defend itself.

The tip of Han Li's sword struck the gray club, and in the next instant, a faint crack rang out as the club split open to release a burst of dense, black baleful qi that surged directly toward Han Li's face.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he sent the ape-like creature flying with a kick, and it crashed into one of the oncoming giant figures.

The giant creature was over a hundred feet tall, and its entire body was covered in gray scales, much like those of a crocodile. Its head resembled that of a giant lizard, but it had no pupils, and its cavernous mouth was filled with sharp and serrated teeth.

It wasn't able to move very quickly with its short and stubby legs, and it swatted the oncoming ape-like creature away with its powerful arms, then opened its mouth to blast a giant green fireball directly at Han Li.

In response, Han Li raised a hand to pat the silver figure perched on his shoulder, and the latter immediately spread over his entire body like a film of liquid, forming a suit of fiery silver armor that left no part of his body exposed.

Han Li then grabbed onto the hilt of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword with both hands and stepped forward while channeling his Reversal True Axis, slicing the fireball into two with a single slash of his sword before bursting straight through it under the protection of his Flame of Essence.

A streak of golden light erupted out of the two halves of the fireball before striking the scaled creature, following which a large golden lock appeared around the creature's neck without any warning.

A burst of radiant golden light erupted out of the lock to form a giant golden rune, which emblazoned itself directly upon the creature's cheek, and it was instantly completely immobilized and rooted to the spot.

Han Li continued to rush at the creature as arcs of golden lightning began to emerge over his sword, and a drop of golden liquid emerged at its tip as he thrust it toward the creature's head.

Right as the tip of the sword was about to pierce into the creature's head, a burst of green light suddenly erupted out of the creature's mouth, even though it had already been immobilized by the golden lock.

The burst of green light sprang forth as a green fireball, and at this point, Han Li was too close to the creature to take evasive measures.

Hence, he could only allow the fireball to strike him on the chest, and he was sent flying back like a cannonball before crashing heavily down onto the ground.

The green flames immediately reared up in an attempt to spread over the rest of his body, but they were instantly snuffed out by the Flame of Essence around him.

Han Li rose up from the ground, then took a glance at Immortal Lord Hot Flame, who was being attacked by around a dozen ape-like creatures and one of the giant scaled creatures. Despite this, he appeared to be quite calm and composed.

He then turned to look at the scaled beast that had been immobilized by the golden lock immortal treasure, and he discovered that there was currently a white-robed human-looking young man standing on its shoulder, looking at him with a faint smile on his face.

This was the mysterious robed figure that had been enshrouded in mist earlier.

At first glance, he appeared to be very handsome, but there was something strange about his appearance, as if his face had been pieced together by different facial features taken from different people, presenting a very unbalanced and disharmonious appearance. What was even more surprising to Han Li was that his eyes were gray in color, indicating that he was a Gray Immortal.

Chapter 681: Creatures of the Gray Realm

"This is the first time I've fought humans, and I was rather curious, so I decided to observe for a while. Your companion over there isn't really remarkable in any way, but you're rather interesting. I can sense an aura of our kind within you," the white-robed man said.

Han Li offered no response as he continued to stare intently at the white-robed man.

He noticed that there was a layer of faint gray light over his body, and the aura that was emanating from it was very similar to Mo Yu's.

"You're not going to say anything? I've heard that your Immortal Realm has always seen our Gray Realm as a primordial land filled with barbaric and unintelligent beasts, but from what I've seen, it seems like your kind is nothing special," the white-robed man sneered in a derisive fashion.

After that, he sat down onto the shoulder of the scaled beast, and a layer of gray light appeared over his hand as he pressed his palm onto the golden lock around the creature's neck. The golden light radiating from the lock immediately dimmed slightly, as if it were being suppressed.

A layer of faint gray light then appeared over the scaled beast's body, and it was able to move again.

How is he suppressing the time law powers in the lock? Han Li thought to himself with a bewildered expression.

Before he had a chance to ponder this matter any further, the dozen or so ape-like creatures around him came pouncing at him once again.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce the gourd that contained his Dao Warriors, then tossed it up into the air before casting an incantation seal onto it.

Numerous dark yellow beans instantly shot out of the mouth of the gourd amid a flash of yellow light, and they transformed into hundreds of Dao Warriors before rushing at the ape-like creatures.

"Oh? This is what your kind refers to as Dao Warriors, right? How interesting," the white robed young man remarked with an intrigued expression.

"There's no need to protect me anymore, go and help Fellow Daoist Hot Flame," Han Li said to the Essence Fire Raven.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the suit of fiery silver armor on his body instantly receded before reverting back into a silver fire raven that was perched on his shoulder. After that, it spread its wings and let loose a clear cry as it flew toward Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

At this moment, Immortal Lord Hot Flame had his hands full dealing with the scaled beasts and the ape-like creatures, and if it weren't for the slowing effect of his golden mirror, he would've most likely already been defeated.

Only after receiving reinforcements in the form of the Essence Fire Raven and a large number of Dao Warriors was he finally able to catch his breath and take a glance in Han Li's direction.

At this moment, Han Li and the white-robed young man were still observing each other from afar, and neither of them was in a hurry to attack.

"I hear that you Gray Immortals have cultivation arts that allow one to integrate baleful qi into their body, do you have any cultivation arts to expel baleful qi?" Han Li suddenly asked.

The white-robed young man was initially rather taken aback by this question, but a thought then occurred to him, and he erupted into laughter.

"No wonder there's so much baleful qi in your body, you must've somehow gotten your hands on one of our cultivation arts, right?"

Looks like it'll be faster to just search his soul...

With that in mind, Han Li sprang up into the air, then channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, and he instantly vanished from the spot.

The white-robed young man faltered slightly upon seeing this, and only then did he realize that Han Li had intentionally concealed his own power and was now moving far faster than before.

A burst of bright gray light appeared in his eyes as he clenched his fists tightly and let loose a loud roar.

A layer of dense baleful qi erupted out of his back like a giant black shield right as Han Li appeared behind him, and Han Li's sword struck the baleful qi shield with a resounding clang before being repelled upward.

With a wave of his hand, the golden lock around the scaled beast's neck lit up, then shrank down rapidly before locking itself around the Gray Immortal's ankle, upon which a golden rune appeared on his chest.

The Gray Immortal's body instantly stiffened, while the black baleful shield behind him also fell completely still.

Despite this, Han Li didn't immediately rush in for the kill. Instead, he flipped a hand over to summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd, and he aimed the mouth of the gourd directly at the Gray Immortal, upon which the spirit patterns on the surface of the gourd lit up in unison.

Immediately thereafter, he thrust the palm of his hand firmly into the underside of the gourd, and a green vortex appeared at its mouth, following which a burst of tremendous power erupted forth from within.

The Gray Immortal's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he no longer pretended to be immobilized as he flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized black badge, then tossed it upward, and the badge instantly rose up into the air before swelling to the size of a shield.

A head of a beast that Han Li had never seen before was engraved onto the badge, and its eyes suddenly began to glow with dark red light as if it had sprung to life.

At the same time, it opened its mouth to reveal a crimson vortex, which was giving off bursts of peculiar energy fluctuations.

A low roar rang out from within the crimson vortex, following which it released a burst of radiant crimson light, which struck the oncoming Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, and a loud clang rang out as the azure light around the sword faded.

The flying sword was stopped cold in its tracks, while the burst of crimson light was also shattered and swept back into the badge.

At this point, the Gray Immortal had finally realized that his human was not going to be a pushover as he expected, and a serious look had appeared on his face to replace his previous mocking sneer.

With a flick of his wrist, a burst of gray light appeared over his hand, and it was as if he had put on an extremely thin gray glove.

He grabbed onto the golden lock around his ankle, and the golden light around the lock flickered erratically before fading altogether, following which it was forced open with a faint crack.

After summoning his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword back to himself, Han Li took a deep breath as a surprised look appeared on his face.

He had no idea how this Gray Immortal was able to suppress the law powers contained within a ninth grade immortal treasure.

He took a glance at Immortal Lord Hot Flame to find that with the assistance of the Essence Fire Raven and the Dao Warriors, he had already managed to slay several of the ape-like creatures, but he was still locked in a fierce battle against the remaining ape-like creatures and the scaled beasts.

Han Li didn't know if the Gray Immortal had any allies nearby, or any reinforcements on the way, so he had to end this battle quickly.

With that in mind, he immediately released his golden spirit domain, but only to the point that it encompassed himself and the Gray Immortal, as well as the scaled beast beneath the latter.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li channeled his Mantra Domain ability and declared, "Positional shift..."

Before the white-robed young man had a chance to do anything, he and Han Li somehow switched positions, and he was hovering in mid-air in the spot where Han Li had just been standing a moment ago, while Han Li was standing on the shoulder of the scaled beast.

From there, Han Li sliced off the scaled beast's head with a swing of his sword, sending large volumes of green blood splattering in all directions.

Some of the blood sprayed onto the white-robed young man's face, and he wiped it from his cheek with his hand to find that it was warm and sticky, seemingly not an illusion.

A hint of panic finally flashed through his eyes at the sight of Han Li, and right at this moment, Han Li spoke once again.

"Decapitate..."

A faint thud rang out, and the white-robed young man felt a cold sensation on his neck, following which the world began to spin around him.

His head had already been separated from his body, and as it tumbled toward the ground, it let loose a scream of horror and indignation.

A streak of silver light instantly shot out of his eyes, then transformed into a tiny silver figure that was around three inches tall. The silver figure had a set of indistinct facial features, and immediately attempted to flee the scene.

However, it had only just flown out of the Gray Immortal's body when it discovered that its physical body was still standing on the scaled beast's shoulder, and it hadn't been decapitated at all.

Only then did it realize that it had fallen prey to an illusion.

A look of alarm and fury appeared on the tiny silver figure's face as it attempted to fly back into its body, but right at this moment, a golden vortex appeared behind the silver figure without any warning, and it was instantly rooted to the spot.

However, instead of allowing the vortex to devour the silver figure, Han Li flew onto the scene and grabbed onto the silver figure, following which a translucent thread shot out of his glabella as he prepared to forcibly search the silver figure's soul.

The silver struggled violently for a short while, but after realizing that its struggles were futile, a burst of gray light suddenly appeared on its abdomen.

Han Li's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly tried to place a restriction upon the silver figure, but it was already too late, and it exploded with a dull thump.

A resigned look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and began to fly back down toward the scaled beast.

To his surprise, the scaled beast had sensed the demise of its master, and it immediately opened its mouth to try and devour the Gray Immortal's body whole.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as three balls of golden lightning emerged from the tip of his sword, and he swooped down from above before slashing his sword at the scaled beast.

A resounding boom rang out as the scaled beast's body was sliced into two alongside the ground beneath it, and green flames erupted in all directions, while its green blood gushed onto the ground.

With a flick of his wrist, Han Li drew the Gray Immortal's body to himself, and after conducting a search, he was unable to find the black badge that the Gray Immortal had used before. However, he did find a white bone bracelet on his wrist.

Is this a storage tool?

Han Li attempted to refine the bracelet, but it displayed no reaction, so he slipped it onto his own wrist for now.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to open the Flower Branch domain, then tossed the body of the Gray Immortal onto the first floor of the pavilion where Mo Guang was staying.

Immediately thereafter, he closed the domain and withdrew his spirit domain before rushing over to Immortal Lord Hot Flame's side.

It didn't take very long at all for the two of them to eradicate all of the remaining enemies, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame's brows were tightly furrowed as he stared at all of the bodies strewn over the ground.

"Are these beings all from the Gray Realm?"

Chapter 682: First Signs of Unrest

"I believe so. The man that I just fought against was a Gray Immortal, so it stands to reason that these creatures were all from the Gray Realm as well. Should we continue our search, or get out of this place for now, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li asked.

"At this point, will you really be content with turning back without getting to the bottom of this?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a wry smile.

"I suppose we don't have a choice in the matter then, do we?" Han Li chuckled.

The two of them took a moment to rest then continued to make their way deeper into the valley, but they had only walked for a few hundred meters before they spotted a circular array that was around a hundred feet in size on the ground.

The array was constructed out of white stone blocks of different shapes, and there were plumes of gray mist rising up out of it, while spatial fluctuations could be detected around the array.

"I'm assuming this array wasn't always here, right, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"I've never seen this array before, and there's no way that our True Mantra Sect would've set up this array," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied with a shake of his head.

"In that case, those people from the Gray Realm were most likely responsible," Han Li said.

"I've heard that the interrealm barrier between the Gray Realm and the True Immortal Realm is notoriously difficult to break through, how were those Gray Realm beings able to get here? Could it be that they relied solely on this array?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame mused.

"That's not very likely. I can sense spatial fluctuations here, but they're not very strong, nowhere near strong enough to break through an interrealm barrier. On top of that, the array doesn't look very complete, either. Instead, it looks like a part of a larger spatial array. If you ask me, those Gray Realm beings most likely came in from elsewhere," Han Li said with a thoughtful look in his eyes.

"You're saying that only a small part of this array has been set up?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

"The array here is most likely an important point in a larger array, and the Gray Realm beings that we encountered could've been assigned here to protect this location. Once the entire array is complete, it's very likely that they'll be able to establish a passageway that connects the Gray Realm to the True Immortal Realm," Han Li elaborated.

"If that's true, then our True Immortal Realm is about to face a calamitous disaster!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame exclaimed.

"I wouldn't go that far. The Gray Realm beings most likely chose the True Mantra Sect ruins as an incision point as they somehow discovered that the space here is very chaotic, thereby making it far easier to access from the Gray Realm. However, what they don't know is that the spatial balance here is extremely fragile, so it most likely won't be able to withstand the establishment of a large-scale spatial passageway," Han Li said.

"So you're saying that if they forcibly set up a spatial passageway here, then this space will collapse?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with a concerned expression.

"I've witnessed more than my fair share of collapsed spaces in the past. The spatial balance here is already very tenuous, and if the balance is broken collapse is almost certainly imminent," Han Li replied with a solemn expression.

"In that case, we have to make haste and find the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra as soon as possible, then leave this place right away," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said.

"Now that even Gray Realm beings have entered these ruins, we really do have to hurry. Otherwise, if we encounter more powerful Gray Immortals, then we may not be so lucky to emerge alive," Han Li agreed.

With that, the two of them disassembled the white stone array and split the materials between each other.

After that, they scoured the valley, upon which they discovered that the cave abode that Patriarch Miro had once cultivated in had already been destroyed, presumably during the battle that led to the demise of the sect.

Hence, they could only leave the valley and travel to the True Mantra Palace according to Immortal Lord Hot Flame's recollection of its location.

......

While Han Li's duo was being attacked by the Gray Realm beings, the battle between Shi Chuankong's trio and the two immortal envoys was drawing to a close. They valley was completely unrecognizable, with both of the mountains at its entrance completely collapsed, and a series of giant craters had appeared on the plaza within the valley.

There were two people standing on one of the few relatively intact spots in the valley, and they were Shi Chuankong and Feng Lin.

Both of them were looking rather pale, and they had sustained some substantial injuries. In particular, Feng Lin was as pale as a sheet, and even the veil on her face couldn't disguise her horrible complexion.

There were three broken bodies laying on the ground next to the two of them, and two of those bodies belonged to none other than Zhao Zhen and Lu Wuliang.

Both of them had been decapitated, and the cuts were extremely smooth.

The final body belonged to Zi Qing, and his entire body was a strange, dark purple color. His skin was occasionally bursting open, and whenever this happened, dark purple blood would spray out in all directions.

As soon as the blood droplets fell onto the ground, a faint sizzling sound would ring out as they easily corroded tiny holes into the ground.

At this moment, Zi Qing's nascent soul was hovering in the air above the body, and it was looking down at its ruined physical body with a disgruntled look on its face.

"I didn't think that Zhao Zhen would have such a vicious technique up his sleeve. Looks like your body's beyond saving, Zi Qing," Feng Lin remarked with a hint of schadenfreude in her voice.

A hint of fury flashed through the eyes of Zi Qing's nascent soul upon hearing this, and it turned to give Feng Lin a vicious glare.

"Don't worry about your body, Zi Qing. You've made a significant contribution in killing those two immortal envoys. Once we return to the Devil Realm, I'll find a suitable body for you to possess, and I'll also ask Father to grant you permission to cultivate in the Devilish Origin Holy Pond. You'll be back to your peak in no more than ten thousand years, and perhaps you could even go beyond your former peak," Shi Chuankong said.

The fury on Zi Qing's face instantly turned to elation upon hearing this.

"Thank you, Young Master!"

"In your current state, you're no longer fit for battle, so just stay and recuperate in this Devilform Gourd for now," Shi Chuankong said as he summoned a black gourd, and a burst of black light surged out of the gourd at his behest to envelop Zi Qing's nascent soul before sucking it into the gourd.

"You did very well, too, Feng Lin. You'll also be rewarded once we return to the Devil Realm," Shi Chuankong said as he flipped a hand over to stow the gourd away.

"Thank you, Young Master!" Feng Lin immediately replied with a hint of elation on her face.

"We've already wasted a lot of time here, so let's clean up the battlefield, then continue onward," Shi Chuankong said.

Feng Lin naturally raised no objections to this, and she began to fly toward the edge of the valley, while Shi Chuankong made his way over to the bodies of the two immortal envoys before looking down at them with a contemplative expression.

Right at this moment, the space outside the valley abruptly shuddered, and strange specks of gray light appeared, following which a thin gray rift emerged without any warning.

Boundless gray mist surged out of the rift and into the valley, instantly filling the nearby area, and it was quickly expanding toward the rest of the valley.

Shi Chuankong's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he made a hand seal, upon which a glowing purple ring shot out of his body, then hovered above his head, raining down rays of purple light to protect him.

Feng Ling also immediately noticed that something was amiss, and she hurriedly returned to Shi Chuankong's side, following which a large purple flag appeared around her.

The nearby gray mist was quickly becoming denser and denser, and ghostly howls were ringing out within it alongside arcs of gray lightning that were flashing incessantly, presenting a peculiar sight to behold.

"Young Master, we have to get out of here! This is the same gray mist that swallowed up Elder Jing!" Feng Lin said with a solemn expression.

"Let's go!"

Shi Chuankong immediately raised a hand without any hesitation upon hearing this, conjuring up a ball of purple light that enveloped them both before speeding away into the distance.

Almost at the exact same moment, a thick bolt of gray lightning shot out of the gray mist, instantly covering a distance of tens of thousands of feet before striking the purple light at an incredible speed.

A loud thump rang out as the purple light exploded, and Shi Chuankong and Feng Lin were struck out of the sky before slamming down onto the ground.

Feng Lin seemed to have been struck by the bolt of lightning, and she threw up a mouthful of blood, which stained the veil over her face red, following which she fell unconscious.

"Feng Lin!"

As soon as Shi Chuankong steadied himself, he noticed that Feng Lin had fallen unconscious, and he hurriedly released a burst of purple light out of his hand to raise up her body so that he could administer some treatment.

Right at this moment, four gray humanoid figures shot out of the gray mist before pouncing at Shi Chuankong and Feng Lin.

These figures were all dressed in gray robes, and they were led by a short figure who possessed a gray, skeletal body as opposed to a body of flesh and blood.

The other three figures behind him all had normal bodies of flesh, and one of them was a young man in a suit of gray armor. He was holding a purple spear, and his long, silver hair was dancing in the wind behind him, adding a sense of flair to his already handsome appearance. However, his murky, gray eyes presented a rather jarring sight to behold.

There was also a tall and beautiful young woman whose exceptional figure showed through even her loose-fitting robe, and as she flew through the air, she was taking occasional glances at the silver-haired young man.

The final figure to round out the trio was a gray-robed elderly man who was quite hideous in appearance, and there was a cold look in his murky, gray eyes.

Trailing along in the gray mist behind them were a variety of gray demon beasts, including lions, tigers, wolves, and apes, and all of them were enormous.

As soon as Shi Chuankong caught sight of the four figures, he immediately identified them as Gray Immortals.

It was naturally quite alarming to see Gray Immortals here, but he remained calm and composed as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing four palm-sized black talismans that were giving off extremely formidable lightning law power fluctuations and devilish qi fluctuations.

A resounding boom rang out as all four of the black talismans exploded in unison, transforming into four thick bolts of black lightning that crashed down upon the four Gray Immortals.

Chapter 683: True Mantra Palace

"Don't let this battle drag on!" the gray skeleton leading from the forefront said in a raspy voice.

At the same time, a bone staff appeared in his grasp amid a flash of gray light, and he swept the staff through the air to release a long streak of gray light, which swept up the four bolts of black lightning unleashed by Shi Chuankong.

As soon as the bolts of lightning came into contact with the streak of gray light, they instantly vanished without a trace, but at the same time, most of the streak of gray light also dissipated.

A stunned look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon seeing this, and he held Feng Lin in his arms as he darted away into the distance as a streak of purple light.

The gray skeleton swept his staff through the air once again, and what remained of the streak of gray light immediately shot forth in hot pursuit.

At the same time, the other three Gray Immortals also sprang into action. The gray-haired young man thrust his spear forward, and a thick gray dragon of light shot out of the tip of the spear.

The young woman flipped a hand over to summon a gray whip, using which she released a thick gray whip projection, while the gray-robed elderly man opened his mouth to release a long streak of gray light.

The four bursts of gray light quickly intertwined to form a large gray net that caught up to Shi Chuankong in a flash.

Faint gray flames were drifting over the net as it fell upon Shi Chuankong and Feng Lin at an alarming speed, and in response, Shi Chuankong opened his mouth to release a ball of black light before casting an incantation seal into it.

The ball of black light instantly transformed into a short black halberd that shot forth upward, and engraved onto the front of the halberd was a fearsome-looking dragon's head that was giving off tremendous devilish qi.

A fierce look then appeared on his face, and with a flick of his wrist, the black halberd swelled to around a thousand feet in size while releasing a high-pitched shriek.

Countless bursts of black light erupted out of the giant black halberd, and in particular, the dragon head design on its tip was flashing incessantly as if it were about to spring to life.

The giant halberd was imbued with tremendous power, slicing through the very space in its path as it crashed heavily down upon the gray net, but the net only trembled slightly before withstanding the attack with ease.

However, it had been slowed down slightly in its descent.

Shi Chuankong was astonished to see this. This Devilish Dragon Halberd was a vastly renowned weapon in the Devil Realm, yet it wasn't even able to put a scratch on the gray net!

Right at this moment, the gray skeleton swept his staff through the air a third time, releasing a burst of gray flames that vanished into the gray net.

The gray flames on the net instantly reared up, then transformed into countless thin strands of gray fire that wrapped themselves around the giant halberd.

Ensnared by the gray flames, the black halberd rapidly shrank back down to its original size, and the devilish light emanating from it also quickly faded as if it were being corroded, while the dragon head design engraved upon it let loose an agonized howl.

The gray net shuddered slightly before continuing to descend, and a grim look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon seeing this, following which he gritted his teeth as he made a hand seal.

The black halberd immediately began to radiate blinding black light before exploding with a resounding boom, and a massive ball of black light emerged from the explosion.

Numerous black dragon projections erupted out of the ball of black light before flying away in all directions, and the surrounding space warped violently as countless spatial rifts emerged.

Bursts of spatial turbulence seeped in through the rifts, forming gusts of ferocious silver wind that swept through the surrounding area.

The gray net was once again stopped cold in its tracks by the black dragon projections and the gusts of silver wind, following which it was sent flying upward.

The detonation of the black halberd had unleashed devastating power, and many of the black dragon projections and gusts of silver wind were able to force their way through the gray net to strike the four Gray Immortals behind it.

The gray skeleton was unleashing one secret technique after another, and it seemed that he was struggling to withstand the onslaught.

Right at this moment, the gray-haired young man stepped forward, and the purple spear in his hand glowed radiantly before releasing countless spear projections like a peacock spreading its canopy.

A string of dull thumps rang out in rapid succession as most of the oncoming assault was counteracted by the spear projections, and the residual shockwaves were enough to force the four Gray Immortals back a few steps, but all of them remained completely unscathed.

Taking advantage of this opportunity, Shi Chuankong opened his mouth to release a burst of silver light, which swept up himself and Feng Lin, then transformed into a silver shuttle projection that split up into hundreds of identical versions of itself before flying away in different directions, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

The four of them chose not to give chase upon seeing this, and the gray demon beasts behind them also drew to a halt.

"He got away so fast!" the gray-robed elderly man exclaimed with a stunned expression.

"He seems to have unleashed a spatial law ability at the end, so it won't be easy to catch him. What do we do now, Mr. Gu?" the gray-haired young man asked as he turned to the gray skeleton.

The skeleton didn't immediately respond. Instead, he swept his staff through the air, and the gray net instantly spread open.

He then flipped a hand over to produce a small gray plate, hovering above which were five gray bone badges, each of which carried a projection of a miniature humanoid figure.

One of the bone badges was already broken and had fallen onto the plate.

"What? Fang Jin is already dead?! How is that possible? As arrogant as he may be, he's at the mid-High Zenith Stage and has two silver lizards at his disposal! How could he have been killed?" the young woman exclaimed with an incredulous expression.

"All of the people who've entered the True Mantra Sect ruins are powerful figures of the True Immortal Realm. We just encountered someone capable of wielding spatial law powers, did we not? Fang Jin is indeed quite powerful, but he's always been very arrogant. He insisted on acting alone in this mission, and his decision has caught up with him," the gray-robed elderly man sneered.

"How could you say that, Gui Tian? Fang Jin was our ally, yet here you are, all but celebrating his death!" the young woman accused in an appalled voice.

The gray-robed elderly man made no attempt to defend himself. Instead, he merely took a glance at the young woman, particularly making it a point out of having his gaze linger on her voluptuous breasts.

The young woman was furious to see this, yet before she had a chance to say anything, the gray skeleton said, "That's enough! We're carrying out a mission right now, so we can't afford to get distracted."

"You're right, Mr. Gu," the gray-robed elderly man hurriedly replied with a nod, but there was still a sly grin playing on his lips.

The gray-haired young man made a calming gesture at the young woman, and she took a deep breath to suppress her fury.

"Seeing as Fang Jin is dead, the array where he is has most likely been destroyed as well. How do we proceed from here, Mr. Gu?" the gray-haired young man asked.

The gray skeleton considered the question for a moment, then turned to look behind himself before sweeping a sleeve through the air to release a burst of gray light, which quickly carried the bodies of Zhao Zhen and Lu Wuliang back to him.

He examined the two bodies momentarily, then stowed them away before swinging his staff through the air.

The gray mist behind him instantly began to churn violently as it swept forward in a frenzy, swallowing up all of the gray demon beasts.

After that, the gray mist continued onward without pause, encompassing the four Gray Immortals as well, then sped forward as an all-devouring gray wave, seemingly in pursuit of Shi Chuankong's duo.

......

Elsewhere in the True Mantra Sect ruins, Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame were flying through the air over a swamp as two streaks of light.

There were numerous pools and puddles littered throughout the swamp, and occasionally, plumes of purple mist would rise up from within it, similar to the illusory smoke of the Illusory Smoke Swamp, except this mist was only a normal miasma with no illusory qualities.

"The True Mantra Palace is not far up ahead. It was another place where our patriarch often went into seclusion," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said.

"That means that it could be where the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra is hidden, right?" Han Li asked.

"Yes, but it's only a possibility. Having said that, even if the cultivation art isn't hidden there, there should be some other treasures inside. I hope they haven't been destroyed," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied.

"Many powers have made their way into these ruins. Right now, even the Gray Immortals have shown up here to complicate things even further, so we should speed up a little more to avoid trouble as much as possible," Han Li said.

"I agree, but just because this place looks safe doesn't mean that there aren't any hidden spatial rifts nearby. If we recklessly speed up without discretion, we could be subjecting ourselves to a great deal of risk," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied in a concerned manner.

"It's fine, my spirit eyes can see through those hidden spatial rifts," Han Li said as he made a hand seal, and a series of purple patterns emerged over his body, giving off formidable devilish qi.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, but Han Li paid no heed to his reaction as bright purple light emerged within his eyes before projecting outward to form two beams of purple light that were around a foot in length.

Countless purple runes were flashing within the beams of purple light, and there were also countless specks of purple radiance dancing within his eyes, presenting a profound sight to behold.

"Alright, let's go," Han Li said as he sped up significantly, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame hurriedly followed along.

The two of them flew for close to another two hours, and the swamp down below gradually faded, replaced by a vast sea.

This area of the sea was quite cold, and occasionally, snow could be seen falling from the sky. Large chunks of ice had also taken shape on the surface of the sea, reflecting the light of the sun in beautiful ways.

Upon arriving at the sea, Immortal Lord Hot Flame pulled out a plate treasure, seemingly to ascertain their current location, then flew away in a certain direction.

The two of them flew onward for a while longer when an island that was close to ten thousand kilometers in size suddenly appeared up ahead.

From afar, one could see a huge mountain at the center of the island. The mountain was as straight and sharp as a giant white sword, and on the mountain summit was a huge palace that was as pristine white as jade.

The palace seemed to have been constructed out of some type of white jade material, and rays of white light were occasionally rising up from it, presenting a majestic sight to behold.

In contrast with the destroyed palaces that Han Li's duo had encountered up to this point, this palace was completely unscathed.

There was a huge plaque hanging up the entrance of the palace that read "True Mantra Palace" in large, golden characters that were glowing radiantly under the light of the sun.

Chapter 684: Loss of Contact

"This is great! This place has been perfectly preserved!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame exclaimed in a celebratory voice.

"The surroundings of this palace have been tampered with, so I don't think it'll be easy to enter the palace," Han Li mused as he inspected the area around the palace with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

"Indeed, our sect's Heaven and Earth Dust Array has been set up around the True Mantra Palace. It's one of our sect's most powerful concealed arrays, and even High Zenith Stage beings struggle to detect it, so it's very impressive that you were able to see it right away!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame said in a surprised voice as he took an extra glance at Han Li's glowing purple eyes.

"You sound very confident, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame. Could it be that you already have a way to bypass the array?" Han Li asked as the purple light in his eyes faded.

"For an outsider, bypassing the array would be near impossible, but you can count on me to get us through, Fellow Daoist Li," Immortal Lord Hot Flame assured with a smile.

Immediately thereafter, he flipped a hand over to produce a silver jade plate before tossing it upward, and at the same time, he cast an incantation seal into the jade plate with his other hand.

Bright silver light instantly rose up from the surface of the jade plate, and it transformed into a ball of silver light that descended to encompass Han Li's duo.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame then began to chant an incantation before pointing at the palace up ahead from afar, and the ball of silver light instantly flew away in that direction at a rather lethargic pace.

After flying for a short distance, the space around the ball of silver light suddenly began to buzz, following which a series of criss-crossing streaks of white light emerged.

These streaks of white light varied in length and size, and they were distributed throughout an area in a radius of close to ten kilometers around the True Mantra Palace, taking on all types of different permutations.

Han Li observed the white light with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and he discovered that this was only the very surface of the array, while the permutations deeper inside were even more complex.

Through the use of his Infernal Devilish Eyes, he was able to see countless specks of white light of different sizes in the surrounding space, presenting a resplendent sight to behold.

However, if he were to focus his gaze on any individual speck of light, then he would discover that it encompassed a tiny, independent world that contained all types of living creatures, the sky, the sea... It was all extremely realistic and profound.

Han Li was surprised to discover that the array was even more profound than he imagined.

These specks of light appeared to all be independent, but some type of connection existed between all of them, and if any of them were to clash against each other, then the entire array would instantly be activated to eradicate the intruder.

Despite the confidence with which Immortal Lord Hot Flame had spoken with earlier, he was proceeding with extreme caution, meticulously controlling the ball of silver light as it weaved through the specks of white light.

After close to two hours, the two of them had only covered about half the distance through the array.

All of a sudden, the array up ahead changed once again, and a series of balls of black light emerged before revolving on the spot while releasing waves of black ripples.

As these ripples gradually expanded outward, the scene up ahead gradually took on an indistinct appearance, and a menacing atmosphere arose in the air.

"The second half of this array is even more difficult to deal with. I'll need to be fully focused, so make sure that you absolutely do not distract me, Fellow Daoist Li," Immortal Lord Hot Flame warned.

Han Li nodded in response, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame knew that Han Li was a reliable person, so he had only issued this warning as a safety precaution.

He took a deep breath, yet right as he was about to direct the ball of silver light onward, the black ripples up ahead were suddenly thrown into complete disarray before rapidly fading away.

The balls of black light also shrank down significantly, and the space up ahead was instantly cleared, allowing Han Li's duo to see the gates of the True Mantra Palace.

In the array behind them, all of the white light also quickly faded, and it was as if the array had somehow been suddenly deactivated.

Both Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame were quite taken aback to see this, but the latter reacted very quickly, pouncing on this opportunity to accelerate the ball of silver light drastically.

In the span of just a few seconds, it passed through the rest of the array before arriving at the gates of the True Mantra Palace.

"What happened just now?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

"I'm assuming the core of this array must be in the True Mantra Palace, so I can only assume that something's happened in there," Han Li speculated.

"Could it be that someone has already gotten here before us?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked as he also hurriedly cast his gaze toward the palace.

From afar, the gates of the True Mantra Palace hadn't appeared all that large, but only now that they were standing directly before them did he truly come to realize just how enormous they were.

Standing in front of the palace gates, the two of them were made to look like a pair of tiny ants, and they could see a long passageway beyond the entrance of the palace, but for some reason,the passageway was very dimly lit.

Even with his exceptional eyesight, Han Li was only able to see just over a hundred feet into the palace from the entrance, and the darkness inside struck him with a peculiar sense of foreboding.

He attempted to extend his spiritual sense into the passageway, only for it to be instantly repelled by a burst of invisible force.

His brows furrowed slightly as he turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame with an inquisitive expression.

"Don't look at me, Fellow Daoist Li, this is my first time here as well. I only know the way to traverse through the Heaven and Earth Dust Array outside as I just so happened to see the array diagram once," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a shrug.

"Well, we certainly can't turn back at this point, so let's go in," Han Li said, then stepped into the palace, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame hurriedly followed along.

There seemed to be some type of special restriction set up within the passageway, and no matter what light sources Han Li's duo tried to use to illuminate the path ahead, they were only able to see less than two hundred feet up ahead at most.

Beyond that point, everything was enshrouded in darkness.

The area was deathly silent with the exception of their footsteps, and even after they had been walking for fifteen minutes, there was still no sign that they were approaching the end of the passageway.

As a safety precaution, neither of them dared to speed up, and they continued at a slow and steady pace.

The complete silence and suffocating darkness culminated in a very unsettling environment, and before long, Immortal Lord Hot Flame's breathing was beginning to become a little labored.

Even Han Li was gradually becoming more and more flustered as they continued down the seemingly never-ending path.

Right at this moment, the sound of faint sobbing rang out up ahead.

Han Li immediately stopped cold in his tracks as he channeled his immortal spiritual power, but the sound up ahead abruptly faded as if it had been nothing more than a figment of his imagination.

"Did you hear that, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li asked as he turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame, only to discover that he was no longer there.

"Fellow Daoist Hot Flame!" Han Li called out as he injected some of his immortal spiritual power into his voice, causing the nearby ground and walls to tremble violently.

However, there was still no response, and it was as if Immortal Lord Hot Flame had truly vanished.

Have I fallen into an illusion?

Han Li's expression darkened slightly as he channeled the immense spiritual power in his mind, but he couldn't sense anything to indicate that he had fallen prey to an illusion.

"Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, can you..."

All of a sudden, his voice trailed off there as he discovered that his connection with Mo Guang had completely faded.

It seemed that his spiritual sense had been sealed by some type of mysterious power, restricting it strictly to the confines of his mind.

Not only had his connection with the Flower Branch domain been severed, the same applied to all of his other storage tools as well.

It wasn't clear whether he had fallen under any illusion, but at this point, Han Li knew that he had to have triggered some type of restriction in the passageway.

He looked forward and back with a hesitant expression for a moment, then suddenly quickened his pace as he continued onward.

He had already been walking down the passageway for a long time, so turning back now would be a huge waste. On top of that, he didn't know if he would be able to turn back and leave even if he wanted to.

A short while later, a burst of black light suddenly emerged up ahead. It was an arrow of black light that was racing through the air at an astonishing speed, hurtling directly toward his chest.

He only had less than two hundred feet of visibility, but his reactions were extremely sharp, and he was able to sidestep the arrow with ease.

The arrow continued to pierce into the darkness behind him, quickly vanishing out of sight.

"Who's there?" Han Li roared as he stopped in his tracks.

The entire passageway rumbled violently for a long while before settling down again, and no response rang out from up ahead.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as he continued onward, but he had only taken a few more steps when another arrow of black light shot out of the darkness, hurtling toward him at the same speed as the previous one.

A perplexed look flashed through his eyes upon seeing this. No matter how many more of these arrows were sent flying at him, they were simply not fast or powerful enough to pose a threat, so what was the point?

With that in mind, he was just about to dodge to the side when all of a sudden, the only remaining light in the surrounding area abruptly faded, plunging him into complete darkness.

A piercing shriek rang out, and Han Li gave a muffled groan as he stumbled a couple of steps backward.

Due to the sudden onset of darkness, he had been a split second too slow to react, and as a result, the second arrow had managed to glance his shoulder.

Even though it was only a glancing blow, Han Li felt as if someone had pierced a red-hot dagger viciously into his soul, inflicting excruciating pain.

Han Li suppressed the frustration in his heart as he hurriedly channeled his immortal spiritual power to try and conjure up some azure light to illuminate the darkness, but no matter what light sources he tried to summon, the surrounding darkness refused to fade, leaving him unable to see or sense anything.

Chapter 685: Loss of All Six Senses

Is the restriction here devouring all light? No, the problem is that my eyes can no longer see!

As soon as this realization dawned on him, a grim look instantly appeared on Han Li's face.

At this moment, he was unable to release his spiritual sense, and his eyesight had been sealed, leaving him completely vulnerable, should there be any more arrows coming his way.

Sure enough, as soon as this thought sprang into his mind, another piercing shriek rang out up ahead.

Han Li hurriedly turned to use his hearing to determine the direction that the arrow was coming from, then attempted to sidestep the projectile, but a cold sensation flashed over his lower abdomen, followed by a burst of intense pain that caused him to give another muffled groan.

Han Li laid a hand onto his lower abdomen to find that a large chunk of flesh was missing there, seemingly having been eaten away by something.

He immediately channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts, and bursts of cool energy surged toward the wounds on his shoulder and his lower abdomen from his thirty-six profound acupoints.

After mastering the Great Universe Origin Arts, not only had he attained incredible strength, his regenerative abilities also improved significantly, and the pain from his two wounds was instantly significantly alleviated.

At the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air to release the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, the blue shield, the golden lock, and the Profound Heavenly Gourd from his body.

All of his other immortal treasures were in his storage tools, which he was no longer able to sense, so they were inaccessible to him.

Before he had a chance to do anything else, another piercing shriek rang out.

Upon determining the location of the arrow with his hearing, Han Li immediately threw a punch in that direction.

The nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords also instantly shot forth before intertwining with one another to form a giant azure sword lotus flower that descended upon the black arrow.

At the same time, a burst of green light shot out of the mouth of the gourd toward the arrow, while the blue shield swelled to several dozen feet in size before positioning itself in front of him.

As for the golden lock, it wasn't a defensive immortal treasure, but it was also serving as a shield.

However, in the next instant, Han Li felt another cold sensation over his lower abdomen, followed by a burst of excruciating pain, and he was sent flying backward as blood came gushing out of his mouth.

He was unable to see, but he could feel that a large hole had been pierced through his lower abdomen, and it felt as if his internal organs were being simultaneously burned by scorching flames and eaten away by corrosive acid.

He fell heavily onto the ground, then immediately sprang to his feet.

Such an injury wasn't enough to completely disable him, and he was channeling his Great Universe Origin Arts with all his might to accelerate his recovery.

What the hell is happening? Han Li thought to himself in a bewildered manner.

Through his spiritual connection with his immortal treasures, he was able to sense that the black arrow of light had pierced straight through them as if it had no substantial form at all.

At this moment, Han Li couldn't help but feel a little panicked. Losing his sight and spiritual sense was already terrible, and now, it seemed like there was no way for him to defend himself from these fearsome black arrows.

Before he had a chance to think of a way out of this predicament, that familiar shriek rang out once again.

To compound his woes even further, the black arrows seemed to be coming faster and faster.

Han Li immediately positioned all of his immortal treasures in front of himself once again, and he also summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released waves of golden ripples in all directions while he dodged to the side.

A faint thud rang out as Han Li was sent flying once again, this time with the arrow piercing through his shoulder.

In the next instant, he sprang back to his feet, and he was feeling even more panicked.

His trump card, his Mantra Treasured Axis, had completely failed him!

Right at this moment, a stunned look appeared on his face as his entire body stiffened.

The surrounding area had fallen completely silent.

He had lost his sense of hearing...

Han Li's heart immediately sank.

Without his hearing, how could he determine the location of the arrows? Was he not just a sitting duck at this point?

All of a sudden, he felt a gust of wind glance over his skin, and he hurriedly dodged to the side, but he had only just sprung into motion when a burst of excruciating agony tore through his chest, sending him flying once again.

A large hole had been punched through his chest, but thankfully, it had missed his heart.

He sprang to his feet once again with his expression twisted with panic and fury.

Without his spiritual sense, eyesight, and hearing, there was no way that he could evade those arrows.

Even with his tremendous regenerative abilities, all it would take would be a single arrow through one of his vital regions to put an end to his life.

Was he going to die here?

Han Li let loose a desperate roar as he paid no further heed to the threat of the arrows and rushed forward with all his might.

However, in the next instant, yet another arrow came flying at him.

At this moment, he was flying forward with all his might, so he was unable to take any evasive action, and a burst of intense pain shot through his right arm, following which his entire arm was amputated at the shoulder.

Han Li gritted his teeth through the pain as he continued to fly onward with all his might.

All of a sudden, his expression stiffened once again.

His body was drenched in blood at this point, but he couldn't smell any of it.

Have I lost my sense of smell as well?

Immediately thereafter, yet another arrow shot forth from up ahead, this time piercing through his right leg.

He continued to forge ahead while disregarding his injuries, but he was becoming more and more frustrated by the second.

It seemed that there was no end to this dark passageway, and for the first time since arriving in the True Immortal Realm, he was plunged into complete despair.

However, there was one final shred of clarity in his mind, and it urged him not to give up.

In the blink of an eye, he was struck by seven or eight more arrows, blowing several more large holes into his body. The only silver lining was that he still had his sense of touch, so he was able to sense the wind swept up by the arrows and dodge at the last second, thereby allowing him to save his vital regions from being struck.

However, even with his tremendous physical constitution, he was starting to grow a little woozy from his severe injuries.

I can't keep going like this!

All of a sudden, Han Li stopped in his tracks, then descended onto the ground, gasping for air.

He had thought that the passageway wouldn't be very long, that he would be able to reach the end in a short time if he were to fly at full speed, but he was clearly incorrect in his evaluation.

He channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts with all his might in an attempt to recover from his injuries, but they were far too severe for his regenerative abilities to keep up with.

What do I do?

Han Li's mind was racing as he tried to think of a way out of this dire situation.

Right at this moment, his expression stiffened once again.

He had lost his sense of touch!

With the deprivation of his sense of touch, all possibility of him evading the black arrows had been erased.

Right at this moment, a cold sensation pierced through his dantian, followed by the all-too-familiar burst of excruciating pain.

Han Li wanted to roar in indignation, but was unable to utter even a single sound.

With the destruction of his dantian and his nascent soul, his consciousness was quicky fading into darkness, and he was unable to hold on despite his desperate efforts to do so.

Right at this moment, the alluring figure of Nangong Wan sprang into his mind.

"Wan'er!" Han Li yelled from the bottom of his heart, and what remained of his consciousness clung stubbornly to this plane of existence, refusing to dissipate.

He couldn't die here... There were so many things that he still had to do... He couldn't give up!

Han Li clung desperately onto his final shred with lucidity with all his might, refusing to sink into the abyss.

Time passed by in an agonizingly slow fashion, and after what seemed like an eternity, a faint crack rang out within his mind, as if something had shattered.

In the next instant, an enormous flow of warmth surged into Han Li's consciousness, causing him to involuntarily relax and pass out.

"Fellow Daoist Li! Fellow Daoist Li!"

An urgent voice rang out beside Han Li's ears, and initially, it seemed to be from another world, but it was slowly becoming clearer and clearer.

Han Li's consciousness slowly returned to him, and he discovered that he was standing in an azure palace with his body completely unscathed.

At this moment, Immortal Lord Hot Flame was standing beside him, watching him with a concerned expression.

"What just... How..."

Han Li was stumbling over his words as he struggled to fathom what he had just experienced.

He quickly inspected his surroundings as he spoke, and he discovered that there was a dark passageway behind him, the very same one that they had passed through at the entrance of the palace.

Bursts of black light were flashing incessantly within the passageway while constantly taking on all types of different forms, and it was as if they had a life of their own.

"This is Patriarch Miro's Six Senses True Mantra Restriction. I only recalled it after I entered the passageway. The restriction is one that refines the mind by dragging you into an illusion where you're deprived of all six of your senses," Immortal Lord Hot Flame explained.

"That was an illusion? It felt even more realistic than reality," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"Those with insufficient mental fortitude will completely lose consciousness after being stripped of one or two of their senses, causing them to be forever lost in the array. Very few people are able to even last until their third or fourth senses are deprived.

“This restriction's primary purpose is to ward off external enemies, but it was also used as a test of willpower by our sect's disciples. I've experienced the restriction on several past occasions, and that's why I was able to overcome it.

“In contrast, you stepped into this restriction completely unprepared, yet you were still able to make your way out, and that shows incredible mental fortitude," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a hint of admiration in his eyes.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daiost Hot Flame. I was simply extremely fortunate to have overcome the restriction," Han Li said with a wave of his hand, and internally, he was feeling a little disgruntled.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame seemed to have sensed Han Li's displeasure, and he explained, "My apologies, Fellow Daoist Li, I had no idea that this restriction had been set up here. The restriction is an extremely perilous one, but it can also benefit one immensely. In particular, one stands to gain the most from their first time experiencing the restriction. Take a look and see if your spiritual sense has been enhanced, Fellow Daoist Li."

Chapter 686: Powerful Treasures

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then conducted a brief internal inspection, upon which a hint of elation appeared on his face.

Indeed, his spiritual sense had been enhanced by roughly 50%, and even the fifth level of his Spirit Refinement Technique was on the verge of a breakthrough.

On top of that, due to the sensory deprivation that he endured, he had also gained a deeper understanding of his Mantra Domain.

However, this wasn't the time to be focusing on cultivation, so Han Li quickly turned his attention back to the azure hall before him.

The hall wasn't very large, only around a thousand feet in size, and it was completely empty with the exception of four stone pillars, one at each corner.

However, at the other end of the hall was a dark passageway that seemed to lead somewhere deeper.

"How long was I unconscious for?" Han Li asked as he turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

"Not very long, maybe about fifteen minutes," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then contacted Daoist Xie through their spiritual connection.

"Did he do anything strange while I was unconscious, Brother Xie?"

While he did trust Immortal Lord Hot Flame as an ally, it was always better to be safe than sorry.

"No, all he did was observe the surrounding environment," Daoist Xie replied through voice transmission.

Han Li felt very reassured to hear this, and he said to Immortal Lord Hot Flame, "My apologies for the delay, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame. Let's keep going."

Immortal Lord Hot Flame naturally didn't object to this. He would've continued onward long ago if he didn't have to stay behind to look after Han Li.

With that, the two of them stepped into the passageway up ahead, and the light here was also quite dim, but there were no restrictions set up.

The passageway wasn't very straight, but it wasn't all that long, either, and before long, the two of them reached the end, at which point they encountered a white door of light.

The sound of a battle could be heard ringing out from within the door of light, and sure enough, someone else had already gotten here ahead of them.

Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame exchanged a glance with each other, then concealed themselves before flying into the door of light in a covert fashion.

Immediately thereafter, they appeared in a giant hall that was over ten thousand feet in size, and it was completely empty aside from two rows of white stone pillars on either side of the hall.

At this moment, there were five figures locked in a fierce battle in the hall, causing the entire place to tremble and rumble violently.

However, the hall was constructed out of some type of extremely resilient material, and it remained largely unscathed despite the intensity of the battle taking place within it.

As Han Li swept his gaze over the five figures, he noticed quite a few familiar faces.

The five figures were split up into two opposing factions, one of which a two-man faction, among which was none other than Fox 3.

He was joined by a blue-skinned woman in a blue cloak with a head of curly green hair. As she moved, her body swayed from side to side like a seductive snake, making it impossible to look away.

The opposing group consisted of three people, two of whom Han Li was able to identify as Su Liu and Gong Shutian, and the final person to round out the trio was an extremely burly and imposing man with a pair of large golden rings hanging from his ears.

Han Li hid behind a stone pillar, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame did the same.

Fox 3 and the blue-skinned woman were definitely on the back foot, but they didn't appear as if they were going to be defeated anytime soon, so both Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame had chosen to conceal themselves and merely observe for now.

Among the five combatants, Han Li didn't recognize the blue-skinned woman and the imposing man, but he did recognize the blue cloak that the woman was wearing. It was the same cloak as the one worn by the member of the Robe Change Order that he had slain earlier, so she was most likely from the same order as well.

As for the imposing man, he wasn't wearing the customary golden robe of Heavenly Court cultivators, but some of the accessories on his body carried Heavenly Court symbols, and that was a clear indication of where he had come from.

Han Li observed the battle for a while, then peered deeper into the hall, upon which he noticed an altar-like platform at the very back of the hall.

The platform was enshrouded in black and white light to form a circular array that was several dozen feet in size, and it resembled a miniature version of the Heaven and Earth Dust Array outside the True Mantra Palace.

The black and white lights within the array were intertwining with one another to form a yin yang symbol, and on the eye of each half of the yin yang symbol was a golden plate and a silver lute, seemingly acting as the cores of the array.

The golden plate had a series of patterns on its surface, and at its center was a thumb-sized protrusion, extending out of which was a golden needle that was slowly revolving.

The plate was flashing with golden light and giving off bursts of time law power fluctuations, indicating that it was a time-attribute immortal treasure. Furthermore, the time law power fluctuations that it was giving off were far superior to those of any of Han Li's time-attribute immortal treasures.

As for the silver lute, it was glowing bright with silver light and also giving off formidable law power fluctuations, except these law power fluctuations were of the space attribute.

Aside from that, there was also a dhvaja hovering above the array, and there were countless runes engraved onto the dhvaja, which was split up into five levels, with each level a different color.

From top to bottom, the colors of the levels were gold, green, blue, crimson, and yellow.

The lights of the five colors intertwined to form a scripture, which was giving off five different types of time law powers, three of which were very familiar to Han Li as they were identical to the auras of the Mantra Axis Scripture, the Water Divination Time Arts, and the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture.

However, the time law power fluctuations being released by the dhvaja were far more profound than the time law powers that he was cultivating.

The dhvaja was enshrouded under a faint five-colored light barrier, which also encompassed the Heaven and Earth Dust array, the golden plate, and the silver lute.

The two treasures were giving off golden and silver radiance that didn't conflict against the five-colored light barrier at all. Instead, there was a subtle balance between them.

Right at this moment, Han Li sensed something, and he turned his gaze to Immortal Lord Hot Flame, only to discover that the latter was staring intently at the three treasures at the back of the hall, particularly the dhvaja.

He was so excited that even his breathing was becoming a little heavier, and it immediately occurred to Han Li that perhaps the dhvaja had something to do with the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

The problem was that Immortal Lord Hot Flame was so worked up that he seemed to be unable to keep his own emotions in check, and Han Li was just about to remind him to ensure that he was well-concealed when a loud roar suddenly rang out.

"Who's hiding there? Come out!"

Immediately thereafter, a red sword projection struck the spot where Han Li's duo was hiding, and the stone pillars that they were hiding behind were instantly snapped into two.

Han Li hurriedly sprang away to take evasive measures, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame was also snapped out of his reverie before darting away to the side.

As a result, the two of them were completely revealed, and they discovered Gongshu Tian glowering at them from afar while holding a giant sword with scorching flames swirling around it.

"So it was just a pair of Golden Immortal Stage insects. You two must have a death wish to have come here!" Gongshu Tian sneered.

Immediately thereafter, his giant sword slipped out of his grasp, then swelled to over a thousand feet in size, and a giant crimson dragon projection emerged over it as it came crashing down upon Han Li's duo with tremendous power.

Even before the sword fully descended upon them, Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame found themselves having to contend with an incredibly scorching aura.

The entire space within a radius of over a thousand feet seemed to have been set alight, and it began to ripple and warp violently.

Han Li immediately swept both sleeves through the air to release nine azure flying swords, which combined as one to form a single giant sword with thick arcs of golden lightning flashing over its surface.

The azure light radiating from the sword was so bright that even the scorching flames tumbling down from above were unable to outshine it.

The giant azure sword rose up into the air at Han Li's behest, and the two enormous swords clashed with an earth-shattering clang that caused the surrounding space to tremble and fracture.

The fiery sword was instantly stopped cold in its tracks, and an incredulous look appeared on Gongshu Tian's face upon seeing this, clearly not expecting his attack to be withstood by a mere Golden Immortal.

Han Li took advantage of this opportunity to grab onto Immortal Lord Hot Flame, and the two of them vanished amid a flash of golden lightning before reappearing near the entrance of the hall.

At the same time, the giant azure sword forced back the opposing fiery sword a little figure, then shot back to Han Li's side.

Gongshu Tian turned to Han Li with a cold expression, but didn't immediately lash out again as the other four combatants in the hall had also disengaged themselves from battle, with Fox 3 and the blue-skinned woman arriving by Han Li's duo.

Fox 3's complexion was a little pale, but there was an elated look on his face as he said to Han Li's duo through voice transmission, "You're finally here, fellow daoists! There's no time to waste! Those three items on that altar are all extremely powerful treasures.

“In particular, that dhvaja very likely contains the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, the paramount cultivation art of the True Mantra Sect, so we absolutely cannot allow them to fall into the hands of the Heavenly Court!"

Even though Han Li had already guessed that the dhvaja could contain the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, he was still ecstatic to hear confirmation from Fox 3, and he immediately replied, "Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Fox, we'll do everything we can to help you!"

In contrast, Immortal Lord Hot Flame's brows furrowed ever so slightly upon hearing this.

Chapter 687: Unconvinced

Han Li noticed the minute change in Immortal Lord Hot Flame's expression, and he asked through voice transmission, "Can we trust Fox 3? Is the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra really in that dhvaja?"

Immortal Lord Hot Flame hesitated momentarily, then gritted his teeth as he replied through voice transmission, "That dhvaja was once a prized immortal treasure of Patriarch Miro's, and it does indeed contain the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. Please help me secure the treasure, and once you do, all I ask for is the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. You can keep the dhvaja in return."

"I'll do my best," Han Li promised.

The blue-skinned woman was in slightly better condition than Fox 3, and she took a glance at Han Li's duo, but immediately lost interest as soon as she sensed that they were only a pair of Golden Immortals.

"By the way, this is Celestial Maiden Bi She from the Robe Change Order. She's currently fighting alongside us to take on these Heavenly Court cultivators," Fox 3 explained.

Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame both issued greetings to the blue-skinned woman, but she completely ignored them as she took a blue pill.

A slightly awkward look appeared on Fox 3's face at the sight of Bi She's lukewarm reception, and he explained to Han Li's duo through voice transmission, "Please don't be offended, fellow daoists. Celestial Maiden Bi She is from the Sea Demon Race, so she harbors some enmity toward us human cultivators."

The Robe Change Order was a subsidiary organization of the Reincarnation Palace, but that didn't give him any authority over Bi She. On top of that, she was a late-High Zenith cultivator, so he absolutely could not afford to get on her bad side.

Having said that, he had to ensure that Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame were happy as well. In particular, even though Han Li was only a Golden Immortal, Fox 3 couldn't help but feel as if there was something unfathomable about him.

Han Li naturally wouldn't take offense over such a minor transgression, and he assured Fox 3 that he didn't mind.

"Fellow Daoist Li, we were separated as soon as we entered these ruins, so I never got the chance to tell you about your Reincarnation Palace mission. Your mission is to help me secure that dhvaja and the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra inside it," Fox 3 said.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, and he immediately replied through voice transmission, "Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Fox, I'll do my best."

At this point, he had promised both Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Fox 3 that he would help them secure the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. As for exactly who he was ultimately going to help, he would just have to decide depending on the circumstances.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame twitched ever so slightly, and he took a subtle glance at Han Li and Fox 3.

As Han Li and the others were conversing with one another, the three Heavenly Court cultivators were also communicating with each other through voice transmission.

"The longer this drags on, the more likely something goes wrong, so let's not hold back anymore!" Chi Rong said in a grim voice.

"You're one to talk! You're the one who's holding back the most out of the three of us. Don't think that I don't know your true identity," Su Liu sneered.

Chi Rong shuddered slightly upon hearing this, and a hint of cold killing intent surfaced in his eyes, but Su Liu merely continued to look at him in a calm and completely fearless manner.

Gongshu Tian took a curious glance at Chi Rong upon hearing this, but then immediately averted his gaze.

Chi Rong took a deep breath, and the cold look on his face faded as he said, "Now's not the time to be bickering. I say we kill these four before we discuss anything else. Any objections?"

"I concur," Su Liu replied, raising no objections.

"Alright, in that case, I'll take on Bi She. Su Liu, you take on Fox 3, and Gongshu Tian, you go after those two Golden Immortals," Chi Rong instructed.

Once again, Su Liu and Gongshu Tian raised no objections.

Right as they were about to spring into action, Immortal Lord Hot Flame suddenly stepped forward and said, "Hold on, fellow daoists, I'd like to say something."

Chi Rong's trio exchanged a surprised glance with each other, and Han Li and the others were also rather taken aback to see this.

"On the way here, Fellow Daoist Li and I were attacked by Gray Immortals, and their numbers were not insignificant. On top of that, they've also set up an interrealm teleportation array here, and they're most likely also targeting the treasures in here.

“There's a very good chance that they'll be here very soon. Gray Immortals are the sworn enemies of the entire True Immortal Realm, so let's set our differences aside for now and eradicate the Gray Immortals together when they arrive, then fight over these treasures after that," Immortal Lord Hot Flame proposed, offering a truce.

Everyone was very surprised to hear this, with the exception of Han Li.

"Gray Immortals? Is that true?" Fox 3 asked with a bewildered expression.

"It is. As I said, Fellow Daoist Li was with me, and he also fought against the Gray Immortals," Immortal Lord Hot Flame replied as he turned to Han Li.

"I can vouch for Fellow Daoist Hot Flame," Han Li confirmed with a nod.

Despite this, he was feeling a little perplexed, wondering why Immortal Lord Hot Flame had suddenly mentioned this. Did he really think that this would be enough to culminate in a ceasefire?

A grim look appeared on Fox 3's face, and he seemed to have fallen into deep thought, while Bi She's brows also furrowed slightly.

Chi Rong, Su Liu, and Gongshu Tian exchanged a glance with one another, following which the three of them pounced collectively at Han Li and the others.

"Surely you could've come up with a better excuse to stall for time!" Gongshu Tian sneered as scorching flames erupted out of his giant sword, giving it the resemblance of a fiery dragon, and it came crashing down upon Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame with far more power than before.

Su Liu also raised a hand as incredibly thick bolts of five-colored lightning erupted out of his body, then converged to form two five-colored lightning pythons, each of which was over a hundred feet in length.

The lightning pythons sprang up into the air, then swooped down toward Fox 3.

At the same time, Chi Rong opened his mouth to release a fiery crimson cloud, which was rumbling and churning incessantly.

Countless balls of fire came raining down upon Bi She out of the fiery cloud, and it was clear the the three of them didn't believe Immortal Lord Hot Flame at all.

Han Li and the others hurriedly sprang into action as well, with Immortal Lord Hot Flame darting back in retreat as he summoned his crimson fan before sweeping it forcefully through the air.

A crimson pillar of fire erupted out of the fan before rising up into the air, and at the same time, he opened his mouth to release a glowing azure talisman that vanished into the pillar of fire in a flash.

The talisman was instantly shattered, transforming into an azure tornado that fused as one with the pillar of crimson flames, which instantly swelled to over a hundred feet thick as it rumbled toward the giant fiery sword.

A cold sneer appeared on Gongshu Tian's face as he made a hand seal, and the flames around his giant sword took on the form of a fiery dragon's head before inhaling sharply.

The giant pillar of fire was instantly sucked into the dragon's mouth, vanishing in the blink of an eye.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to do anything else, the giant fiery sword up above had already crashed down upon him, enveloping his entire body in a burst of scorching heat.

He felt as if he were being crushed under a giant mountain, and all of his movements had become extremely slow and sluggish.

His face instantly turned bright red under the sweltering heat, and he felt as if he were about to burst into flames.

Right at this moment, a giant azure sword appeared in front of Gongshu Tian's fiery sword, and the two swords clashed with a deafening clang, with the fiery sword once again stopped cold in its tracks.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of azure light shot forth from behind, sweeping up Immortal Lord Hot Flame's body before dragging him back by over a thousand feet in the blink of an eye.

Han Li then appeared in front of Immortal Lord Hot Flame, but not only was Gongshu Tian not infuriated to see his attack foiled, a faint smile appeared on his face, as if some sinister plot of his had just been realized.

The dragon's head on the fiery sword opened its mouth to blast forth ten bursts of crimson flamees, each of which contained a large crimson flag. All of the flags had flames swirling around them, forming countless fire ravens, fire pythons, fiery tigers, and other flaming projections, all of which were giving off incredible heat.

The ten fiery flags instantly formed a fiery cage that trapped the giant azure sword within it, and Han Li's connection to his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords was instantly weakened significantly.

His expression changed slightly as he hurriedly attempted to summon the sword back to himself, but despite its violent struggles, the giant azure sword was unable to break free from its fiery cage.

"Let's see how you'll fare without that little sword of yours!" Gongshu Tian sneered as a vast expanse of crimson flames erupted out of his head and into the giant fiery sword up above.

The flames around the fiery sword reared up even further, but instead of crashing down again, a ball of blinding white light began to appear on its surface.

The ball of white light shot out of the tip of the sword, and initially, it was only the size of a bowl, but it then rapidly swelled to several dozen feet in diameter before crashing down toward Han Li like an asteroid.

Extremely pure and translucent white flames were swirling around the fireball, and all of the space in its wake warped and twisted violently.

These white flames were capable of incinerating the very space itself, and what was even more alarming was that six or seven more of them had shot out of the fiery sword at Gongshu Tian's behest, with all of them crashing down toward Han Li one after another.

All of a sudden, Han Li found himself surrounded with nowhere to run.

Chapter 688: Returning the Favor

A serious look appeared on Han Li's face as he raised an arm to release a small blue shield, which swelled to around seventy to eighty feet in size, then transformed into a blue water barrier.

A turbulent river projection appeared over the water barrier, and it was giving off bursts of thunderous churning and rumbling noises.

A string of resounding booms rang out as the white fireballs struck the blue water barrier one after another, sending waves of blue and white light erupting in all directions.

The blue water barrier trembled violently, and several vortexes then appeared on its surface, but in the blink of an eye, it was back to normal again.

Gongshu Tian's expression changed slightly upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, Han Li made a hand seal, and his giant azure sword split back up into nine small swords before tumbling down out of the air as if they had lost all of their power.

Immediately thereafter, nine more azure swords flew out of his sleeves before hurtling rapidly toward Gongshu Tian.

At this point, Immortal Lord Hot Flame had also been given a chance to catch his breath, and he chanted an incantation, upon which a row of crimson runes appeared on the surface of his fan before it was swept forcefully toward Gongshu Tian.

Nine bursts of flames of different colors erupted out of the fan, and all of the flames converged to form a giant fiery phoenix that was around a thousand feet in size, with nine long tail feathers trailing along behind it.

The phoenix spread its wings before pouncing at Gongshu Tian with tremendous power, and Gongshu Tian's expression darkened slightly as he summoned his giant sword back into his grasp before slashing it viciously through the air.

Countless thick streaks of fiery sword qi surged forth in a frenzy, forming a vast net of fire that swallowed up the fiery phoenix, following which a string of resounding booms rang out.

While Han Li was locked in battle against Gongshu Tian, he was occasionally checking on Fox 3 and Bi She, who were battling Su Liu and Chi Rong, respectively, and both of them were clearly on the back foot.

At this moment, arcs of five-colored lightning were crackling around Su Liu, and he was able to conjure up enormous spears of lightning at will. At the same time, there were around a dozen formidable lightning swords flying circling around above his head, forming a lightning sword array that protected him from all directions.

In the face of the all-encompassing barrage of five-colored lightning spears, Fox 3's illusory law powers were completely suppressed, and he could only passively evade the oncoming attacks with his movement techniques and that spatial treasure of his.

However, that spatial treasure was truly extraordinary, and it always seemed to be able to save him from lethal attacks just in the nick of time, so Su Liu wasn't able to strike him down for now.

As for Bi She, she was not faring well against Chi Rong at all. There were eight millstone-sized blue beads revolving around her, all of which were glowing with blue light and giving off formidable glacial qi, and the blue light released by the eight beads had come together to form a translucent blue light barrier.

However, the blue light barrier was enveloped within a sea of crimson flames, and a fiery dragon could be seen dancing within it.

A burst of indescribable heat was surging out of the sea of flames, threatening to set the surrounding space alight.

Waves of crimson flames crashed ferociously against the blue light barrier, causing it to rapidly soften and melt away.

Bi She was frantically making a string of hand seals as she struggled to maintain the blue light barrier, and all of a sudden, a burst of blue light erupted out of the top of her head, then transformed into a giant blue serpentine projection that was around a thousand feet in size.

The serpent had a flat and level head, and its entire body was covered in a layer of white scales. There were numerous blue ice spikes growing on its back, and it was giving off an incredibly formidable glacial aura.

As soon as the serpentine projection appeared, it immediately opened its mouth to release bursts of blue glacial qi that fused into the blue light barrier, which instantly brightened significantly before being restored to its former, undamaged state.

Chi Rong's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he took a glance at the other two battles, upon which his dismay deepened even further as he could see that neither Gongshu Tian nor Su Liu were close to finishing off their opponents.

Red light flashed within his eyes as he made a hand seal, and the flames around his body expanded rapidly outward, filling the entire hall in the blink of an eye to form a giant fiery spirit domain that encompassed everyone within it.

Immediately thereafter, all of the flames within the spirit domain converged above his head, instantly forming a shimmering, crimson bell.

The bell was extremely antiquated in appearance, and it looked as if it had been forged out of fire copper. There were different designs such as mountains, rivers, and celestial bodies engraved upon it, as well as many squiggly, worm-like runes.

Han Li's heart jolted slightly at the sight of the crimson bell.

Not only was the bell giving off an incredibly formidable fiery aura, that fiery aura was also interspersed with incredibly potent time law power fluctuations.

Chi Rong raised a hand before slamming his palm down upon the crimson bell, producing a melodious chime that seemed to be able to penetrate one's souls.

As soon as Han Li heard this bell chime, he instantly felt himself becoming a lot more sluggish, and even his nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had been slowed down by tenfold.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame, Fox 3, and Bi She were all also affected, moving far slower than before, but Gongshu Tian, Su Liu, and Chi Rong himself weren't affected at all.

Chi Rong made a hand seal, and the flames within the spirit domain converged once again to form eight fiery dragons that appeared around the blue light barrier in a flash.

The fiery dragon that had been prowling within the sea of flames also emerged, and together, the nine fiery dragons circled around Bi She while letting loose a collective roar that caused the entire hall to tremble violently.

"Go!" Chi Rong yelled, and the nine fiery dragons swooped down in unison to crash against the blue light barrier, which was instantly shattered, following which the nine fiery dragons crashed into Bi She with immense power.

Bi She attempted to take evasive measures, but in her slowed state, she was unable to dodge the attack. As a result, she was sent flying back through the air, smashing a massive crater into a wall like a plummeting asteroid, and scorching flames could still be seen surging within the crater.

Almost at the exact same moment, Su Liu began to make a rapid string of hand seals, and the lightning swords above his head instantly swelled to over a hundred times their original size as all of their tips turned to face forward.

A vast expanse of five-colored lightning then erupted out of his body before fusing into the lightning swords, which instantly took on a translucent appearance.

Su Liu then raised an arm before swinging it down upon Fox 3, and the dozen or so giant lightning swords above his head vanished in a flash, only to reappear near Fox 3 an instant later.

An alarmed look appeared on Fox 3's face as several translucent chains shot out of his glabella before sweeping toward the giant lightning swords, and at the same time, he attempted to flee from the attack, but he was far slower than Su Liu.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as a vast explosion of five-colored lightning swallowed up Fox 3's entire body.

Enormous streaks of sword qi interspersed with five-colored lightning flashed up and down within the ball of light, releasing blinding light.

On the other side, Gongshu Tian was ecstatic to see Han Li's duo suddenly moving so slowly, and he immediately swooped in for the kill.

He let loose a loud roar as the giant fiery sword in his hand shot forth through the air, then suddenly vanished before transforming into two streaks of fiery sword qi, each of which was three hundred to four hundred feet in length.

There were countless tiny runes flashing over the two streaks of sword qi, giving off intensely formidable fire law power fluctuations.

As soon as the two streaks of fiery qi appeared, they immediately vanished into thin air.

In the next instant, the two streaks of sword qi appeared behind Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame amid a burst of spatial fluctuations before slashing toward them.

Han Li and Immortal Lord Hot Flame were greatly alarmed by this turn of events, but they were far too slow in their current state to evade the streaks of oncoming sword qi.

Gongshu Tian's eyes were glowing, and he could already envision the decapitation of Han Li's duo, but right at this moment, a golden wheel suddenly appeared behind Han Li.

The wheel revolved rapidly, and Han Li's sluggish body suddenly became extremely fast and agile.

He swept both sleeves through the air in a rapid motion, and the blue water barrier in front of him instantly swept back until it was behind him.

At the same time, the water barrier extended outward by several thousand feet to protect Immortal Lord Hot Flame as well.

Two resounding booms rang out as the two streaks of sword qi struck the water barrier in unison, and bursts of crimson flames and sword qi crashed viciously against the water barrier, causing it to tremble incessantly, but it was able to keep the oncoming attacks at bay.

The excitement in Gongshu Tian's eyes instantly stiffened upon seeing this, following which it was replaced by incredulity.

Han Li turned to take a glance at Fox and Bi She, then immediately made a hand seal, upon which his spirit domain was also released, encompassing the entire hall in the blink of an eye.

Enshrouded within Han Li's time spirit domain, Su Liu, Chi Rong, and Gongshu Tian were also slowed down significantly, to the point that they had become even a little slower than Han Li and his allies.

A stunned look flashed through Immortal Lord Hot Flame's eyes at the sight of the surrounding golden spirit domain, while Su Liu and Chi Rong were both astonished.

"This is a time spirit domain!"

"Impossible!"

Chapter 689: Identified

Bi She initially faltered slightly in the wake of the release of Han Li's spirit doman, following which an ecstatic look appeared on her face, and she instantly shot out of the crater in the wall, appearing several thousand feet away in the blink of an eye.

At this moment, the suit of soft blue armor that she was wearing was severely damaged, revealing much of the skin underneath, which was covered in a layer of fine blue scales, many of which had also been shattered, causing her to bleed profusely.

She hurriedly swallowed a pill while turning her gaze to Han Li, and a complex look flashed through her eyes.

At the same time, a figure shot out of the vast expanse of five-colored lightning in the hall, and it was none other than Fox 3.

His clothes were in tatters, and his body was riddled with char marks, presenting a sorry sight to behold, but his aura was still quite stable, and he was clearly in far better condition than Bi She.

"I owe you one, Fellow Daoist Li. If we get out of this alive, I'll treat you to the as much wine as you want for three days!" Fox 3 chortled as he summoned a green talisman before slapping it onto his own body, and the injuries that he had sustained immediately began to heal rapidly.

Chi Rong and Su Liu certainly weren't just going to stand by and allow Fox 3 and Bi She to recover, and they immediately pounced forward in pursuit.

Bi She and Fox 3 were currently a little faster than Chi Rong and Su Liu, but there wasn't enough space in the hall for them to do much maneuvering, so they had no choice but to face them in battle again.

Meanwhile, Gongshu Tian was glowering intently at Han Li with a newfound resentment in his eyes, and Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this.

Sure enough, Gongshu Tian suddenly roared, "You're Li Feiyu!"

Han Li wasn't surprised to hear his identity exposed.

He had been forced to unleash his time spirit domain, and with two immortal envoys present, it wasn't a surprise at all that he had been identified.

He had been reluctant to unveil his time spirit domain precisely for fear of this exact scenario, but he had no choice, considering how everyone on his side had been in grave peril just now.

"I should've known that it was you! Everyone thought that Wyrm 3 was the one who killed Gongshu Jiu, but I know that you're the true culprit! I didn't think that you would dare to come to the Black Soil Immortal Region. Did you really think that you could go wherever you please just because you have some basic mastery over the laws of time?" Gongshu Tian sneered with a furious expression.

"There are countless people who want to kill me, you're nothing special. Leave him to me and go help Celestial Maiden Bi She, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame," Han Li said with a faint smile.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame opened his mouth to respond upon hearing this, but ultimately remained silent as he flew toward Bi She.

Gongshu Tian was even more infuriated by Han Li's blatant disrespect, and he roared, "You'll pay for your arrogance!"

At the same time, radiant crimson light erupted out of his body before sweeping outward in all directions, forming a fiery spirit domain that encompassed the entire hall in an instant.

Immediately thereafter, all of the flames in the spirit domain converged to form a fiery giant that was over a thousand feet tall, and its entire body was giving off fearsome fire law power fluctuations.

Enshrouded within the fiery spirit domain, Han Li felt the surrounding air constrict around him, while the air temperature spiked drastically. He felt as if he had been dropped into a blazing furnace, making it almost impossible for him to breathe.

However, a layer of silver flames then emerged over his body, and the surrounding heat instantly faded, following which he began to dart back in retreat.

Gongshu Tian was bewildered to see Han Li completely unaffected by his spirit domain, and he "You're not getting away!"

He made a hand seal as he spoke, and the flames on the surface of the fiery giant reared up as it raised an arm up high, then sent a gigantic fist crashing down upon Han Li.

The enormous fist left a series of long spatial rifts in its wake, and even before it arrived, Han Li was struck by a sense of asphyxiating pressure that threatened to completely immobilize him.

However, he remained calm and collected as he made a rapid string of hand seals, and the blue water barrier in front of him quickly shrank down to form a wall of water that was around three feet thick.

The river projection appeared on the wall of water once again, but it was flowing much slower than before, and the blue light emanating from it was also a little dim.

Han Li knew that the shield's power was greatly diminished due to the tremendous fire law powers that filled this entire space.

The wall of water had only just taken shape when the fiery fist crashed into it with an earth-shattering boom, and red and blue light erupted in all directions alongside plumes of white smoke.

The river projection within the wall of water was rapidly shrinking, and the blue light emanating from it was also flickering unsteadily.

The fiery giant continued to pile on the pressure, and its other fist came crashing down like a flaming asteroid.

The river projection within the blue wall of water instantly shrank down into a tiny stream that almost dried up entirely, and with the third punch from the fiery giant, the wall of water exploded into a vast expanse of blue light before dissipating altogether.

In the face of the fiery giant's fourth punch, Han Li remained completely unfazed, and thirty-six profound acupoints lit up in unison on his chest as he retaliated with a punch of his own.

Much to Gongshu Tian's astonishment, as soon as the two fists clashed, the fiery giant's fist instantly exploded into countless bursts of crimson flames along with its entire arm, and much of the flames were devoured by the layer of silver flames on Han Li's fist.

Thanks to the tremendous fire law powers within the fiery spirit domain, the fiery giant was instantly able to regrow a new arm, but it didn't immediately lash out again.

"That's a Flame of Essence! To think that a mere Golden Immortal would have so many tricks up his sleeve. Now wonder Gongshu Jiu fell to his demise at your hands. I've always been searching for a spirit flame of heaven and earth to act as an intermediary to integrate all of my spirit flames, this Flame of Essence will be perfect!" Gongshu Tian sneered as he stood atop the fiery giant's head.

Han Li paid no heed to Gongshu Tian as he made a hand seal, and his nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords shot forth through the air with arcs of golden lightning flashing over them before converging toward Gongshu Tian from all directions at an astonishing speed.

The nine azure flying swords were arranged in a formation that resembled an azure sword lotus flower, and countless bursts of fearsome sword qi were sweeping through the air, threatening to slice Gongshu Jiu into pieces.

Gongshu Tian's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he summoned a giant fiery sword into his grasp before sweeping it forcefully through the air.

A vast expanse of scorching flames surged forth, transforming into a fiery wyrm that swiveled around in mid-air to send countless streaks of fiery sword qi erupting out of its mouth.

Azure and crimson sword qi clashed incessantly around Gongshu Tian, resulting in explosions of light that were almost too bright to behold.

Most of the fiery sword qi was destroyed, but the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were also sent flying.

As the fiery wyrm roamed through the area, countless streaks of fiery sword qi re-emerged, and at the same time, Gongshu Tian opened his mouth to release a ball of white light, within which was a small ruler that was only around an inch in length.

Gongshu Tian pointed a finger at the ruler as he chanted an incantation, and the ruler rapidly swelled to several dozen feet in length, with countless five-colored rune etched onto its surface.

All of the five-colored runes on the ruler lit up in unison, and a layer of five-colored spirit flame emerged over them. At the same time, a series of identical five-colored spirit rulers appeared within Gongshu Tian's fiery spirit domain without any warning, and all of them began revolving on the spot to present a mesmerizing sight to behold.

Immediately thereafter, balls of five-colored flame erupted out of the spirit rulers before raining down upon Han Li.

Initially, there were only dozens of these five-colored fireballs, but in the blink of an eye, that number swelled to tens of thousands, and Han Li was bombarded from all directions.

He immediately raised a hand upon seeing this, and the silver flames around him reared up to form a fiery silver barrier that enveloped him from all directions, but to his astonishment, the Flame of Essence was unable to devour these five-colored flames. Instead, it was only just barely able to keep them at bay.

Right as Gongshu Tian was about to do something else, Han Li raised his hand once again to summon a golden flag, and it began revolving in mid-air above his head.

The flag then swelled to ten times its original size at his behest, and countless specks of golden starlight surged out of it, forming a starlight vortex that rapidly expanded outward.

Han Li and the Flame of Essence were swallowed up by the torrent of golden starlight, and both of them vanished in a flash.

The five-colored flames converged upon the golden starlight, only to merely pass through as if it had no substantial form.

The golden starlight quickly spread through the surrounding area, instantly filling the entire nearby area in a radius of several hundred feet, and it was still continuing to expand.

A wary look appeared in Gongshu Tian's eyes upon seeing this, and he immediately flew back in retreat.

The fiery giant also did the same, and as it retreated, its body rapidly shrank down to around the size of an average grown man as it remained close by Gongshu Tian's side.

Despite all of the derision that he had directed at Han Li, Gongshu Tian didn't dare to look down on Han Li in the slightest.

After vanishing into the starry vortex, it was as if Han Li had truly disappeared. Gongshu Tian was unable to sense his presence, but his time spirit domain still remained. Its time-slowing effect was severely compromised due to the influence of Gongshu Tian's fiery spirit domain, but he still didn't dare to let his guard down.

Chapter 690: Perilous Battle

Right as Gongshu Tian was hesitating about how to proceed, countless golden runes suddenly appeared nearby amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

Gongshu Tian's entire body was enveloped by these golden runes, and he was slowed down even further as a result.

At the same time, the river of golden starlight brightened significantly, as if it were resonating with the time spirit domain, and its rate of expansion abruptly sped up by severalfold, swallowing up Gongshu Tian in the blink of an eye.

Gongshu Tian immediately felt as if he had been plunged into a pit of quicksand, and bursts of tremendous pressure were constricting toward him from all directions, dragging him deeper into the starlight.

He immediately sprang into action, releasing countless streaks of crimson sword qi out of his giant fiery sword to eradicate the surrounding golden starlight.

At the same time, he swept his other sleeve through the air, and the five-colored spirit ruler shot forth and swelled drastically in size before falling into the grasp of his fiery domain spirit.

The five-colored flames emanating from the spirit ruler suddenly came together to form a pure white flame, and the domain spirit raised its hand, upon which balls of white flames shot out of the spirit ruler toward the surrounding golden starlight.

All of the nearby starlight was instantly incinerated upon contact with these white flames, and with the two of them joining forces, they were instantly able to clear out a large area.

Gongshu Tian immediately slashed his fiery sword through the air, releasing streaks of sword qi that enveloped both himself and the fiery domain spirit to form a rhomboid streak of swordlight that sped away from the river of starlight.

Not only was the streak of rhomboid swordlight extremely fast, it was also peerlessly sharp, and it tore through the river of starlight with ease.

However, right as it was on the verge of escaping the river of starlight altogether, numerous threads of golden light shot out from within. They were Han Li's time law threads, and there were as many as twenty to thirty of them.

These time law threads intertwined with one another to form a large golden net that stood in the rhomboid swordlight's path, and the golden net collapsed inward to a massive degree, but it remained intact and was able to stop the swordlight in its tracks.

At the same time, Han Li appeared behind the streak of rhomboid swordlight without any warning, and the thirty-six profound acupoints on his chest and abdomen lit up once again as he threw a punch to strike the swordlight.

The rhomboid swordlight was instantly shattered with a resounding boom, and Gongshu Tian and his fiery domain spirit were sent flying as a stunned look appeared on his face.

Han Li immediately flew after Gongshu Tian in pursuit, and a layer of golden ape fur emerged over his body as he swelled rapidly in size, transforming into a giant golden ape before slamming both fists down with tremendous power.

Two giant golden fist projections erupted out of his hand before hurtling toward Gongshu Tian, who raised a hand to conjure up a string of fiery shields that were around a foot in size in front of himself.

The two golden fist projections blasted straight through the shields in their path, but there seemed to be no end to these shields, and they were able to keep the fist projections at bay.

However, before Gongshu Tian had a chance to catch his breath, several translucent chains shot out of Han Li's glabella, then appeared behind Gongshu Tian's head in a flash before attempting to burrow their way in.

Simultaneously, a burst of azure light flashed behind Gongshu Tian, and the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords reappeared before forming another azure sword lotus flower that revolved rapidly to send countless streaks of formidable azure sword qi raining down upon Gongshu Tian.

The golden net also flew through the air, but instead of flying toward Gongshu Tian, it appeared in front of the fiery domain spirit, separating it from Gongshu Tian.

In this instant, Han Li was going all-out in an attempt to kill Gongshu Tian.

As for whether Su Liu would detect the Spiritual Sense Cage that he had unleashed, that was something that he would just have to worry about later.

Gongshu Tian could sense Han Li's determination and killing intent, but he merely sneered as he opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence into the giant sword in his hand.

"You're not going to get me that easily!"

The sword instantly took on a crimson color, and it began to give off an extremely formidable aura.

As the sword was slashed through the air, thousands of streaks of crimson sword qi appeared around Gongshu Tian, eradicating the pair of golden fist projections before also keeping the azure sword lotus flower at bay.

As for the spiritual sense chains, as soon as they came into contact with Gongshu Tian's head, a ball of white light suddenly emerged from his head to form a white light barrier that stopped the chains in their tracks.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and before he had a chance to do anything else, Gongshu Tian lashed out with his sword as he roared, "It's my turn now!"

An incredibly long crescent-shaped crimson sword projection was unleashed at Han Li, and it was so fast that it reached him in the blink of an eye, as if by virtue of instantaneous teleportation.

A burst of glacial sword intent erupted out of the sword projection, making Han Li feel as if all of his blood were about to freeze solid in his veins.

His entire body instantly stiffened, and even though he was able to instantly recover, it was already too late for him to take evasive measures, so he could only raise an arm to shield himself from the sword projection.

The sword projection struck Han Li's fist before rapidly spreading upward along his arm, and right at this moment, Han Li let loose a loud roar, upon which a series of true spirit projections emerged behind him before fusing into his body.

His giant ape body instantly swelled drastically in size before transforming into a purplish-golden devilish deity with three heads and six arms. Countless silver spirit patterns also appeared over his body alongside a layer of purplish-golden scales.

The crescent-shaped sword projection was still advancing onward, but it had already slowed down significantly.

The two heads on the shoulders of the devilish deity opened their mouths in unison, and each of them released a burst of purplish-golden light to strike the crescent-shaped sword projection, destroying it upon contact.

A hint of surprise flashed through Gongshu Tian's eyes upon seeing this, and he immediately began to fly back in retreat.

A cold look appeared in the devilish deities as it raised all of its arms aside from the wounded one, then swung its fists through the air to release five balls of golden light that appeared near Gongshu Tian in a flash, then fused as one to form a radiant golden vortex.

A burst of tremendous suction erupted out of the golden vortex before encompassing Gongshu Tian's entire body, instantly immobilizing him.

Gongshu Tian immediately let loose a thunderous roar as the flames all over its body reared up, while his fiery spirit domain shrank down to only several hundred feet in size in the blink of an eye.

However, the flames within his fiery spirit domain became far more formidable as a result, turning into a golden color while giving off an unprecedentedly scorching aura.

The golden vortex around him was instantly destroyed by these golden flames, unable to withstand their immeasurable heat.

However, right at this moment, the purplish-golden devilish deity appeared behind him in a flash, following which a massive golden axis emerged behind the devilish deity.

A vast expanse of golden ripples erupted out of the axis, instantly encompassing the entire surrounding area within a radius of a thousand feet, enveloping both Gongshu Tian and his fiery spirit domain within it.

Gongshu Tian instantly fell completely still, as did the golden flames in his fiery spirit domain, and it was as if both of them had been frozen solid.

The Mantra Treasured Axis was able to immobilize everything within its scope of influence, but Gongshu Tian's fiery spirit domain was so formidable that the golden ripples were trembling violently while gradually dissipating, as if they were also unable to withstand the heat.

Han Li immediately sprang into action without any hesitation, and his nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords shot forth once again before slashing through Gongshu Tian's body.

In the blink of an eye, Gongshu Tian's body was sliced into dozens of pieces, and his nascent soul was also destroyed.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, at the end of this sequence, Han Li's complexion had turned deathly pale, but he still mustered up the strength to withdraw his Mantra Treasured Axis.

With the Mantra Treasured Axis gone, Gongshu Tian's fiery spirit domain instantly dissipated, while the fiery domain spirit in the distance also exploded before fading away.

At the same time, the fiery cage that Han Li's other nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were trapped in also reverted back into ten fiery flags, while the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords inside fell onto the ground.

Han Li paid no heed to all of this as he reverted back to his human form while focusing on sensing what was happening outside.

At the moment, the Mantra Treasured Axis was his biggest trump card, and given the complex circumstances in the True Mantra Sect ruins, he definitely didn't want to have his trump card exposed to everyone.

The sea of golden stars was able to cut off the sensory ability of spirit domains, and that was why he had gone out of his way to drag Gongshu Tian in here.

Everyone outside was still locked in battles of their own, and it appeared that none of them had detected the aura of his Mantra Treasured Axis.

This came as quite a relief to Han Li, and he stowed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords away, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which picked up Gongshu Tian's immortal treasures, then swept over his body as well before returning to Han Li.

The burst of azure light returned with the ten fiery flags, the giant crimson sword, a red storage bracelet, and a white talisman.

At this moment, Han Li's attention was focused solely on the white talisman.

It was something that he had found from the top of Gongshu Tian's head, and there were several squiggly spirit patterns engraved onto it, giving off a peculiar aura fluctuation that resembled spiritual power, but was also somewhat different.

He examined all of the items briefly before stowing them away as now wasn't the time to be studying them in depth.

Han Li then flipped a hand over to produce a green talisman that he adhered to his own arm, and radiant green light seeped into the arm from the talisman, quickly healing the wound there until there was only an imperceptible red mark left.

A pleased look appeared on his face upon seeing this, and he withdrew the sea of golden starlight to reveal himself.

The pieces of Gongshu Tian's body instantly fell to the ground, and Su Liu and Chi Rong were very alarmed to see this, while Fox 3 and the others were ecstatic.

Chapter 691: Star Official

Han Li swept his gaze around the hall, then immediately flew toward Fox 3, who was locked in battle against Su Liu.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame wasn't all that powerful, but his golden mirror was able to slow down all attacks, providing immense defensive value, and with his assistance, Bi She should be able to hold her own against Chi Rong for now.

In contrast, Fox 3's situation was a little more dire, and at this point, all he could do was passively defend against Su Liu's lightning attacks.

Upon spotting the approaching Han Li, Su Liu opened his mouth to release a ball of five-colored light, which transformed into an antiquated five-colored cauldron.

A plume of five-colored lightning threads then erupted out of the top of the cauldron, and it transformed into a five-colored lightning net that descended upon Han Li.

However, right at this moment, a burst of golden lightning abruptly erupted out of Han Li's body, and he instantly vanished from the spot, causing the five-colored lightning net to completely miss its target.

In the next instant, a burst of golden lightning appeared behind Chi Rong, and Han Li emerged out of thin air without any warning before sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that hurtled directly toward Chi Rong.

Chi Rong was very much taken aback by this turn of events, and a burst of crimson light erupted out of his body alongside countless crimson runes, which revolved above his head in a frenzy.

In the blink of an eye, a giant crimson shield took shape, and the nine swords came crashing down upon it with a resounding boom.

The crimson shield trembled violently amid an eruption of crimson and azure light, and it was able to temporarily keep the nine swords at bay.

However, this crimson shield was something that he had conjured up on very short notice, and it was already beginning to crack, indicating that it wouldn't be able to last much longer.

Chi Rong immediately attempted to flee the scene, but right at this moment, a large golden net suddenly appeared before him.

It was the same net that was formed by Han Li's interwoven time law threads, and it immediately ensnared him while releasing formidable time law power fluctuations that immobilized him in mid-air.

A cold gleam flashed through Han Li's eyes as he thrust a palm forward, and a giant golden palm projection instantly appeared above Chi Rong's head before crashing down with tremendous power.

A dull thump rang out as Chi Rong's body exploded, but not into flesh and blood. Instead, it had exploded into balls of crimson flames that scattered in all directions.

Immediately thereafter, an ancient incantation rang out, and the balls of crimson flames converged in the distance to reform Chi Rong's body, except he was looking much paler than before.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Bi She had been completely dumbstruck by this abrupt turn of events, and only now did they snap back to their senses before rushing over to Han Li's side.

"I don't think I've ever met a Golden Immortal like you. You're the first opponent that I've been excited to fight for the past ten thousand years," Chi Rong said with intense killing intent in his eyes.

Han Li paid no heed to this as he made a hand seal, and his nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly transformed into nine enormous azure swords with arcs of golden lightning dancing over them.

A rumbling thunderclap rang out as nine giant swords hurtled directly toward Chi Rong, while the net formed by time law threads vanished into Han Li's time spirit domain, seemingly having concealed itself again.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Bi She exchanged a glance with each other upon seeing this, then immediately sprang into action as well.

The former chanted an incantation before sweeping his crimson fan through the air, and a resounding boom rang out as another fiery phoenix flew out of the fan before swooping down upon Chi Rong.

Bi She also made a hand seal, and bright blue light erupted out of her body as the giant blue serpentine projection reappeared behind her.

The serpentine projection opened its mouth to release a burst of blue mist, which split up into four or five misty blue serpents that pounced at Chi Rong from another direction.

With the three of them joining forces, their collective attacks carried devastating power, and with the time spirit domain on their side, their teamwork was completely flawless.

Even a cultivator of Chi Rong's power didn't dare to take the attacks from the trio head-on, and he shot back in retreat while sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing a glowing white pouch that clashed against one of Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The pouch instantly exploded upon contact, and tens of thousand of dark red insects the size of grains of rice emerged from within, forming a dark red cloud that emitted a thunderous buzzing sound.

There were specks of red flames burning over the bodies of these tiny insects, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold, and the swarm was instantly scattered upon being struck by the attacks from Han Li's trio.

Immediately thereafter, the insects began to fly away in all directions in a speedy and agile fashion, and virtually none of them had been killed by the oncoming attacks.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame's expression changed drastically at the sight of these insects, and he instantly stopped cold in his tracks.

Han Li and Bi She faltered slightly upon seeing this, then stopped where they were as well, but they continued to unleash more attacks.

All of a sudden, a dark red flute appeared in Chi Rong's grasp, but instead of blowing on it, he swept it through the air a few times, then pressed his fingers over the holes of the flute in a certain sequence.

Melodious flute music rang out, and the scattered insects instantly flew further away in all directions, as if they had received some type of instruction, skirting around the attacks from Han Li's trio before flying toward them.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and azure light began to flash over his body, while Bi She also raised her hands in preparation to attack.

"Look out, fellow daoists! Those are Fire Age Fireflies that are capable of burning through the lifespans of others! Make sure you don't let them get close to you, and leave them to me!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame suddenly declared.

He summoned a dark red peptachord as he spoke, then quickly ran his fingers over its strings, producing stunning music that resembled draconic roars and rumbling thunderclaps.

As soon as the Fire Age Fireflies heard this music, they instantly stopped cold in their tracks and began to circle around on the spot as if they were drunk.

"That's the Vast Sea Dragon Roar Melody! How do you know how to play this melody?" Chi Rong asked as he turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame with a stunned expression.

As soon as he stopped in his tracks, the attacks from Han Li's trio instantly caught up to him, but he remained calm and collected as he made a grabbing motion to summon a large crimson bell, which began to chime in an urgent fashion.

All of a sudden, everything around the bell became extremely slow, and the attacks from Han Li's trio were still flying onward, but they had also been slowed down significantly.

Chi Rong then began to chant an incantation, and a burst of crimson light emerged over his body, following which he vanished into his fiery spirit domain.

As soon as he disappeared, the attacks from Han Li's trio finally struck the crimson bell, which shattered upon contact, restoring the surrounding flow of time back to normal.

Immediately thereafter, Chi Rong reappeared elsewhere before immediately turning his gaze to Immortal Lord Hot Flame, who also turned to look at him with a bewildered expression.

After scrutinizing Immortal Lord Hot Flame for a while, a hint of surprise and elation appeared on his face as he exclaimed, "You're Senior Martial Brother Huo Zhuozi!"

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, and both he and Bi She refrained from attacking Chi Rong for now.

Right at this moment, an urgent voice rang out from afar.

"Oi, if you're not going to fight, then can I get some help over here?"

Han Li turned in that direction to find that Fox 3 was in a rather dire situation, having almost been backed into a corner by Su Liu.

He immediately made a hand seal, and a large golden net appeared above Su Liu before descending upon him.

Even before the net had fully descended, it was already releasing a burst of formidable time law powers.

Even though Su Liu had been fighting against Fox 3 this entire time, he had constantly been keeping a close eye on the other battle as well, so he was already aware of just how powerful the golden net was.

In response, he quickly made a hand seal, and the five-colored cauldron beside him instantly rose up into the air, following which a plume of five-colored lightning threads erupted forth from within, forming a net of lightning.

The two nets clashed, and the lightning net and the five-colored cauldron were instantly immobilized, but the golden net was also kept at bay for an instant.

Taking advantage of this brief window of opportunity, Su Liu shot forth to the side as an arc of five-colored lightning, appearing several hundred feet away just an instant later.

Fox 3 hurriedly flew back in retreat to open up some distance between them, while Chi Rong said, "Hold on a second, Fellow Daoist Su Liu, I have some things that I want to ask them."

Su Liu took a glance at the golden net, and a hint of wariness flashed through his eyes as he obliged with Chi Rong's request.

"Master once told me that I had a senior martial brother. The fact that you're able to tame Master's Fire Age Fireflies means that you must be Senior Martial Brother Huo Zhuozi!" Chi Rong said as he stared intently at Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

"Who is this master that you're referring to?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked in a skeptical manner.

"My master's name is Qi Mozi," Chi Rong replied in a reverent voice.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame immediately shuddered upon hearing this, and he asked in a trembling voice, "Master is still alive?"

Thinking back to everything that he had seen in the ruins, Han Li already guessed that Qi Mozi was most likely still alive, and he turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame with a peculiar look in his eyes.

"What do you mean by that, Senior Martial Brother? With our master's unfathomable powers, what could've possibly led to his demise?" Chi Rong asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"This is... This is fantastic news!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame murmured to himself as tears welled up in his eyes.

Meanwhile, Su Liu was looking on with his brows tightly furrowed in contemplation.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame suppressed the joy in his heart as he said, "Our master must've been extremely fortunate to have survived the fall of our sect all those years ago. May I ask where he is right now?"

A peculiar look appeared on Chi Rong's face upon hearing this, and only after a long silence did he reply, "Our master is currently serving as a star official at the Heavenly Court."

Chapter 692: Circumstances Behind the Sect's Demise

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was instantly rooted to the spot upon hearing this, following which an incredulous look appeared on his face.

"Why is Master serving at the Heavenly Court?"

Han Li had already anticipated this, and his gaze roamed over Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Chi Rong in a contemplative fashion.

Su Liu seemed to be aware of what had happened all those years ago as well, and he was observing the two disciple brothers with a look that was bordering on amusement.

"The circumstances from back then are rather complex, so you should ask Master directly when you see him. For now, let's join forces and take care of these Reincarnation Palace scoundrels first," Chi Rong said with slightly furrowed brows.

Fox 3 and Bi She exchanged a complex glance with each other upon hearing this.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame appeared to be rather insignificant, but given the current circumstances, even a slight change in the power balance would severely impact the state of the battlefield.

On top of that, without Immortal Lord Hot Flame on their side to tame the Fire Age Fireflies, they were not going to be easy to deal with.

A hesitant look appeared on Immortal Lord Hot Flame's face upon hearing this.

"Is it still not already clear enough to you, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame? Qi Mozi was only able to survive the demise of the True Mantra Sect as he had already betrayed the sect and defected to the Heavenly Court well in advance!" Han Li declared.

Chi Rong's expression instantly darkened significantly upon hearing this, and he turned to Han Li with a furious expression as he spat through gritted teeth, "Who are you to be referring to my master directly by his name?"

"Why did Master do this?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked.

"Why do you say that like our master did something wrong? At the height of its powers, the True Mantra Sect was the sole dominant force in the entire Black Soil Immortal Region, but it was still nothing compared with the Heavenly Court. It's just a pity that aside from our master, everyone in the sect denied this fact, harboring delusions that the sect could coexist with the Heavenly Court in harmony," Chi Rong sneered.

"That's impossible... Our patriarch was always so kind and benevolent. Even though our sect was going from strength to strength, we never had any conflict with the Heavenly Court, and we've evenly actively suppressed our own expansion. Otherwise, given our patriarch's powers and reputation, we could've easily taken several of the nearby immortal regions.

“On top of that, we were in support of the Heavenly Court's plan to establish the Four Allies Immortal Palace to oversee the four allied immortal regions, but it was the Heavenly Court that went back on their word to attack us," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said in a disbelieving voice.

"I didn't think you were so naive, Senior Martial Brother. No wonder Master made up an excuse to send you away from the sect in advance. Back then, the Heavenly Court had proposed for the True Mantra Sect to nominate a disciple to serve as the palace master of the Four Allies Immortal Palace in order to forge a friendly alliance with the True Mantra Sect.

“On the surface, it appeared to be an act of appeasement, but in reality, it was nothing more than a form of placation," Chi Rong scoffed.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was still rather perplexed upon hearing this, but Han Li was already able to read between the lines, and he said, "So it was all a ploy to divide and conquer the True Mantra Sect. Even without this Four Allies Immortal Palace, the four immortal regions were all in the True Mantra Sect's scope of influence anyway, so the Heavenly Court was essentially just gifting the True Mantra Sect control of an area that they had already had control over.

“Once the Immortal Palace is established, it'll gradually grow more and more distant from the True Mantra Sect, becoming a thorn in its side. The fact that the True Mantra Sect agreed to this proposal at all is already a huge concession, so why is it that the Heavenly Court still decided to wipe out the sect?"

Chi Rong took a glance at Han Li, then said in a meaningful voice, "If the True Mantra Sect had accepted the Heavenly Court's proposal to make Master the first palace master of the Four Allies Immortal Palace instead of insisting on nominating Mu Yan, perhaps the sect would've ultimately fallen into destitution anyway, but it definitely wouldn't have been wiped out in such brutal fashion."

At this point, realization had dawned upon Immortal Lord Hot Flame as well, and he asked, "You're saying that master had already defected to the Heavenly Court even before the Heavenly Court sent those envoys to our sect to discuss this matter?"

"That's right. In fact, our master was the one who proposed the establishment of the Four Allies Immortal Palace to the Heavenly Court. If things had continued according to their original trajectory, then a battle between the sect and the Heavenly Court would've been inevitable. Our master was trying to find a way for our sect to survive," Chi Rong replied with a nod.

"Don't make him sound so noble! He was trying to find a way for the sect to survive? All he did was sacrifice the sect's interests for his own selfish gain! If he wanted to defect to the Heavenly Court, then he would've had to prove himself useful, and what better way to do that than to offer up the heads of Patriarch Miro and his four disciples on a silver platter?" Han Li sneered.

At this point, Chi Rong couldn't be bothered to try and make any further excuses for Qi Mozi, and he merely replied, "Patriarch Miro was the biggest threat to the Time Dao Ancestor, so he would've ultimately met his demise regardless of whether Master decided to take this route."

"So the proposal to establish the Four Allies Immortal Palace and for one of Patriarch Miro's disciples to serve as its first palace master was nothing more than a sham. The Heavenly Court only used this excuse to send those envoys into the True Mantra Sect as scouts in preparation to take down the sect," Han Li said in a derisive fashion.

Chi Rong's expression darkened even further upon hearing this, and he turned to Han Li with barely repressible fury in his eyes.

At the same time, he couldn't help but wonder how Han Li was able to be so spot-on with all of his analysis of this situation;

Immortal Lord Hot Flame took a moment to compose himself, then said, "I have another question: who was the mysterious individual that suddenly came to visit the True Mantra Sect while the Heavenly Court's envoys were here?"

"It was the palace master of our Reincarnation Palace," Fox 3 replied before Chi Rong had a chance to.

Han Li turned to Fox 3 with a surprised expression upon hearing this.

"Our palace master came to warn Patriarch Miro of the Heavenly Court's intentions. Unfortunately, Patriarch Miro had some deep-rooted biases against the Gray Realm, and he regarded our palace master as untrustworthy due to our Reincarnation Palace's connection to the Gray Realm.

“Hence, he wasn't willing to join forces with our Reincarnation Palace. Otherwise, there's no way that he would have perished under such tragic circumstances," Fox 3 sighed.

This was a clear indication of just how wary cultivators of the True Immortal Realm were of beings from the Gray Realm.

"So that means you already knew the truth behind our True Mantra Sect's demise even before coming here. In that case, why did you deceive me?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked with tightly furrowed brows.

Fox 3 hesitated momentarily, then replied in a candid fashion, "Firstly, I didn't know if you were actually completely oblivious to the circumstances leading to the demise of the sect, and secondly, I really did need you to lead me into these ruins."

"Why are you still wasting time talking to him, Senior Martial Brother? Do you not want to return to the Golden Origin Immortal Region with me to see our master?" Chi Rong asked with a disdainful expression.

"I came here to find out the truth behind the demise of our sect, and I fully intend to get the answers that I came here for. I want to know what kind of role our master played back then," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as he turned to Chi Rong.

"Is it not already obvious enough? He was a traitor! Your senior martial uncles, Mu Yan and He Ze, both perished by his hands," Fox 3 declared in an expressionless manner.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, and he immediately understood why He Ze had told him to kill Qi Mozi back in the Water Divination Palace, and why Mu Yan had been filled with so much resentment and indignation at his time of death.

"What happened after that visit from the Reincarnation Palace Master?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame asked as he turned to Fox 3.

Fox 3 took a moment to collect his thoughts, then replied, "Patriarch Miro didn't agree to join forces with our Reincarnation Palace, but the seed of doubt had been sowed in his mind, so he paid a visit to the Devil Realm to borrow a spatial immortal treasure from the Devilish Monarch using a time-attribute immortal treasure as collateral.

“He used the immortal treasure to secretly bolster the True Mantra Sect's protective array, and if he had successfully completed the procedure, then even if the Heavenly Court had attacked, the sect would've been able to put up some resistance. Unfortunately..."

Immortal Lord Hot Flame could already guess what Fox 3 was going to say, but he still couldn't help but ask, "Unfortunately what?"

"Unfortunately, Qi Mozi reported Patriarch Miro's meeting with our Reincarnation Palace Master to the Heavenly Court, so the Heavenly Court attacked the True Mantra Sect, accusing it of colluding with the Reincarnation Palace and the Gray Realm. The True Mantra Sect's new protective array still hadn't been completed, and Patriarch Miro was weakened from the strain of setting up the array, so the sect was wiped out," Fox 3 sighed.

"No one could've anticipated that the Time Dao Ancestor would make an appearance during the battle to kill Patriarch Miro. Both of them possessed unfathomable power, and their battle spread fear and panic across the entire Black Soil Immortal Region.

“If it weren't for the conscious effort that Patriarch Miro had made to keep the battle within the boundaries of the True Mantra Sect, much more would've been destroyed than just this one sect," Fox 3 continued.

"Up to this point, you've only mentioned three of Patriarch Miro's five disciples. What happened to the other two?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"After the battle, Jin Yuanzi vanished for a long time. It's said that he later returned at a far higher cultivation base than at the time of the sect's destruction and challenged the Time Dao Ancestor, but was also killed. As for Wu Yangzi, he joined our Reincarnation Palace and is currently serving as a deputy palace master," Fox 3 replied.

"Senior Martial Uncle Wu is still alive?"

At this point, Immortal Lord Hot Flame didn't know whether he should be elated or concerned in response to this news.

"Back when our palace master visited Patriarch Miro, Deputy Palace Master Wu had also been present, and he was the only one willing to heed our palace master's warning. Unfortunately, he couldn't go against his master's wishes, and he couldn't join our Reincarnation Palace on his own.

“However, after the event, he did contact our palace master in secret, imploring our palace master to save Patriarch Miro should he ever be in life-threatening danger, but due to Qi Mozi's betrayal, everything happened far too abruptly, and our palace master was only able to save him," Fox 3 said.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame fell silent, while Han Li was mulling over what he had just heard.